<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-09-09T00:09:09.899Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-09-09T00:09:09.899Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Learning to Code in your 30s with Patrick San Juan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-learning-to-code-in-your-30s-patrick-san-juan/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-learning-to-code-in-your-30s-patrick-san-juan/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T17:33:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I'm joined by Patrick San Juan, a software engineer who first learned to code in his 30s. I've known Patrick since the early days of freeCodeCamp. He has always been a positive, supportive force within the community. Patrick grew up the son of first-generation immigrants from the Philippines. His]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rediscovering The Joy Of Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/rediscovering-joy-happiness-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/rediscovering-joy-happiness-design/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pratik Joglekar takes a philosophical approach to remind designers about the lost joy within themselves by effectively placing massive importance on mindfulness, introspection, and forward-looking. Without joy, the work we do would feel meaningless. To prevent it from happening, check out a few ideas that would help rediscover that spark of joy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Pratik Joglekar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Scraping with Google Sheets – How to Scrape Web Pages with Built-in Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-scraping-google-sheets/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-scraping-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T21:14:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You read that right – you can practice web scraping without leaving your happy place: Google Sheets. Google Sheets has five built-in functions that help you import data from other sheets and other web pages. We'll walk through all of them in order from easiest (most limited) to hardest (most]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Java in Ubuntu – JDK Linux Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-java-in-ubuntu/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-java-in-ubuntu/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Installing software on Linux is usually easier, or at least that's what it seems like. But this is usually not the case as we've come to a realization that installing and configuring some specific tools on Linux might be more time-consuming than on Windows or MacOS. An example of this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How JavaScript String Concatenation Works – the "+" Operator vs the "+=" Operator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-string-concatenation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-string-concatenation/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T18:50:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[String concatenation is a common task that we do often. String concatenation is the operation of joining character strings end-to-end. For example, the concatenation of "snow" and "ball" is "snowball". In this article, I will be showing two methods by which you can concatenate strings in JavaScript. I will also]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Object-Oriented Programming in Python – Explained in Plain English]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/object-oriented-programming-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/object-oriented-programming-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T18:39:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> “Any fool can know. The point is to understand.” - Albert Einstein Object-oriented programming is a popular way to write computer programs. Because of this, all programmers should understand what OOP is, what languages you can use to program this way, and why it is important. When asked in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master the T3 Stack and Build a YouTube Clone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-the-t3-stack-and-build-a-youtube-clone/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-the-t3-stack-and-build-a-youtube-clone/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T16:35:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a full-featured YouTube clone requres a deep understanding of a wide variety of technologies. If you want to gain that understading, we have a course for you. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use the T3 stack to create]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Remove Empty Rows and Columns in Google Sheets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-empty-rows-and-columns-in-google-sheets/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-empty-rows-and-columns-in-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T07:10:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you will learn how to remove empty rows and columns from Google Sheets using Google Apps Script. A while ago I wrote an article on how to remove empty rows and columns from Google Sheets [https://kcl.hashnode.dev/how-to-delete-empty-rows-and-columns-in-google-sheets] .  I recently revisited that article and I now present]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nibesh Khadka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Diagrams as Code with Mermaid, GitHub, and Visual Studio Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/diagrams-as-code-with-mermaid-github-and-vs-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/diagrams-as-code-with-mermaid-github-and-vs-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T20:51:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Diagrams are an important part of technical documentation. In this article we will explore how we can use code to generate diagrams and leverage them in Markdown.  Here is an example of how a code generated diagram looks like: Diagram generated by codeNo tools, no dragging, aligning and snapping]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Contribute to Open-Source Projects – A Handbook for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-contribute-to-open-source-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-contribute-to-open-source-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T15:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past decade, open-source projects have become the backbone of the technology ecosystem. They power everything from applications to innovations across different fields. These collaborative inventions bring together people with different skill sets including developers, designers, and tech enthusiasts in general with one goal in mind to build: to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hillary Nyakundi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Signal Processing and Systems in Programming – Guide for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/signal-processing-and-systems-in-programming/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/signal-processing-and-systems-in-programming/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T14:49:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Signal processing is an important field in engineering and programming.  Basically, it allows engineers and programmers to improve data so that people can use it more effectively. For example, it is thanks to signal processing that much of the background noise in a phone call is removed. This way,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Long Live The Test Pyramid]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/long-live-test-pyramid/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/long-live-test-pyramid/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is the Test Pyramid really dead? Discover the more contemporary testing strategies and evaluate the Test Pyramid’s relevance in today’s software development practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ramona Schwering)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generating Real-Time Audio Sentiment Analysis With AI]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/generating-real-time-audio-sentiment-analysis-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/generating-real-time-audio-sentiment-analysis-ai/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Joas Pambou builds the tool to provide a sentiment score in **real-time** with enhanced user experience by providing multilingual support. You will use an OpenAI library called Whisper that transcribes audio files into text and detects the language, and Gradio, a UI framework, to establish the interface.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joas Pambou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A September Of Never Ending Adventures (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-september-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-september-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T08:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s get ready for September with some fresh wallpaper designs! Created with love by artists and designers from across the globe, the wallpapers in this collection come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Falling For Oklch: A Love Story Of Color Spaces, Gamuts, And CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/oklch-color-spaces-gamuts-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/oklch-color-spaces-gamuts-css/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS Color Module Level 4 specification defined a slew of new color features when it became a candidate recommendation in 2022, including Oklab and Oklch, which have widened the field of color we have to work with. Explore the Oklch color space and how to start using it in CSS today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Double Diamond Design Process]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/improving-double-diamond-design-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/improving-double-diamond-design-process/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The so-called “Double Diamond” is a great way of visualizing an ideal design process — but it’s just not the way most companies deliver new projects or services. Andy Budd proposes a new “Double Diamond” idea that better aligns with the way work actually gets done and highlights the place where design has the most leverage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andy Budd)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Few Interesting Ways To Use CSS Shadows For More Than Depth]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/interesting-ways-use-css-shadows/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/interesting-ways-use-css-shadows/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We often think of shadows in CSS as something to reach for when we want to add depth to a design. But shadows can be used for more than depth. Let’s experiment with different shadows — two CSS properties and a filter — to make interesting hover effects, different text styles, and even casting shadows on other shadows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Preethi Sam)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better Context Menus With Safe Triangles]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/better-context-menus-safe-triangles/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/better-context-menus-safe-triangles/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how to improve the user experience of nested menus and tackle a minor yet common issue with them when the user’s pointer leaves the menu item for a moment, and the nested menu goes away, requiring the user to re-hover and try again. A well-known concept called the “safe triangle” solves this problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Costa Alexoglou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern Methods For Improving Drupal’s Largest Contentful Paint Core Web Vital]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/methods-improving-drupal-largest-contentful-paint-core-web-vital/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/methods-improving-drupal-largest-contentful-paint-core-web-vital/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The background image used in the hero component, which is slow to load, is a very common problem with any component that uses a large image file as a background image. In this article, Mike Herchel walks you through how to tackle this common performance issue using modern techniques.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mike Herchel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Knip: An Automated Tool For Finding Unused Files, Exports, And Dependencies]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/knip-automated-tool-find-unused-files-exports-dependencies/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/knip-automated-tool-find-unused-files-exports-dependencies/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of the projects have at least a few unused files, exports, and dependencies lying around, often because it’s difficult knowing when one thing relies on another and scary removing something you’re not sure is in use. Lars Kappert shares a tool he’s been working on that offers a solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lars Kappert)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Accessible Text Over Images: Best Practices, Techniques And Resources (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/designing-accessible-text-over-images-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/designing-accessible-text-over-images-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In part 2 of the series, Hannah Milan reviews various accessible text over images techniques for designing your content, including framing the image, soft-colored gradients technique, text styles and text position, solid color shapes, and use of colored backgrounds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Hannah Milan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>