<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-04-26T00:09:21.404Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-04-26T00:09:21.404Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Java Used For in 2023? The Java Programming Language and Java Platform Strengths]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-java-used-for/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-java-used-for/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T21:26:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Java is a very popular programming language you can use to create a variety of software applications. It's an object-oriented language that was made to be simple to read, write, and learn.  Millions of developers use Java to create everything from desktop programs to sophisticated web apps. This makes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Supercharge Your Studying with Python, Anki, and ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/supercharged-studying-with-python-anki-chatgpt/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/supercharged-studying-with-python-anki-chatgpt/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T20:35:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have heard how students can use ChatGPT [https://chat.openai.com] to cheat on assignments. But we should also talk about what a fantastic study tool it can be.  In this article we'll discuss how you can use ChatGPT to help you study and learn new skills. You'll see how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Otavio Ehrenberger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Insert into a JavaScript Array at a Specific Index – JS Push]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/insert-into-javascript-array-at-specific-index/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/insert-into-javascript-array-at-specific-index/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T18:14:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript arrays are an important part of the language. They allow you to store and manipulate collections of data. Sometimes, you may need to insert a new element into an array at a specific index. To accomplish this task, you can use the push() method or the splice()  method.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering Zustand: A Simple and Efficient State Management Library for React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/zustand-course-react-state-management/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/zustand-course-react-state-management/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T17:21:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern web applications demand efficient and easy-to-use state management solutions that don't compromise on flexibility or performance. Zustand, a minimalistic state management library for React, offers just that. We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you unlock the full potential of Zustand and create]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Upload Files to Amazon S3 with Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-upload-files-to-aws-s3-with-node/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-upload-files-to-aws-s3-with-node/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T16:31:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[File upload is a common feature in a lot of modern applications. These platforms accept different file formats, including jpeg, png, gif, pdf, txt, zip, and mp3.  Some applications will also restrict uploads to a specific file type. For example, when uploading your resume on LinkedIn, you will see]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fiyinfoluwa Akinsiku</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an Interactive Accordion Component with React and GSAP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-interactive-accordion-component-with-react-and-gsap/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-interactive-accordion-component-with-react-and-gsap/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T15:47:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As websites become more sophisticated and user expectations continue to rise, web developers must search for ways to create more engaging and interactive user interfaces.  One powerful tool in a developer's arsenal is the accordion component, a versatile and widely-used element found on nearly every website.  In this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaja Ibifubara David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Could UX Be The Key To Unlocking Web3 Mass Adoption?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/ux-web3-mass-adoption/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/ux-web3-mass-adoption/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decentralized web is our new reality, but Web3 UX is shockingly bad. In this article, Pete Boyle addresses the major shortcomings in Web3 adoption and how we might be able to solve them and make the entire ecosystem more user-friendly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Pete Boyle)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Large Language Models and Cybersecurity – What You Should Know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/large-language-models-and-cybersecurity/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/large-language-models-and-cybersecurity/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T01:03:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT has had well over a billion visits since its release. Now, what happens when you combine the greatest language learning model of the decade with malicious hacking...what could go wrong? 💀 In this article, we'll explore what artificial intelligence is, its current state, how large language models like ChatGPT]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Iwugo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get the Current URL with JavaScript – JS Location Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-the-current-url-with-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-the-current-url-with-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T00:34:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a web developer, you'll work with JavaScript when building dynamic and interactive web applications. One common task that you'll need to perform is getting the current URL of a web page. In this article, you will learn how to get the current URL using JavaScript's Location object. I'll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use ChatGPT – Prompts for Data Scientists]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-chatgpt-for-data-scientists/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-chatgpt-for-data-scientists/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T23:01:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days, many people are concerned with the way AI is evolving. They see it effortlessly solving problems, performing tasks quickly and accurately, and doing jobs easily and efficiently.  And while some people are scared, others are actually embracing it. I'm one of those people who are embracing it,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Server Side Rendering in JavaScript – SSR vs CSR Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/server-side-rendering-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/server-side-rendering-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T22:12:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The concept of Server Side Rendering (SSR) is often misunderstood. So my aim in this article is to bring clarity to this process and how it works.  Here's what we'll cover in this guide:  1. What is server side rendering? What are its pros and cons when compared]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Gary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Potentially Dangerous Non-Accessibility Of Cookie Notices]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/potentially-dangerous-non-accessibility-cookie-notices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/potentially-dangerous-non-accessibility-cookie-notices/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this piece, a Web Content Accessibility Guidelines (WCAG) auditor shares some cookie banner error patterns that can massively hurt a page’s overall conformance. Let’s explore what to look out for with this omnipresent piece of the web interface.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Marcus Herrmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring The Potential Of Web Workers For Multithreading On The Web]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/potential-web-workers-multithreading-web/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/potential-web-workers-multithreading-web/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Sarah Oke Okolo explores the importance of Web Workers for multithreading on the web, including the limitations and considerations of using them and the strategies for mitigating potential issues associated with them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sarah Oke Okolo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building And Dockerizing A Node.js App With Stateless Architecture With Help From Kinsta]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/building-dockerizing-nodejs-app-stateless-architecture-kinsta/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/building-dockerizing-nodejs-app-stateless-architecture-kinsta/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dockerizing your Node.js apps can lead to smashing success—offering consistency, easy debugging, and hassle-free dependency management. When you host this container on Kinsta, you also benefit from high-speed performance, robust security, and top-notch scalability. By combining these two, you'll surely have a whale of a time as you sail smoothly through the development seas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tejas Kumar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Color Mechanics In UI Kits]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/color-mechanics-ui-kits/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/color-mechanics-ui-kits/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Adel Khamatov shares a model of color mechanics that he came up with during research on developing UI kits and illustrates an approach to solving related problems with best practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adel Khamatov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 59 With Chiara Aliotta: What Is Design Storytelling?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/smashing-podcast-episode-59/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/smashing-podcast-episode-59/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of The Smashing Podcast, we take a look at design storytelling. What is it, and how can it help us shape digital experiences? Vitaly talks to Chiara Aliotta to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Design Thinking?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/what-is-design-thinking/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/what-is-design-thinking/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered if things could have been done differently? But not sure how? Well, then, do not fall in love with the solution, but fall in love with the problem! Here’s an article to dive deep into how design thinking could do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Krithika Subramanian)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passkeys: What the Heck and Why?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377305</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/passkeys-what-the-heck-and-why/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T17:41:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These things called passkeys sure are making the rounds these days. They were a main attraction at W3C TPAC 2022, gained support in Safari 16, are finding their way into macOS and iOS, and are slated to …
Passkeys: What the Heck and Why? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Neal Fennimore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Design An Effective User Onboarding Flow]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/design-effective-user-onboarding-flow/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/design-effective-user-onboarding-flow/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to maximize conversions or collect necessary user information for other purposes, a user onboarding flow is necessary. In this article, you will learn how, with the help of Feathery, to design an effective user onboarding flow for your app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Suzanne Scacca)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Protect Your App With A Threat Model Based On JSONDiff]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/protect-app-threat-model-jsondiff/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/protect-app-threat-model-jsondiff/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a developer who wants to concentrate on delivering a killer application rather than worrying about countless security issues, threat model documents can help you do that. With small architectural changes, we can make these threats manageable and prevent them in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zack Grossbart &amp; Terry Yao)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Algorithms: Skills Of Designers That AI Can’t Replicate]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/skills-designers-ai-cant-replicate/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/skills-designers-ai-cant-replicate/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article highlights non-technical skills like curiosity, observation, empathy, advocacy, visual communication, and collaboration that designers routinely use in their process to make a difference through design. AI can be used to augment designers’ workflow instead of replacing people.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lyndon Cerejo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swing Into April (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With April just around the corner, we have a new collection of desktop and mobile wallpapers waiting for you to celebrate the beginning of the new month. Designed by creatives from all across the globe, the wallpapers come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Comprehensive Checklist For Running Design Workshops]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/organizing-design-workshops-checklist/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/organizing-design-workshops-checklist/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Workshops are all about people: they involve people, are conducted by people, and aim to close the gaps in people’s communication. Slava Shestopalov shares a checklist with everything you need to keep in mind when running a workshop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Slava Shestopalov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fine-Grained Access Handling And Data Management With Row-Level Security]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/access-handling-data-management-row-level-security/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/access-handling-data-management-row-level-security/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dealing with sensitive data is an important topic for any app. In this article, you will find out how to handle sensitive or confidential information in your apps and what Row-Level Security means.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Handoff Is No Handoff]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/best-handoff-is-no-handoff/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/best-handoff-is-no-handoff/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design handoffs are inefficient and painful. They cause frustration, friction and a lot of back and forth. Can we avoid them altogether? Of course we can! Let’s see how to do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>