<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-01-26T00:10:17.393Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-01-26T00:10:17.393Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Running the Biggest Programming Channel on YouTube with freeCodeCamp's Beau Carnes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-biggest-youtube-programming-channel-beau-carnes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-biggest-youtube-programming-channel-beau-carnes/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T19:50:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beau Carnes has run the freeCodeCamp community YouTube channel for the past 5 years, taking it from 75,000 subscribers all the way up to 9 million. Beau started out working as a Special Education teacher at a Michigan high school. He taught himself how to code before working as a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Hash Map? Time Complexity and Two Sum Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-hash-map/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-hash-map/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T17:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A hash table or hash map, is a data structure that helps with mapping keys to values for highly efficient operations like the lookup, insertion and deletion operations. In this tutorial, you'll learn the following:  * Constant and linear time complexity.  * Why use a hash map?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sule-Balogun Olanrewaju Ganiu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Natural Language Processing Techniques for Topic Identification – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/topic-identification-using-natural-language-processing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/topic-identification-using-natural-language-processing/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T16:16:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's a lot of textual information available these days. It ranges from articles to social media posts and research papers. So our ability to distill meaningful insights is key. This helps us make informed decisions in a wide array of contexts.  For example, you can analyze a large volume]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ibrahim Abayomi Ogunbiyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn LangChain and Gen AI by Building 6 Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-langchain-and-gen-ai-by-building-6-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-langchain-and-gen-ai-by-building-6-projects/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T16:09:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning LangChain empowers you to seamlessly integrate advanced language models like GPT-4 into diverse applications, unlocking capabilities in natural language processing and AI-driven applications. We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build six end-to-end projects using LangChain and a variety]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Blurry Shimmer Effect]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/css-blurry-shimmer-effect/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/css-blurry-shimmer-effect/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taking inspiration from shadows, author Yair Even Or creates the same sort of thing, only with a blurring effect in place of the shadow. Read along for a step-by-step explanation of how it comes together using a combination of masks, gradients, and the good ol’ `backdrop-filter` property.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yair Even Or)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free JavaScript Bootcamp for 2024 – Learn JS with the Bad Website Club]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-webdev-and-js-bootcamps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-webdev-and-js-bootcamps/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T13:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello again, I’m Jess. I’ve been running free, online bootcamps around the freeCodeCamp Responsive Web Development and Javascript curricula since 2020.  I’m so excited to update the you all on how this has been going, while reminding you that we’ll be starting a free JavaScript bootcamp [http://badwebsite.club]  focused]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Rose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Units – When to Use rem, em, px, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-units-when-to-use-each-one/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-units-when-to-use-each-one/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T00:58:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS units allow you to measure and specify different property values. You use them to modify CSS properties such as margins, padding, height, and width to make them compatible with devices of all screen sizes. CSS units have two basic types:  * Absolute units  * Relative units Absolute]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esther Christopher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get the First Line of a Multiline String in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-the-first-line-of-a-multiline-string-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-the-first-line-of-a-multiline-string-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T23:33:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, getting the first element of an array or string is pretty easy. But when it comes to getting the first line of a multiline string, some approaches can hurt your app's performance in certain cases. In this article, we will look at the three best ways you can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Furkan Emin Can</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy Next.js Apps to Github Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-next-js-app-to-github-pages/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-next-js-app-to-github-pages/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T22:46:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I will walk you through the process of publishing a Next.js application on GitHub Pages.  What makes this guide particularly helpful is that I'll teach you how to integrate with GitHub Actions, too. This means your application will be automatically deployed every time you push code]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matéush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code Extensions to Boost Your Productivity in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-vscode-extensions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-vscode-extensions/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T22:42:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the 2023 Stack Overflow Developer Survey [https://survey.stackoverflow.co/2023/#section-most-popular-technologies-integrated-development-environment] , Visual Studio Code (also known as VSCode) ranked as the most preferred integrated developer environment (IDE) tool.  Visual Studio Code has many great features out-of-the-box, and supports a large community of extensions to add enhanced functionality.  Stack Overflow]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Natalie Pina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Back Up and Restore Azure SQL Databases]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-back-up-and-restore-sql-azure-database/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-back-up-and-restore-sql-azure-database/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T22:34:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's Azure’s provides many services via a single cloud, which lets them offer one solution for multiple corporate infrastructures. Teams use Azure because they value the opportunity to run SQL databases in the cloud and complete simple operations via the Azure portal.  But you'll need to have a way]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Tray</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Dilemma In Graphic Design: Steering Towards Excellence In Typography And Beyond]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/ai-dilemma-graphic-design-typography/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/ai-dilemma-graphic-design-typography/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI promises a major upheaval in typography, with designers finding themselves navigating both opportunities and challenges. How will it impact quality, design roles, and our use of type in the future? As we explore this new frontier, we realise that we are at a juncture as significant as Gutenberg’s press, set to redefine how we interact with text and visual communication.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Filip Paldia &amp; Jamie Clarke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Complex But Awesome CSS border-image Property]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/css-border-image-property/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/css-border-image-property/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS `border-image` property is one of those properties you undoubtedly know exists but may not have ever reached for. In this article, Temani Afif demonstrates different approaches for using `border-image` to create clever decorative accents and shapes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Front-End Tools Of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/top-frontend-tools-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/top-frontend-tools-2023/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Useful front-end tools for CSS and JavaScript developers that were most popular last year and will help you speed up your development workflow. Let’s dive in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Louis Lazaris)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SolidStart: A Different Breed Of Meta-Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/solidstart-different-breed-meta-framework/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/solidstart-different-breed-meta-framework/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready for a little exercise of pulling a framework apart and putting the pieces back together? In this article, Atila Fassina explains how meta-frameworks have evolved around core libraries in their own unique ways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API And Delightful UI Animations (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/view-transitions-api-ui-animations-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/view-transitions-api-ui-animations-part2/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API is a new — but game-changing — feature that allows us to do the types of reactive state-based UI and page transitions that have traditionally been exclusive to JavaScript frameworks. In the second half of this mini two-part series, Adrian Bece expands on the demos from the first article to demonstrate how the View Transitions API can be used to transition not just elements between two states but the transition between full views and pages in single-page and multi-page applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Magic Of New Beginnings (January 2024 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2024/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s start into the new year with a little inspiration boost: wallpapers created with love by the community for the community. Happy 2024!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Sense Of “Senseless” JavaScript Features]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/making-sense-of-senseless-javascript-features/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/making-sense-of-senseless-javascript-features/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript may be the most popular client-side language in the world, but it’s far from perfect and not without its quirks. Juan Diego Rodriguez examines several “absurd” JavaScript eccentricities and explains how they made it into the language as well as how to avoid them in your own code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>