<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-09-21T00:14:35.001Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-09-21T00:14:35.001Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Props in React.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-props-in-reactjs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-props-in-reactjs/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T20:16:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Props are an important concept to understand in React. You use props to pass data and values from one component to another to get dynamic and unique outputs.  Websites built with React like Facebook, Twitter, and Netflix use the same design patterns across many sections that just have different]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joy O. Oluwafemi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Datetime.now() – How to Get Today's Date and Time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-datetime-now-how-to-get-todays-date-and-time/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-datetime-now-how-to-get-todays-date-and-time/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T20:12:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use the datetime module in Python to retrieve data about date and time.  In this article, you'll learn how to use the datetime object from the datetime  module to get the current date and time properties. You'll also learn how to get the date and time]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code a Minecraft Clone Using React and Three.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-a-minecraft-clone-using-react-and-three-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-a-minecraft-clone-using-react-and-three-js/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T19:36:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It may not be possible to code a Minecraft clone in 30 seconds [https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MAlSjtxy5ak], but you can definitely create one in under two hours. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create a fully-functional Minecraft clone using React, JavaScript, and Three.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Configure Metadata for a Single-Page Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/configure-metadata-in-single-page-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/configure-metadata-in-single-page-applications/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T17:20:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why Metadata Matters Metadata is an integral part of any modern web app, because it's inherently tethered to search engine optimization (SEO).  Search engines and their respective results page (SERPS) rely on metadata to properly index and display relative information for each site. Also, meta tags are relied upon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Gary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to write a Good Technical Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-a-good-technical-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-a-good-technical-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T16:59:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a software developer, then you know how often you search Google to help you solve specific problems when you're coding. Every developer looks at online tutorials to solve the problems they have. To help you solve your problem, these tutorials should have a few things that make]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Avdhoot Fulsundar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Developers Should Have a YouTube Channel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-developers-should-have-a-youtube-channel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-developers-should-have-a-youtube-channel/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T16:14:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a software developer, chances are you'll be learning constantly. There is a famous quote that says, > “Forget about the kids, fathers are still learning”. This couldn't be more true in the case of coding. You constantly need to learn, develop, and upgrade your skills. And what is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nishant Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Checkerboard Background… But With Rounded Corners and Hover Styles]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373167</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-checkerboard-background-but-with-rounded-corners-and-hover-styles/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T13:19:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On one hand, creating simple checkered backgrounds with CSS is easy. On the other hand, though, unless we are one of the CSS-gradient-ninjas, we are kind of stuck with basic patterns.
At least that’s what I thought while staring at …
CSS Checkerboard Background… But With Rounded Corners and Hover Styles originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 53 With Rémi Parmentier: Can HTML Email Use Modern CSS?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/smashing-podcast-episode-53/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/smashing-podcast-episode-53/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we’re talking about HTML email. Do we still have to design like we would for IE5? Vitaly talks to expert Rémi Parmentier to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New In Gatsby 2022?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/new-gatsby-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/new-gatsby-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby has evolved quite dramatically in the last two years. In this article, Paul Scanlon explains what Gatsby can do today, and how he used some of the new features when upgrading his personal website from Gatsby 2 to Gatsby 4.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Authenticate Your React App with Passport.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-passport-authentication/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-passport-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T22:29:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authentication is a major part of any serious React application. You need to have a good and reliable way to authenticate your users in your developer tool belt. There are dozens of authentication solutions to choose from today, many of which come with a price tag. Which one should you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Selector Types – How to Select Elements to Style in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-select-elements-to-style-in-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-select-elements-to-style-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T22:01:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you want to style an element with CSS, you first have to "select" it. In this article, I'll show you seven (7) ways in which you can do that. Here's the syntax for styling elements in CSS: selector {   /* styles here */ } You have the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install OpenJDK (Free Java) – Multi OS Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/install-openjdk-free-java-multi-os-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/install-openjdk-free-java-multi-os-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T20:52:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a nutshell, there are two coexisting branches of Java: the proprietary, closed-source Oracle Java and the community-maintained open-source OpenJDK [https://github.com/openjdk/jdk]. OpenJDK is licensed under GPL-2.0 [https://github.com/openjdk/jdk/blob/master/LICENSE], and it consists of a Java Virtual Machine and a java-bytecode compiler. Since this is the easier and cheaper way, it's the one]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Otavio Ehrenberger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Retro Draggable Web Component With Lit]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/building-retro-draggable-web-component-using-lit/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/building-retro-draggable-web-component-using-lit/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s article, Andrico Karoulla explains how to create a cool draggable effect by listening to the drag events and writing some custom logic inside the handlers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andrico Karoulla)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Do Test-Driven Development with Svelte and Vitest – A Project-Based Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-do-test-driven-development-with-svelte-and-vitest/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-do-test-driven-development-with-svelte-and-vitest/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T17:20:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Test Driven Development (TDD) is one of the best ways to make sure your code is high quality and works like it's supposed to work. It can also help you create reliable builds during continuous deployments.  In this post, we will learn how to create a Svelte application using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sriram Thiagarajan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making a Real-Time Clock With a Conic Gradient Face]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373184</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/making-a-real-time-clock-with-a-conic-gradient-face/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T12:58:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gradients have been a part of the CSS spectrum for quite some time now. We see a lot of radial and linear gradients in a lot of projects, but there is one type of gradient that seems to be a …
Making a Real-Time Clock With a Conic Gradient Face originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brecht De Ruyte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rethinking Star Ratings For Readers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/rethinking-star-ratings-readers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/rethinking-star-ratings-readers/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can companies change their rating and review systems to better benefit users? Matt Athanasiou shares some steps to improve the experience of reviewing literature and other products — while also building stronger connections.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matt Athanasiou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Details on `details`]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373372</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/more-details-on-details/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T13:12:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of chatter around the ol’ <details> and <summary> elements lately! I saw Lea Verou recently tweet an observation about the element’s display behavior and that sorta splintered into more observations and usage notes from folks, including a revived …
More Details on `details` originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Headless In Times Of Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/accessibility-times-headless/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/accessibility-times-headless/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you want to make your new website as accessible as possible? Amazing, that’s a great mindset! Let’s have a closer look at the factors you should take into consideration when choosing a content management system (CMS) in terms of web accessibility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Josefine Schaefer)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When is it OK to Disable Text Selection?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373100</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/when-is-it-ok-to-disable-text-selection/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T13:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using CSS, it’s possible to prevent users from selecting text within an element using user-select: none. Now, it’s understandable why doing so might be considered “controversial”. I mean, should we be disabling standard user behaviors? Generally speaking, no, we …
When is it OK to Disable Text Selection? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Schwarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript APIs You Don’t Know About]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/javascript-api-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/javascript-api-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Juan Diego covers the least known yet extremely useful APIs, such as the Page Visibility API, Web Sharing API, Broadcast Channel API and Internationalization API. Together we will see what they are, where we should use them, and how to use them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebKit Features in Safari 16.0]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373367</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/webkit-features-in-safari-16-0/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T16:14:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whew boy, Safari 16 is officially out in the wild and it packs in a bunch of features, some new and exciting (Subgrid! Container Queries! Font Palettes!) and others we’ve been waiting on for better cross-browser support (Motion Path! Overscroll …
WebKit Features in Safari 16.0 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Basics of Remix]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373081</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-basics-of-remix/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T12:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve probably heard a lot of hype around one of the newest kids on the framework block, Remix. It may be surprising that it got its start back in 2019, but it was originally only available as a subscription-based premium …
The Basics of Remix originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brittney Postma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Sense Of WAI-ARIA: A Comprehensive Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/wai-aria-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/wai-aria-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Kate Kalcevich explains when to use ARIA and how to use it properly so that you can use ARIA in a way that’s helpful to the many disabled people who use [assistive technology](https://makeitfable.com/glossary/?utm_source=Smashing+Magazine&utm_medium=sponsored+content&utm_campaign=Upskill&utm_term=Fable&utm_content=Sept2022) to navigate the Internet. Let’s dive in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kate Kalcevich)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Interactive Figma Widgets]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372991</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/building-interactive-figma-widgets/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T13:05:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Figma has always encouraged collaboration between developers and designers. It strives on an endless treasury of community-made plugins. Need 3D elements? There’s a plugin for that. Need abstract SVGs? There’s a plugin for that, too.
That said, the design part of Figma has …
Building Interactive Figma Widgets originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eluda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet “Smart Interface Design Patterns Checklists” (Deck With 166 Cards)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/smart-interface-design-checklist-cards-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/smart-interface-design-checklist-cards-release/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet “Smart Interface Design Patterns Checklists”, a deck of 166 checklist cards to help you design and build better interfaces, faster. With accordions, mega-drop-downs, data tables, carousels, and everything in-between.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Made a Pure CSS Puzzle Game]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372952</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-i-made-a-pure-css-puzzle-game/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T13:21:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently discovered the joy of creating CSS-only games. It’s always fascinating how HTML and CSS are capable of handling the logic of an entire online game, so I had to try it! Such games usually rely on the ol’ …
How I Made a Pure CSS Puzzle Game originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One Formula To Rule Them All: The ROI Of A Design System]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/formula-roi-design-system/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/formula-roi-design-system/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design systems are a crucial success factor for digital businesses, and virtually every major player works with one. Still, they can sometimes be hard to sell to management. Here’s a ready-to-use formula to calculate the ROI of any design system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Maximilian Speicher &amp; Guido Baena Wehrmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New With Forms in 2022?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372979</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/whats-new-with-forms-in-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T13:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Browsers are constantly adding new HTML, JavaScript and CSS features. Here are some useful additions to working with forms that you might have missed…
requestSubmit()
Safari 16 will be the final browser to add support for requestSubmit.
Before we …
What’s New With Forms in 2022? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ollie Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UX Checklists For Interface Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/ux-checklists-for-interface-designers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/ux-checklists-for-interface-designers/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UX checklists with best design practices, accessibility guidelines, design system checklist, tables UX checklist, UX research methods, form design UX and flowcharts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overlapping Bar Charts]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372968</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/overlapping-bar-charts/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T13:46:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the name suggests, overlapping charts visualize two different sets of data in a single diagram. The idea is that the overlapping bars allow us to compare data, say, year-over-year. They are also useful for things like tracking progress for …
Overlapping Bar Charts originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saleh Mubashar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Realities And Myths Of Contrast And Color]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/realities-myths-contrast-color/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/realities-myths-contrast-color/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Andrew Somers, a 35-year veteran of the Hollywood film and television industry, shares his experience about the hard-fought battles and lessons learned designing for illuminated presentations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andrew Somers)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacking CSS Animation State and Playback Time]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372850</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/hacking-css-animation-state-and-playback-time/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T18:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS-only Wolfenstein is a little project that I made a few weeks ago. It was an experiment with CSS 3D transformations and animations.
Inspired by the FPS demo and another Wolfenstein CodePen, I decided to build my own version. …
Hacking CSS Animation State and Playback Time originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lu Wang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 52 With Yiying Lu: How Do You Become An NFT Artist?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/smashing-podcast-episode-52/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/smashing-podcast-episode-52/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we ask how do you go from running a creative studio to designing NFTs. Vitaly talks to artist Yiying Lu to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flutter For Front-End Web Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372853</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/flutter-for-front-end-web-developers/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T20:10:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I started as a front-end web developer and then became a Flutter developer. I think there were some concepts that helped me adopt Flutter easier. There were also some new concepts that were different.
In this article, I want to …
Flutter For Front-End Web Developers originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Obumuneme Nwabude</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Understanding Privacy, A New Smashing Book By Heather Burns]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/understanding-privacy-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/understanding-privacy-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet “Understanding Privacy”, our upcoming book on what data privacy is really about beyond scary headlines. Approx. 350 pages. eBook available in October, print shipping in November.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Accessibility And Usability Journey Of Drupal’s Primary Navigation]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/accessibility-usability-drupal-primary-navigation/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/accessibility-usability-drupal-primary-navigation/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Mike Herchel covers Drupal’s new default theme, Olivero, which is usable, accessible, robust, and beautiful and will help you improve websites’ navigation systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mike Herchel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the CSScenes, September 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373126</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/behind-the-csscenes-sept2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T20:06:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Those of you who have been reading CSS-Tricks for a while may remember that we used to publish a little thing we called CSS-Tricks Chronicles. Our friend Chris Coyier would write up a reflection from the past couple of …
Behind the CSScenes, September 2022 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haley Mills</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Brief Introduction to JAWS, NVDA, and VoiceOver]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372855</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/comparing-jaws-nvda-and-voiceover/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T17:47:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A screen reader is an important accessibility tool for people with no or limited vision. People who are blind or those with low vision can use a screen reader to navigate the computer. Screen readers will read contents on the …
A Brief Introduction to JAWS, NVDA, and VoiceOver originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilknur Eren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iShadeed’s Container Queries Lab]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373087</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/ishadeeds-container-queries-lab/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T14:29:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahmad Shadeed got an early jump on container queries and has a growing collection of examples based on everyday patterns.
And, if you missed it, his latest post on container queries does a wonderful job covering how they work since …
iShadeed’s Container Queries Lab originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Databases For Front-End Developers: The Concepts Under The Hood (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/databases-frontend-developers-concepts-under-hood/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/databases-frontend-developers-concepts-under-hood/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the second part of “Databases For Front-End Developers” series, Atila Fassina explores concepts to equip you to have your own opinions about which kinds of databases suit your specific needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful JavaScript Data Grid Libraries]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/useful-javascript-data-grid-libraries/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/useful-javascript-data-grid-libraries/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Zara Cooper provides a rundown of some popular data grid libraries that would be a great addition to any data-heavy application and shares recommendations on what factors to consider when choosing a suitable data grid library.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding The Balance (September 2022 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-september-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-september-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T08:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s welcome September with some fresh desktop wallpapers. Designed by artists and designers from across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar for the month. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Improve And Measure Your Progress Learning Web Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/improve-measure-progress-learning-web-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/improve-measure-progress-learning-web-design/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever felt overwhelmed by the number of things you need to learn? Today, we look at how [Uxcel](https://uxcel.com/) eases this transition and approaches actively learning new skills to take our careers to the next level.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shane Hudson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Makes A Great Toggle Button? (Case Study, Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/toggle-button-case-study-part-2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/toggle-button-case-study-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The problem of how to design an effective toggle button that shows the selected option clearly is a long-term open question among UI/UX designers. In this second part, Eduard Kuric explains a complex list of visual cues used by toggle buttons to communicate which of their options is active.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eduard Kuric)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Better Error Messages UX]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/error-messages-ux-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/error-messages-ux-design/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Error messages need to be easy to spot, but they also need to be helpful. Let’s explore when error messages should live above input fields and why toast error messages are usually not a very good idea.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better Video Streaming With imgix]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/better-video-streaming-with-imgix/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/better-video-streaming-with-imgix/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you need to deliver a large number of images and videos, a solution like [imgix](https://imgix.com/?utm_medium=banner&utm_source=smashingmag&utm_campaign=video-api-smashingmag-article-2022-08) can optimize and process both types of assets without you having to build it from the ground up or cobble together different solutions. Let’s take a closer look at how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Doug Sillars)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 51 With Ben Callahan: What’s The Value Of A Design System?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/smashing-podcast-episode-51/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/smashing-podcast-episode-51/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we ask how you can prove the value of a Design System and how you can pitch it effectively to stakeholders. Vitaly talks to Ben Callahan to find out more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>