<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-03-09T00:09:24.410Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-03-09T00:09:24.410Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Success At Scale: Last Chance For Pre-Sale Price]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/success-at-scale-book-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/success-at-scale-book-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our next book, “Success at Scale” is finally at the printer, which means we’ll be shipping books soon. It’s also your last chance to get the book at the presale price. Get your copy and save now!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Having Fun in Tech with  CTO and Meme Queen Cassidy Williams (Cassidoo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-cassidy-williams-cassidoo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-cassidy-williams-cassidoo/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T15:45:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week's episode of The freeCodeCamp Podcast, I interview developer-turned-CTO Cassidy Williams, also known as Cassidoo on Twitter and TikTok. She's worked in tech for over a decade as a developer at several tech companies, including Amazon and Netlify. She has gradually progressed to senior developer and now CTO.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Hooks – How to Use the useState & useEffect Hooks in Your Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-usestate-and-useeffect-hooks-in-your-project/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-usestate-and-useeffect-hooks-in-your-project/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T15:37:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hooks allow function components to have access to state and other React features, such as lifecycle methods. These Hook features were introduced to React version 16.8. One of the interesting things about the Hook features is that they let you use React without classes. This, in turn, helps simplify your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okoro Emmanuel Nzube</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement Relationship Based Access Control (ReBAC)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/implement-relationship-based-access-control/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/implement-relationship-based-access-control/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T14:08:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's digital age, managing who can access what resources is more critical than ever. That's where ReBAC comes in. It's a fresh take on authorization, focusing on the relationships between different entities rather than just assigning static roles or attributes. Traditional access control methods, like Role-Based Access Control (RBAC),]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Imran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SVG Toggle Button Tutorial – How to Handle Dark Mode with CSS and JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-handle-dark-mode-with-css-and-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-handle-dark-mode-with-css-and-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T13:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can you detect dark mode in CSS and JavaScript? How can you manually override it with a toggle button? And how can you create a sun and moon icon with SVG? In this tutorial, you will learn how to detect dark mode in CSS and JavaScript, and you will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hunor Márton Borbély</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern CSS Tooltips And Speech Bubbles (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/modern-css-tooltips-speech-bubbles-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/modern-css-tooltips-speech-bubbles-part2/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Part 1 of this series, Temani Afif explored different CSS techniques to create tooltip shapes. The main challenge was to rely on a single element and create optimized code that could easily be controlled using CSS variables to update the size, shape, and position of the tail. In this second part, you are going explore more shapes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a CRUD API – NodeJS and Express Project for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-crud-api-project/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-crud-api-project/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T11:04:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An API is a technology that powers communication between software applications on the internet. API stands for Application Programming Interface, and it is basically a set of rules and protocols that define how different software can interact with each other.  Imagine having two different programs: program A and program]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Yakubu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a 3D Art Gallery with Three.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-3d-art-gallery-with-threejs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-3d-art-gallery-with-threejs/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T16:21:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[3D web experiences can provide engaging and interactive user interfaces. And one of the best JavaScript libraries to create these experiences is Three.js. We just posed a comprehensive Three.js course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This course is designed to guide you through the process of building an interactive 3D]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up React Testing Library With Next.js – A Step-by-Step Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-setup-react-testing-library-with-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-setup-react-testing-library-with-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T15:58:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, you will learn how to set up React Testing Library in Next.js. We'll also talk about why you should always test your React applications. I'll discuss the features and benefits of using the React Testing Library to test your React applications and how to configure it with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matéush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create an Inventory List with React useReducer, Axios, and JSON Server]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-an-inventory-list-with-react-usereducer-axios-and-json-server/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-an-inventory-list-with-react-usereducer-axios-and-json-server/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T15:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to web development, it's hard to ignore React.js. It has been one of the leading user interface libraries for a decade, and it supports a lot of popular frameworks like Next.js in the background. If you are a React developer, you likely appreciate its component-based architecture, uni-directional]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TAPAS ADHIKARY</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Tailwind CSS in Spanish – Full Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-tailwind-css-in-spanish-full-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-tailwind-css-in-spanish-full-course/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T15:30:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tailwind is a CSS framework with pre-defined classes that you can combine to build modern and responsive websites. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org Spanish YouTube channel [https://www.youtube.com/freecodecampespanol] that will teach you Tailwind CSS. You will go from the basics to actually building your own real-world projects. By]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create an Interactive Button Component in Figma]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-an-interactive-button-component-in-figma/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-an-interactive-button-component-in-figma/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T18:44:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Designers are always searching for tools that help ease their workflow and create innovative solutions for their users. This ranges from components, style guides, and design systems, to plugins and extensions. In this article, we're going to look at components as features which can help boost your efficiency as a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijelekhai Faith Olohijere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The End Of My Gatsby Journey]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/end-of-gatsby-journey/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/end-of-gatsby-journey/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[“Gatsby headaches”](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/gatsby-headaches-i18n-part-1/) are over. Juan Diego Rodríguez reflects on his decision to stop using Gatsby as his go-to framework. Through a detailed examination of its strengths and weaknesses, he provides valuable insights and alternative options for developers navigating their tooling choices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern CSS Tooltips And Speech Bubbles (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/modern-css-tooltips-speech-bubbles-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/modern-css-tooltips-speech-bubbles-part1/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tooltips are a very common pattern used in CSS for years. There are a lot of ways to approach tooltips in CSS, though some evoke headaches with all the magic numbers they require. In this article, Temani Afif presents modern techniques to create tooltips with the smallest amount of markup and the greatest amount of flexibility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Waiting For Spring (March 2024 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-march-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-march-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new batch of desktop wallpapers is for you. Designed by artists and designers from across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar for March 2024. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reporting Core Web Vitals With The Performance API]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/reporting-core-web-vitals-performance-api/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/reporting-core-web-vitals-performance-api/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Performance API is a set of standards for measuring and evaluating performance metrics with JavaScript. This article demonstrates how to use the Performance API to generate performance metrics directly in the DOM to create your own reporting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Web Designer’s Accessibility Advocacy Toolkit]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/web-designer-accessibility-advocacy-toolkit/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/web-designer-accessibility-advocacy-toolkit/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital designer Yichan Wang has put together this collection of strategies and selling points to help you encourage and advocate for accessibility in your place of work, including useful scripts you can use as starting points.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yichan Wang)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vanilla JavaScript, Libraries, And The Quest For Stateful DOM Rendering]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/vanilla-javascript-libraries-quest-stateful-dom-rendering/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/vanilla-javascript-libraries-quest-stateful-dom-rendering/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s well-established that the web faces wide-ranging usability and performance issues, from user-hostile UI patterns and twisted search results to sluggish performance and battery-draining bloat. In this article, Frederik examines one small-but-significant aspect where developers take the reins: Painting pixels on the screen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederik Dohr)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Practical Guide To Designing For Colorblind People]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/designing-for-colorblindness/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/designing-for-colorblindness/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Color accessibility is more than just ticking boxes. Even with good contrast, some color palettes can make interfaces challenging for users. Here are some practical guidelines to ensure more inclusive design for colorblind people. An upcoming part of Smart Interface Design Patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile Accessibility Barriers For Assistive Technology Users]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/mobile-accessibility-barriers-assistive-technology-users/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/mobile-accessibility-barriers-assistive-technology-users/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility goes beyond making products user-friendly. It can significantly impact the quality of life for people with disabilities. Kate Kalcevich shares lessons she learned from assistive technology users — challenges and barriers they encounter on mobile devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kate Kalcevich)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Accessibility Standards Can Empower Better Chart Visual Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/accessibility-standards-empower-better-chart-visual-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/accessibility-standards-empower-better-chart-visual-design/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility for data visualization extends well beyond web standards, at least if you’re trying to create an experience that’s actually useful. This article focuses on techniques for creating useful and accessible visualizations that extend well beyond compliance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kent Eisenhuth)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Practical Guide To Designing For Children]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/practical-guide-design-children/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/practical-guide-design-children/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to design for children aged 3–12, with insights into user behavior, considerations for parents, and practical UX guidelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Draw Radar Charts In Web]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/draw-radar-charts-web/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/draw-radar-charts-web/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A radar chart — also commonly called a spider chart — is yet another way to visualize data and make connections. Radar charts are inherently geometric, making them both a perfect fit and fun to make with CSS, thanks to the `polygon()` function. Read along as Preethi Sam demonstrates the process and sprinkles it with a pinch of JavaScript to make a handy, reusable component.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Preethi Sam)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frequently Heard In My Beginning Front-End Web Development Class]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/frequently-heard-beginning-front-end-web-development-class/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/frequently-heard-beginning-front-end-web-development-class/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What could we learn from entry-level students in front-end web development? As seasoned professionals, you might think you’ve seen it all, but the truth is that the newcomers are asking the most intriguing questions and making connections that those of us who have spent years on the front end may have never considered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>