<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-11-07T00:13:00.240Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-11-07T00:13:00.240Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TypeError: module object is not callable [Python Error Solved]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typeerror-module-object-is-not-callable-python-error-solved/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typeerror-module-object-is-not-callable-python-error-solved/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T22:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll talk about the "TypeError: 'module' object is not callable" error in Python.  We'll start by defining some of the keywords found in the error message — module  and callable.  You'll then see some examples that raise the error, and how to fix it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tailwind CSS Landing Page Themes for Busy Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tailwind-css-landing-pages-and-themes-for-busy-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tailwind-css-landing-pages-and-themes-for-busy-developers/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T21:44:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers across all levels of experience spend hours hunched over their computers, trying to translate the UI designer's ideas into a functional website or application. Considering that you're reading this, chances are that this is a pretty relatable scenario for you. And you know all too well just how tedious]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edan Ben-Atar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the SQL CASE Statement – with Example Challenge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-case-statement/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-case-statement/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T14:28:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing SQL with multiple conditions can be an arduous task, especially if you need to make numerous checks.  For example, an if () else if () else {} check case expression handles all SQL conditionals. If the first condition is satisfied, the query stops executing with a return value.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sule-Balogun Olanrewaju Ganiu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Couple Changes Coming in Chrome 108]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374894</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-couple-changes-coming-in-chrome-108/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T13:13:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“A change to overflow on replaced elements in CSS”:
From Chrome 108, the following replaced elements respect the overflow property: img, video and canvas. In earlier versions of Chrome, this property was ignored on these elements.
This 
…
A Couple Changes Coming in Chrome 108 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practical Steps To Build Transparency In Your Remote Business]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/practical-steps-build-transparency-remote-business/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/practical-steps-build-transparency-remote-business/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transparency is part of the fabric of many remote businesses. It doesn’t, however, come naturally to everyone, especially if you’ve only recently become remote. In this article, Siobhan takes you through some of the practical ways that you can build transparency within your organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Siobhan McKeown)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[String to Int in Java – How to Convert a String to an Integer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-convert-a-string-to-an-integer-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-convert-a-string-to-an-integer-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T22:02:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When working with a programming language, you may want to convert strings to integers. An example would be performing a mathematical operation using the value of a string variable.  In this article, you'll learn how to convert a string to an integer in Java using two methods of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python lower() – How to Lowercase a Python String with the tolower Function Equivalent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-lowercase-python-string/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-lowercase-python-string/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T16:16:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A string is a datatype that consists of characters wrapped in quotation marks. These characters can be letters, symbols, or numbers.  In Python, there are different ways of working with strings. These methods are built-in functions that change the results of the string.  For instance, if I want]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tantoluwa Heritage Alabi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Format a Number as Currency in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-format-number-as-currency-in-javascript-one-line-of-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-format-number-as-currency-in-javascript-one-line-of-code/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T15:29:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working with data from an API or an external resource, you'll get these data in some general format. For example, if you are building a store, you might have data like price. This price data might be in the form of a general number such as 14340 or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript for React Developers – Why TypeScript is Useful and How it Works]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typescript-for-react-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typescript-for-react-developers/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T15:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've been using React for a while, you may have noticed times when the freedom and wild nature of JavaScript works against you (and not because of JS 😄). This can be especially true if you're working in a team. You may not know it, but you need TypeScript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Asta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Difference Between Web Sockets, Web Workers, and Service Workers]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374731</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-difference-between-web-sockets-web-workers-and-service-workers/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T12:56:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web Sockets, Web Workers, Service Workers… these are terms you may have read or overheard. Maybe not all of them, but likely at least one of them. And even if you have a good handle on front-end development, there’s a …
The Difference Between Web Sockets, Web Workers, and Service Workers originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aisha Bukar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Smashing Front-End & UX Workshops]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/new-frontend-coding-ux-online-workshops/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/new-frontend-coding-ux-online-workshops/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s the state of HTML Email, Vue.js and Next.js? Would you like to level up with modern CSS? What are new, smart interface design patterns we could use? Let’s figure it all out together with our [brand new online workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) alongside our free community meetups.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quick Sort – Algorithm Time Complexity with C++ and Java Code Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/quick-sort-algorithm-time-complexity-with-cpp-and-java-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/quick-sort-algorithm-time-complexity-with-cpp-and-java-code/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T00:43:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you'll learn about one of the most commonly used programming algorithms – the quick sort algorithm.  You'll get to know how the algorithm works with the help of visual guides. You'll also see some code examples that will help you implement the algorithm in C++ and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Minify – Minifying JS with a Minifier or jsmin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-minify-minifying-js-with-a-minifier-or-jsmin/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-minify-minifying-js-with-a-minifier-or-jsmin/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T23:50:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You might be wondering – what is minification and how does it improve your JavaScript applications? What tools can you use to minify your JS? I'll answer these questions in this article. What is Minification? Minification is the process of "minimizing" code by removing the irrelevant parts of the code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TypeError: builtin_function_or_method object is not subscriptable Python Error [SOLVED]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typeerror-builtin-function-or-method-object-is-not-subscriptable-python-error-solved/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typeerror-builtin-function-or-method-object-is-not-subscriptable-python-error-solved/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T23:43:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the name suggests, the error TypeError: builtin_function_or_method object is not subscriptable is a “typeerror” that occurs when you try to call a built-in function the wrong way. When a "typeerror" occurs, the program is telling you that you’re mixing up types. That means, for example, you might be concatenating]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing The Perfect Mobile Navigation UX]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/navigation-design-mobile-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/navigation-design-mobile-ux/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When designing navigation on mobile, we don’t have to rely on slide-in-menus or nested accordions. We can also use the curtain design pattern, and show multiple levels of navigation at once.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Links About CSS Gradients]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374697</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/some-links-about-css-gradients/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T12:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every once in a while, the blogging zeitgiest seems to coalesce around a certain topic and it’s like the saved articles in my bookmarks folder are having a conversation. The conversation sitting in there now is all about CSS Gradients …
Some Links About CSS Gradients originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rendering External API Data in WordPress Blocks on the Back End]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374381</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/rendering-external-api-data-in-wordpress-blocks-on-the-back-end/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T12:57:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a continuation of my last article about “Rendering External API Data in WordPress Blocks on the Front End”. In that last one, we learned how to take an external API and integrate it with a block that …
Rendering External API Data in WordPress Blocks on the Back End originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manoj Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Putting The Graph In GraphQL With The Neo4j GraphQL Library]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/graph-neo4j-graphql-library/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/graph-neo4j-graphql-library/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If building a GraphQL API backed by a native graph database sounds interesting or at all helpful for the problems you’re trying to solve as a developer, perhaps you’d like to give the open-source [Neo4j GraphQL Library](https://srv.buysellads.com/ads/long/x/TCZPLYDDTTTTTTFR6JINCTTTTTTGVUIVKKTTTTTTCT2NTYYTTTTTTI4BVH7U4JBCKQ466IDGV2IUWESGCV7WALL5QYYE) a try. Let’s take a closer look at the reasons why!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (William Lyon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New CSS Media Query Range Syntax]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374670</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-new-css-media-query-range-syntax/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T13:05:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Media Queries Level 4 specification has introduced a new syntax for targeting a range of viewport widths using common mathematical comparison operators, like , and =, that make more sense syntactically while writing less code for responsive web design.
The New CSS Media Query Range Syntax originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi Selvam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On The Edge Of November (2022 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November is just around the corner, and with it, a new collection of desktop wallpapers to celebrate the beginning of the month. Designed by creatives from all across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar. Let’s make November colorful!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create Advanced Animations With CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/advanced-animations-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/advanced-animations-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-29T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Yosra Emad explains how to create a rollercoaster path that a ball follows using cubic beziers and CSS transitions. You’ll also learn how the cubic-bezier function in CSS works in detail and how to stack multiple simple animations to create one complex one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yosra Emad)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Motion Controls In The Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/motion-controls-browser/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/motion-controls-browser/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've ever wanted to build a web app that you can control with hand gestures as if by magic, this article is for you. With a couple of APIs and some JavaScript, you can build apps that behave like sorcery.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yaphi Berhanu)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fancy Image Decorations: Outlines and Complex Animations]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374302</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/fancy-image-decorations-outlines-and-complex-animations/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T12:45:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve spent the last two articles in this three-part series playing with gradients to make really neat image decorations using nothing but the <img> element. In this third and final piece, we are going to explore more techniques using the …
Fancy Image Decorations: Outlines and Complex Animations originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Holographic Trading Card Effect]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374609</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/holographic-trading-card-effect/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T17:05:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Simon Goellner (@simeydotme)’s collection of Holographic Trading Cards have captured our attention.
Under the hood there is a suite of filter(), background-blend-mode(), mix-blend-mode(), and clip-path() combinations that have been painstakingly tweaked to reach the desired effect. I …
Holographic Trading Card Effect originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bradley Kouchi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Typographic Hierarchies]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/typographic-hierarchies/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/typographic-hierarchies/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Alma Hoffmann discusses six basic variables to establish a typographic hierarchy, explains how to look at each differently, and in turn, designs pieces by intentionally modifying each variable to create a typographic hierarchy effectively.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alma Hoffmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Animated, Clickable Cards With the :has() Relational Pseudo Class]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374690</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-animated-clickable-cards-with-the-has-relational-pseudo-class/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T14:15:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS :has() pseudo class is rolling out in many browsers with Chrome and Safari already fully supporting it. It’s often referred to it as “the parent selector” — as in, we can select style a parent element from a …
Creating Animated, Clickable Cards With the :has() Relational Pseudo Class originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brecht De Ruyte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State Of CSS Survey: Influence The Future Of CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/state-css-survey-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/state-css-survey-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The annual survey for anyone who writes CSS, [State of CSS](https://stateofcss.com/en-us/?source=smashing_magazine_css_survey), is nearing the end of its response period for 2022. The survey is available in many different languages and all questions are optional.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lea Verou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is There Too Much CSS Now?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374364</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/is-there-too-much-css-now/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T12:59:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As front-end developers, we’ve wished for a lot of things over the years — ways to center things in CSS, encapsulate styles, set an element’s aspect ratio, get finer-grained control over our colors, select an element based on its children’s …
Is There Too Much CSS Now? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sacha Greif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fancy Image Decorations: Masks and Advanced Hover Effects]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374194</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/fancy-image-decorations-masks-and-advanced-hover-effects/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T12:46:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Part 2 of this three-part series! We are still decorating images without any extra elements and pseudo-elements. I hope you already took the time to digest Part 1 because we will continue working with a lot of gradients …
Fancy Image Decorations: Masks and Advanced Hover Effects originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Futuristic CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/futuristic-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/futuristic-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Sacha Greif tries to anticipate future CSS trends and takes a look at some far-fetched and futuristic CSS features that might one day make their way to the browser.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sacha Greif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instant Articles, Proprietary Syndication, and a Web Built on User Fidelity Preferences]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374470</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/instant-articles-proprietary-syndication-user-fidelity-preferences/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T19:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love it when there’s a sense of synergy in the blogosphere. First, I caught Nick Heer’s coverage of Meta ending support for Instant Articles, its proprietary format for stripped-down performant news articles. He also compares it to the similar …
Instant Articles, Proprietary Syndication, and a Web Built on User Fidelity Preferences originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New In DevTools: Halloween Edition 🎃]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/devtools-updates-halloween-edition/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/devtools-updates-halloween-edition/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Patrick Brosset gives an update on the most impactful new features that are now available in DevTools, across Firefox, Chrome, Safari, and Edge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Patrick Brosset)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsive Animations for Every Screen Size and Device]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374345</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/responsive-animations-for-every-screen-size-and-device/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T12:42:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before I career jumped into development, I did a bunch of motion graphics work in After Effects. But even with that background, I still found animating on the web pretty baffling.
Video graphics are designed within a specific ratio and …
Responsive Animations for Every Screen Size and Device originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cassie Evans</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make a Folder “Slit” Effect With CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374376</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-make-a-folder-slit-effect-with-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T12:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you put something — say a regular sheet of paper — in a manilla folder, a part of that thing might peek out of the folder a little bit. The same sort of thing with a wallet and credit …
How to Make a Folder “Slit” Effect With CSS originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Privacy: A New Smashing Book Is Here]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/understanding-privacy-book-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/understanding-privacy-book-release/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Understanding Privacy, our brand new Smashing Book to make sense of privacy, and learn how to create inclusive, safe and privacy-aware digital experiences. eBook now available, print shipping in November.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manuel Matuzovic: max() Trickery]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374466</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/manuel-matuzovic-max-trickery/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T13:54:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By way of a post by Manuel Matuzović which is by way of a demo by Temani Afif.
.wrapper {
  margin-inline: max(0px, ((100% - 64rem) / 2)); 
}
You’d be doing yourself a favor to read Manuel’s breakdown of …
Manuel Matuzovic: max() Trickery originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pure CSS Bezier Curve Motion Paths]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373600</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/pure-css-bezier-curve-motion-paths/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T15:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Besides being elegant, Bezier curves have nice mathematical properties due to their definition and construction. No wonder they are widely used in so many areas! Now, how about using Bezier curves as motion paths with CSS?
Pure CSS Bezier Curve Motion Paths originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lu Wang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Full-Site Editing: A Deep Dive Into The New Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/wordpress-full-site-editing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/wordpress-full-site-editing/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Nick Schäferhoff will take a deep dive into WordPress Full-Site Editing, examine the tools it provides for theme development, and provide a tutorial on how to use it to make changes to your site.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nick Schäferhoff)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Effective Communication For Everyday Meetings]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/effective-communication-everyday-meetings/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/effective-communication-everyday-meetings/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article about conducting productive meetings, Andrii Zhdan will give you a step-by-step guide on preparing a solid meeting structure that will let you follow the original plan and reach the meeting goals, and he will also share a few tips based on his design experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andrii Zhdan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sustainable Web Development Strategies Within An Organization]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/sustainable-web-development-strategies-organization/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/sustainable-web-development-strategies-organization/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Climate change and sustainability are increasing concerns for digital organizations, as well as individuals working in tech. In this article, we’ll explore some of the ways we can raise awareness and effect change within an organization to create a more positive environmental impact.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delightful UI Animations With Shared Element Transitions API (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/ui-animations-shared-element-transitions-api-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/ui-animations-shared-element-transitions-api-part2/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Adrian Bece will show how to create same-document page transitions for Single Page Apps using Shared Element Transitions API and check out its future implementation and potential for creating cross-document transitions in Multi-Page Apps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>