<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-11-01T00:10:23.394Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-11-01T00:10:23.394Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Answering Common Questions About Interpreting Page Speed Reports]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/answering-questions-interpreting-page-speed-reports/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/answering-questions-interpreting-page-speed-reports/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take a closer look at how various performance tools audit and report on performance metrics, such as core web vitals. Geoff Graham answers a set of common questions that pop up during performance audits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tales Of November (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T09:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November is just around the corner, and with it, a new collection of desktop wallpapers to celebrate the beginning of the month. Designed by creatives from all across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar. Let’s make this November colorful!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Scrape Amazon Product Reviews Behind a Login]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-scrape-amazon-product-reviews-behind-a-login/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-scrape-amazon-product-reviews-behind-a-login/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T16:46:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon is the most popular e-commerce website for web scrapers, with billions of product pages being scraped every month.  It is also home to a vast database of product reviews, which can be very useful for market research and competitor monitoring.  You can extract relevant data from the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Satyam Tripathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin and Android Development – Build a Chat App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/kotlin-and-android-development-build-a-chat-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/kotlin-and-android-development-build-a-chat-app/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T16:24:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready to dive into the world of Android development using Kotlin? We just posted a 10-hour Android course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Alexandru Cristian created this course. I will help you understand how to develop with Kotlin and Android. This course will take you on a journey]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Automate Data Exports and Email Reports with Python – a Step-by-Step Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automate-data-exports-email-reports-with-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automate-data-exports-email-reports-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T16:08:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's data-driven world, automation is key to streamlining tasks and saving time. In this beginner-friendly tutorial, I'll walk you through the process of automating data exports from a PostgreSQL database and sending them as an email attachment using Python.  This step-by-step guide will help you grasp the fundamentals]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Frameworks vs Custom CSS – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-frameworks-vs-custom-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-frameworks-vs-custom-css/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T14:51:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to styling web pages, CSS or Cascading Style Sheets is the go-to tool for web developers. CSS is what gives your website that visually appealing look and feel, from colors and fonts to layout and positioning.  But there are two distinct approaches to applying CSS: using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passkeys: A No-Frills Explainer On The Future Of Password-Less Authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/passkeys-explainer-future-password-less-authentication/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/passkeys-explainer-future-password-less-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Passkeys are beginning to make their way into popular apps, from password managers to multi-factor authenticators, but what exactly are they? As this new technology promises to make passwords a thing of the past, Neal Fennimore explains the concepts behind passkeys, demonstrates how they work, and speculates what we might expect from them in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Neal Fennimore)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Overcoming 3 Layoffs with Senior Dev Kevin Miller]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-kevin-miller-coder-conversations/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-kevin-miller-coder-conversations/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T17:22:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's podcast, I interview Kevin Miller. He's a senior developer and host of the Coder Conversations YouTube channel. Kevin studied accounting in Texas and worked overnight for 7 years at hotels, making only $11 an hour. But his knowledge of spreadsheets lead to him learning more about]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What I Wish I Knew About Working In Development Right Out Of School]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/beginner-web-development-working-career/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/beginner-web-development-working-career/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Victoria Johnson began a career in front-end development upon graduating from college. Now, roughly one year later, she reflects back on the decisions she made to crack into the field and find her first full-time job. This is her story, and she’s sharing it to provide those who are just starting out with another beginner’s perspective.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Victoria Johnson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Good Documentation with Docsify]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-good-documentation-with-docsify/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-good-documentation-with-docsify/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T19:21:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Documentation is critical to a successful product. Without documentation, it's more difficult for people to use your product, and it's just as important if you're running an open-source project, too. Creating a documentation site can be challenging, especially if you're not familiar with front-end development.  I have been a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Created a SQL-like Language to Run Queries on Local Git Repositories]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/gql-design-and-implementation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/gql-design-and-implementation/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone! I'm a Software engineer who's interested in low-level programming, compilers, and tool development.  Three months ago I decided to learn the Rust programming language and build a Git client that focuses on simplicity and productivity. ‌I started to think about how I could build the Git client]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amr Hesham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Algorithmic Trading Using Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-algorithmic-trading-using-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-algorithmic-trading-using-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T12:38:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the realm of financial markets, algorithmic trading has revolutionized the way trades are executed, providing a systematic approach to analyzing data and making investment decisions. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to implement algorithmic trading with Python using a variety]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Actionable And Reliable Usability Questionnaire With Only 7 Items: <span style="font-variant: small-caps">Inuit</span>]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/actionable-reliable-usability-questionnaire-inuit/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/actionable-reliable-usability-questionnaire-inuit/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inuit (short for “**In**terface **U**sability **I**nstrumen**t**”) is a new questionnaire you can use to assess the usability of your user interface. It has been designed to be more diagnostic than existing usability instruments like, e.g., SUS and for use with machine learning, all the while asking fewer questions than other questionnaires. This article explores how and why Inuit has been developed and why we can be sure that it actually measures usability, and reliably so.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Maximilian Speicher &amp; Johanna Jagow)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Structure JSON Responses in ChatGPT with Function Calling]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-json-back-from-chatgpt-with-function-calling/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-json-back-from-chatgpt-with-function-calling/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T18:09:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT's Problem With JSON Open up the ChatGPT UI [https://chat.openai.com/] and ask it for some JSON. Chances are you will get a response like you can see in the cover photo above: a JSON object presented to you in markdown format, with some text to either side explaining what the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Charlesworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn MySQL – Beginner's Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-mysql-beginners-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-mysql-beginners-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T12:43:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Databases have become an integral part of storing and managing data efficiently. MySQL, a widely used open-source relational database management system, empowers users to handle data in a structured manner, facilitating easier retrieval and manipulation of information. Understanding MySQL is vital for developers, data analysts, and anyone aspiring to delve]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fight For The Main Thread]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/speedcurve-fight-main-thread/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/speedcurve-fight-main-thread/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having access to a free reporting tool like Lighthouse in DevTools is a great start for diagnosing performance issues by identifying bottlenecks on the main thread. Even better are paid tools like [SpeedCurve](https://www.speedcurve.com/?utm_source=smashingmag&utm_medium=magazine&utm_campaign=sm7_2023&utm_id=sm7_2023&utm_term=sm7_2023) to dig deeper into the data for more targeted insights and to produce visual reports to help make a case for performance improvements for your team and other stakeholders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Removing Object Properties Tells Us About JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/removing-object-properties-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/removing-object-properties-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Removing properties from an object in JavaScript might not be the most exciting job, but there are many ways to achieve it, each revealing a fundamental aspect of how JavaScript works. Juan Diego Rodríguez explores each technique in this article.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Roundup Of WCAG 2.2 Explainers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/roundup-wcag-explainers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/roundup-wcag-explainers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WCAG 2.2 officially became a “W3C Recommended” web standard on October 5, 2023, and with it, new success criteria and changes to existing guidelines for accessible user experiences. What are the changes, and how can you conform to them? This roundup provides links to WCAG 2.2 explainers that have been published or updated since the release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Choose Typefaces For Fintech Products: Best Practices Guide (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/choose-typefaces-fintech-products-best-practices-guide-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/choose-typefaces-fintech-products-best-practices-guide-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Finding the right typeface is tricky as a whole. Dividing the process into steps and having the right information at hand will make this journey a design adventure full of surprises. To avoid sinking into unnecessary details, use this guide as a map for your path. Review various font paraments and learn how to apply them to your designs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Daria Karpenko)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Animate Along A Path In CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/animate-along-path-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/animate-along-path-css/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS loaders and progress indicators are some of the most widely used examples in tutorials and documentation. In this article, Preethi demonstrates an approach using animated custom properties, a conic gradient, CSS `offset`, and emoji to create the illusion of a scooter racing along a donut track.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Preethi Sam)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 66 With Ethan Marcotte: What Is A Tech Union?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/smashing-podcast-episode-66/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/smashing-podcast-episode-66/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s Smashing Podcast episode, we’re talking about Tech Unions. What part can unions play in a modern tech workplace? Drew McLellan talks to Ethan Marcotte to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Headaches: Working With Media (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/gatsby-headaches-working-media-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/gatsby-headaches-working-media-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the final part of this two-part series on solving headaches when working with media files in Gatsby projects, Juan Rodriguez demonstrates strategies and techniques for handling various types of documents, including Markdown files, PDFs, and 3D models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Choose Typefaces For Fintech Products: Our Best Practices Guide (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/choose-typefaces-fintech-products-guide-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/choose-typefaces-fintech-products-guide-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-13T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fintech products are systems that are overloaded by many types of data like numerals, texts, spreadsheets, and so on. Working with these products requires the designer to pay a high level of attention and responsibility, as he becomes a provider between user and data. Daria shares her approach to digital product typography and reviews the key points to consider when choosing typefaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Daria Karpenko)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything I Know About UX Research I First Learned From Lt. Columbo]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/ux-research-learn-from-lt-columbo/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/ux-research-learn-from-lt-columbo/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working in the area of UX sometimes feels like a crime drama. Can’t believe it? Then look at these fun parallels between modern UX practices and a classical TV detective.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Slava Shestopalov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A High-Level Overview Of Large Language Model Concepts, Use Cases, And Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/overview-large-language-model-concepts-use-cases-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/overview-large-language-model-concepts-use-cases-tools/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discuss the concept of large language models (LLMs) and how they are implemented with a set of data to develop an application. Joas compares a collection of no-code and low-code apps designed to help you get a feel for not only how the concept works but also to get a sense of what types of models are available to train AI on different skill sets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joas Pambou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Headaches: Working With Media (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/gatsby-headaches-working-media-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/gatsby-headaches-working-media-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how to incorporate a variety of media formats, such as images, videos, GIFs, SVGs, and so on, in a Gatsby website. Juan Rodriguez shares what he’s learned about optimizing files for improved performance after working with different plugins and techniques.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Re-Creating The Pop-Out Hover Effect With Modern CSS (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/re-creating-pop-out-hover-effect-modern-css-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/re-creating-pop-out-hover-effect-modern-css-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Re-create a fancy hover effect where an avatar pops out of a starburst pattern for the frame on hover. The idea is to apply the concepts in a new context and gain another view of how trigonometric functions can influence the way we mask elements in CSS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Problem With WordPress Is Positioning, Not Plugins]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/problem-wordpress-positioning-not-plugins/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/problem-wordpress-positioning-not-plugins/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Geoff explores the often-overlooked divide between WordPress.org and WordPress.com, shedding light on the blurred lines between open-source ideals and commercial interests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WaterBear: Building A Free Platform For Impactful Documentaries (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/waterbear-building-free-platform-documentaries-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/waterbear-building-free-platform-documentaries-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this second article of a two-part series, Adrian shares insights about building WaterBear — his first project as a lead developer — discussing the challenges his team encountered while building it and various accessibility and performance improvements they’ve made. You’ll get a peek at the inner workings of a team striving to find its groove to systematize the work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>