<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-07-08T00:11:27.271Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-07-08T00:11:27.271Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Tiered List Maker with Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-tier-list-maker/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-tier-list-maker/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T20:48:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Pythonistas! Do you want to level up your Python and API skills while also building something really useful? Well, then you're in the right place. This hands-on tutorial showcases how to leverage Python's capabilities to code an interactive tiered list builder right within your terminal.  We'll use some]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atharva Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python List to String – How to Convert Lists in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-list-to-string-how-to-convert-lists-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-list-to-string-how-to-convert-lists-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T18:10:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you need to save a list as a text file, display it in a user-friendly format, or pass it as a parameter to a function, knowing how to convert a list to a string is essential. In this tutorial, we will explore various methods to convert Python lists to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Avoid the N+1 Query Problem in GraphQL and REST APIs [with Benchmarks]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/n-plus-one-query-problem/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/n-plus-one-query-problem/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T17:59:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The N+1 query problem is a performance issue you might face while building APIs, regardless of whether they're GraphQL or REST APIs. In fact, this problem occurs when your application needs to return a set of data that includes related nested data – for example, a post that includes comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mohamed Mayallo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Come Up With Good Coding Project Ideas]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-come-up-with-coding-project-ideas/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-come-up-with-coding-project-ideas/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T17:57:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a developer looking to improve your coding skills, building projects is a great way to do that. But coming up with project ideas that actually make you eager to start can be tough. That's why I wrote this article: to help you learn how to come up with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erin Borders</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shines, Perspective, And Rotations: Fancy CSS 3D Effects For Images]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/shines-perspective-rotations-css-3d-effects-images/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/shines-perspective-rotations-css-3d-effects-images/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS has all kinds of tricks that are capable of turning images into neat, interactive elements. This article is a collection of fancy 3D effects for images that demonstrate those CSS powers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Import from File – Importing Local Files in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-import-from-file-importing-local-files-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-import-from-file-importing-local-files-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T22:40:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many reasons you might want to import files in Python. Perhaps you're doing data analysis, custom file processing, file manipulation, automation and so on.  Fortunately, Python provides a number of ways and methods to help you accomplish this task.  In this article, we will examine some]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use a Foreign Key to Create Many-to-One Relationships in Django]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-one-to-many-relationship-in-django/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-one-to-many-relationship-in-django/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T20:33:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Django, there are three main types of relationships: one-to-one, many-to-one, and many-to-many. In this article, I will explain the many-to-one relationship in Django. If you are a beginner with some knowledge about Django project setup or even have some decent experience in Django, you can follow along with this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sampurna Chapagain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Action and Func Delegates in C# – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/action-and-func-delegates-in-c-sharp/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/action-and-func-delegates-in-c-sharp/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T19:46:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In C#, types called delegates represent references to methods with specific signatures.  Developers use delegates to implement callback methods, handle events, and perform tasks where executing a method at a later time is necessary.  C# offers various delegates, and two commonly used ones are Action and Func, both]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Umoh Tobby</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use CSS Selectors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-css-selectors/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-css-selectors/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T19:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can apply CSS to elements like paragraphs and ordered lists, which you can learn more about by reading this article [/news/css-style-sheets-basics/]. But you're not just restricted to those two approaches.  As we'll see in this tutorial, you can also control content behavior using custom or ID styles, pseudo]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[String to Array in Java – How to Convert Strings to Arrays]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/string-to-array-in-java-how-to-convert-a-string-to-an-array-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/string-to-array-in-java-how-to-convert-a-string-to-an-array-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T19:37:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being able to convert a string into an array can be quite helpful when you're developing text-processing applications or working with data.  A string in Java is a group of characters, whereas an array is a collection of the same type of element. You may deconstruct a string into]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn JavaScript for Beginners – JS Basics Handbook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-javascript-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-javascript-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T19:01:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The goal of this handbook is to quickly introduce you to the basics of JavaScript so you can start programming applications. Instead of covering all the theories and concepts of JavaScript, I'll be teaching you only the most important building blocks of the language. We'll cover things like variables, data]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The UX Of Flight Searches: How We Challenged Industry Standards]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/reimagining-flight-search-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/reimagining-flight-search-ux/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As of today, the world’s 50 top airlines have all agreed on the same flight search pattern. Yet the path to booking the right flight remains frustrating and confusing. Is there really only one solution? Explore the thought experiment which turned the seemingly untouchable pattern on its head and offered new food for thought.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Robert Goesch)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sustainable Design Toolkits And Resources]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/sustainable-design-toolkits-and-resources/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/sustainable-design-toolkits-and-resources/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can we create products and experiences that don’t cause harm to the planet and to the people who use them? What do we need to consider to make more sustainable design decisions and reduce the carbon footprint of our websites? In this post, we compiled valuable resources that will get you familiar with the principles of sustainable design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke &amp; Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Off To New Adventures (July 2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-july-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-july-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s welcome the new month with some fresh desktop wallpapers. Designed by artists and designers from around the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar for July 2023. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s The Perfect Design Process?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/perfect-design-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/perfect-design-process/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The design process is messy. You might be following a structured approach, but too often, it takes a life of its own. And before you know it, you are designing in chaos, with last-minute changes and missed deadlines. So, what’s the “perfect” design process?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful DevTools Tips and Tricks]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/popular-devtools-tips/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/popular-devtools-tips/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s discover the most popular DevTools tips that can boost your productivity and revolutionize your debugging workflow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Patrick Brosset)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind The Curtains Of Wikipedia Redesign]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/behind-curtains-wikipedia-redesign/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/behind-curtains-wikipedia-redesign/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Wikipedia team shipped a redesign of the ubiquitous and one of the [most visited websites](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_most_visited_websites) on the web. Alex Hollender and Jon Robson led the work and generously discussed the effort with us in a thorough, wide-ranging interview that covers the design, development, and processes that went into the project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Penpot’s Flex Layout: Building CSS Layouts In A Design Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/penpot-flex-layout-building-css-layouts-design-tool/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/penpot-flex-layout-building-css-layouts-design-tool/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s article, let’s explore how we can use Flex Layout and see how it empowers designers with greater control over their work while saving everyone’s time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using AI To Detect Sentiment In Audio Files]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/ai-detect-sentiment-audio-files/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/ai-detect-sentiment-audio-files/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dive into an article where you will build an app that evaluates audio files for positive and negative sentiments. The idea is that you will create an interface for uploading an audio file, then transcribe the contents into text before analyzing the text and assigning it a positive or negative score for how the tone is perceived.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joas Pambou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Editing Comes To The Headless CMS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/visual-editing-headless-cms/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/visual-editing-headless-cms/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visual editing is beginning to make its way into headless architecture and the early results look promising. We’ll look at a few headless CMSs that currently support visual editing in this article.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Scott Gallant)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Headaches And How To Cure Them: i18n (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/gatsby-headaches-i18n-part-2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/gatsby-headaches-i18n-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part 2 of the series concentrates on implementing internationalization (i18n) on a Gatsby website, an essential feature on any multilingual website that can be quite a bit of trouble if incorrectly implemented, creating more problems than it solves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Was SmashingConf In San Franciso Like?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/smashingconf-sanfrancisco2023-recap/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/smashingconf-sanfrancisco2023-recap/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One way of getting a more behind-the-scenes experience of any Smashing event is to apply as a volunteer, and Ren did just that! The SmashingConf team organized a conference in good ol’ San Francisco this year, and here’s pretty much how it went down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ren Chen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Codux: The React Visual Editor That Improves Developer Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/codux-react-visual-editor-improves-developer-experience/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/codux-react-visual-editor-improves-developer-experience/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[Codux](https://codux.hopp.to/smashing) is a new visual IDE brought to you by the fine folks over at[ Wix](https://www.wix.com/). It’s got a lot of low-code features that level the playing field for app development but is really designed for React developers. How so, you ask? That’s what we’re going to explore in this article.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build Server-Side Rendered (SSR) Svelte Apps With SvelteKit]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/build-server-side-rendered-svelte-apps-sveltekit/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/build-server-side-rendered-svelte-apps-sveltekit/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SvelteKit is a framework for building apps using Svelte. In this article, Sriram shows you how to build a server-side rendered (SSR) SvelteKit application and deploy it to Netlify by following this step-by-step guide.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sriram Thiagarajan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 62 With Slava Shestopalov: What Is Design Management?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/smashing-podcast-episode-62/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/smashing-podcast-episode-62/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of The Smashing Podcast, we ask what is a design manager? What does it take and how does it relate to the role of Designer? Vitaly talks to Slava Shestopalov to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Headaches And How To Cure Them: i18n (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/gatsby-headaches-i18n-part-1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/gatsby-headaches-i18n-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this first part of a two-part hands-on guide, Juan Rodriguez explains how to use several i18n plugins for Gatsby and reviews some others.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design Under Constraints: Challenges, Opportunities, And Practical Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/design-constraints-challenges-opportunities-practical-strategies/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/design-constraints-challenges-opportunities-practical-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unleash the power of creative limitation! Learn how constraints aren’t barriers but instead stepping stones to innovative design. Find out how to challenge unproductive restrictions and leverage the rest to your advantage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>