<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-01-01T00:12:18.716Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-01-01T00:12:18.716Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opening The Doors To 2023 (January Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2023/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-31T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s start into the new year with a little inspiration boost: wallpapers created with love by the community for the community. Happy 2023!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fluid Typography: Predicting A Problem With Your User’s Zoom-In]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/fluid-typography-predict-problem-users-zoom-in/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/fluid-typography-predict-problem-users-zoom-in/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-30T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Ruslan Yevych will show you an easy way how to predict the appearance of a problem known as WCAG Failure Under 1.4.4 Resize Text (AA) while zooming the page. You will have a clear understanding of the possible risks of using responsive typography at the stage of development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ruslan Yevych)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thank You (2022 Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375486</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/thank-you-2022-edition/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-28T15:46:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You know, this is the time of year where Chris normally publishes a big ol’ reflection of the past year. The first one was published in 2007, the same year CSS-Tricks began, and it continued all the way through 2021…
Thank You (2022 Edition) originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Command-Line Data Manipulation]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/guide-command-line-data-manipulation-cli-miller/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/guide-command-line-data-manipulation-cli-miller/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-27T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No more random scripts in Python and JavaScript to transform CSV or JSON data. In this article, Alvin Bryan shows you how to use Miller, a small and powerful CLI tool, to do all your data processing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alvin Bryan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying CSS Logical Properties On Web Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/deploying-css-logical-properties-on-web-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/deploying-css-logical-properties-on-web-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have already heard of CSS logical properties or RTL adaptations but are still deciding whether to deploy them widely. To help raise your awareness of their possibilities, Nicolas Hoffmann shares his experience of how he and his team at Proton carried out a massive move from CSS logical props to production and how you can consider them from a different perspective in your very own projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nicolas Hoffmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn to Code RPG Version 1.5 is Now Playable with Hours of New Gameplay]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-code-rpg-1-5-update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-code-rpg-1-5-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-23T02:43:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello from the Learn to Code RPG dev team! We are Lynn, KayLa, and Nielda. And we've been hard at work building out new adventures for our characters. I'm excited to announce the launch of Learn to Code RPG v1.5, a year after the launch of Learn to Code RPG]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lynn Zheng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Cache Expensive Database Queries Using the Momento Serverless Cache]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/serverless-caching-for-your-web-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/serverless-caching-for-your-web-applications/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T20:45:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When to Use a Cache When you are building a web-application, you'll need to fetch data from a database. As your traffic and the size of your database grows, you will find that querying your database gets slower and slower. In order to return requests to users quickly, a cache]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Brown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[String Equality in JavaScript – How to Compare Strings in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/string-equality-in-javascript-how-to-compare-strings-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/string-equality-in-javascript-how-to-compare-strings-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T18:57:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When writing code or building a solution, you might need to compare two strings to see if they are the same before proceeding with an operation. For example, when a user signs in, you'll want to compare the username the provide to the one in your database to see if]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding to a Dict in Python – How to Add to a Dictionary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/adding-to-a-dict-in-python-how-to-add-to-a-dictionary/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/adding-to-a-dict-in-python-how-to-add-to-a-dictionary/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T18:04:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Python dictionary is like a JavaScript object – it’s a sequence of key:value  pairs. So, you can create them like this: stack_dict = {     "frontend": "JavaScript",     "backend": "Node JS",     "markup": "HTML and JSX", } To access]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Execution Context – How JS Works Behind the Scenes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-javascript-works-behind-the-scene-javascript-execution-context/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-javascript-works-behind-the-scene-javascript-execution-context/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T17:50:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered how JavaScript works behind the scenes? It's actually quite fascinating! And that's what you'll learn about here. JavaScript is a single-threaded interpreted language. Every browser has its own JavaScript engine. Google Chrome has the V8 engine, Mozilla Firefox has SpiderMonkey, and so on. They all are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rwitesh Bera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is enumerate() in Python? Enumeration Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-enumerate-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-enumerate-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-22T15:56:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The enumerate() function is one of the built-in functions in Python. It provides a handy way to access each item in an iterable, along with a count value that specifies the order in which the item was accessed.  In this article you will learn all that you need to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suchandra Datta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Filtering in C# – How to Filter a List with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/filtering-in-csharp-how-to-filter-a-list-with-code-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/filtering-in-csharp-how-to-filter-a-list-with-code-examples/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T21:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Filtering through a data set is one of the most basic operations a developer should know how to perform.  Filtering [https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/dotnet/csharp/programming-guide/concepts/linq/filtering-data]  refers to the process of restricting the result set to contain only those elements that satisfy a specified condition. It is also known as selection.  To]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edeh Israel Chidera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TypeError: can't multiply sequence by non-int of type float [Solved Python Error]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typeerror-cant-multiply-sequence-by-non-int-of-type-float-solved-python-error-3/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typeerror-cant-multiply-sequence-by-non-int-of-type-float-solved-python-error-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T21:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most times when you encounter errors while coding, you can discover the reason why the error is occurring and how you can fix it in the error message. The Python error, "TypeError: can't multiply sequence by non-int of type float" is no exception to that. I have prepared this article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Scapy – Python Networking Tool Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-scapy-python-networking/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-scapy-python-networking/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T21:02:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post you will learn about an amazing tool named Scapy. Scapy is a Python library that enables us to send, sniff, and dissect network frames.  It is useful in a variety of use cases, one of which is to actually get some hands-on experience when you learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Rosenbaum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Concurrent Programming in Go – Goroutines, Channels, and More Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/concurrent-programming-in-go/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/concurrent-programming-in-go/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T19:02:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Concurrency refers to a programming language's ability to deal with lots of things at once. A good way to understand concurrency is by imagining multiple cars traveling on two lanes. Sometimes the cars overtake each other, and sometimes they stop and let others pass by. Another good example is when]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rwitesh Bera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022 Roundup of Web Research]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375869</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/2022-roundup-of-web-research/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T15:03:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve started making a tradition of rounding up the latest front-end research at the end of each year. We did it in 2020 and again in 2021. Reports are released throughout the year by a bunch of different companies …
2022 Roundup of Web Research originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Help choose the syntax for CSS Nesting]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376319</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/help-choose-the-syntax-for-css-nesting/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T16:04:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Nesting is making the rounds yet again. Remember earlier this year when Adam and Miriam put three syntax options up for a vote? Those results were tallied and it wasn’t even even close.
Now there’s another chance …
Help choose the syntax for CSS Nesting originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful Accessibility And Usability Examples To Help Improve Your Designs]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/useful-accessibility-usability-examples-help-improve-your-designs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/useful-accessibility-usability-examples-help-improve-your-designs/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Thomas Bohm shares strategies and methods to tackle some common graphic communication problems and gives you insights into how to improve accessibility and usability and make your designs much better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Thomas Bohm)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Playground: Running WordPress in the Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376297</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/wordpress-playground-run-in-browser/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T16:52:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being able to quickly spin up a WordPress instance has been the strength of WordPress ever since its famous “five-minute install”. Upload a few files, configure a few settings, and you’re off.
The friction of uploading files has gotten …
WordPress Playground: Running WordPress in the Browser originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taking The Stress Out Of Design System Management]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/taking-stress-out-design-system-management/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/taking-stress-out-design-system-management/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Masha goes over five tips that make it easier to manage a design system while increasing its effectiveness. This short guide is aimed at smaller teams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Masha Shaposhnikova)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Infinite 3D Sliders]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375621</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-infinite-3d-sliders/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T14:58:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this series, we’ve been making image sliders with nothing but HTML and CSS. The idea is that we can use the same markup but different CSS to get wildly different results, no matter how many images we toss …
CSS Infinite 3D Sliders originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boosting Productivity For Designers With Efficient Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/optimizing-design-workflow-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/optimizing-design-workflow-tools/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Ashish Bogawat shares some of his favorite ways how to boost productivity and do things faster, better, and probably more fun by using efficient tools and workflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ashish Bogawat)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So, you’d like to animate the display property]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375714</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/so-youd-like-to-animate-the-display-property/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T15:41:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS Working Group gave that a thumbs-up a couple weeks ago. The super-duper conceptual proposal being that we can animate or transition from, say, display: block to display: none.
It’s a bit of a brain-twister to reason …
So, you’d like to animate the display property originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Prioritize User Security When Collecting Offline Data]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/prioritize-user-security-collecting-offline-data/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/prioritize-user-security-collecting-offline-data/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Concerns over online privacy and security are nothing new. In this article, Suzanne Scacca explores how the right CSV importer can help businesses better prioritize user security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Suzanne Scacca)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Links on AI-Related Stuff]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376201</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/some-links-on-ai-related-stuff/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-14T21:34:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every so often, I find that the links I save to read later fall into natural groups or patterns that reveal common threads of interest. The past couple of weeks have produced a lot of thoughts about ChatGPT, an …
Some Links on AI-Related Stuff originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unchain My Inaccessibly-Labelled Heart]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375952</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/unchain-my-inaccessibly-labelled-heart/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-14T14:08:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Suzy Naschansky from the HTMHell Advent Calendar:
<h2 id="article1-heading"All About Dragons</h2<pI like dragons. Blah blah blah blah blah.</p<p<a id="article1-read-more" aria-labelledby="article1-read-more article1-heading"Read more</a</p
See that aria-labelledby attribute? It chains two IDs from the …
Unchain My Inaccessibly-Labelled Heart originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Holiday Snowtacular 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376229</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/holiday-snowtacular-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T23:03:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve got ourselves a real holiday treat! Join host Alex Trost from the Frontend Horse community for the Holiday Snowtacular 2022 this Friday, December 16.
There’s a lineup of 12 awesome speakers — including Chris Coyier, Cassidy Williams, Kevin …
Holiday Snowtacular 2022 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Privacy: Protect Your Users, Protect Yourself]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/understanding-privacy-protect-your-users-protect-yourself/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/understanding-privacy-protect-your-users-protect-yourself/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All of us want to create inclusive, safe, and privacy-aware digital experiences, but where to begin? Our brand new Smashing Book, “Understanding Privacy,” written by Heather Burns, can help you lay the ground for future developers, designers, and project managers to build a better web for tomorrow. [Jump to the details](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/understanding-privacy-new-smashing-book/#about-the-book) or [get the book right away](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/printed-books/understanding-privacy/).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Heather Burns)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible Front-End Patterns For Responsive Tables (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/accessible-front-end-patterns-responsive-tables-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/accessible-front-end-patterns-responsive-tables-part2/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no universal solution for making every kind of table responsive and usable on smaller screens, so we have to rely on various patterns, which Adrian explains in this two-part series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Few Times Container Size Queries Would Have Helped Me Out]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375728</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-few-times-container-size-queries-would-have-helped-me-out/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T13:53:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Container Queries are still gaining traction and many of us are getting our hands wet with them, even if it’s for little experiments or whatnot. They’ve got great, but not quite full, browser support — enough to justify using …
A Few Times Container Size Queries Would Have Helped Me Out originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Christofi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting up a screen reader testing environment on your computer]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375722</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/setting-up-a-screen-reader-testing-environment-on-your-computer/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-12T20:56:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sara Soueidan with everything you need, from what screen reading options are out there all the way to setting up virtual machines for them, installing them, and confguring keyboard options. It’s truly a one-stop reference that pulls together disparate …
Setting up a screen reader testing environment on your computer originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saving Settings for a Custom WordPress Block in the Block Editor]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375577</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/saving-settings-for-a-custom-wordpress-block-in-the-block-editor/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-12T14:06:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve accomplished a bunch of stuff in this series! We created a custom WordPress block that fetches data from an external API and renders it on the front end. Then we took that work and extended it so the data …
Saving Settings for a Custom WordPress Block in the Block Editor originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manoj Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Future Of Design: Human-Powered Or AI-Driven?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/future-design-human-powered-ai-driven/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/future-design-human-powered-ai-driven/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Keima Kai provides a brief history of AI in web design, explores its current implications for creativity, and offers suggestions for how web designers can stay ahead of the curve.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Keima Kai)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Infinite Slider Flipping Through Polaroid Images]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375537</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-infinite-slider-flipping-through-polaroid-images/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-09T14:26:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last article, we made a pretty cool little slider (or “carousel” if that’s what you prefer) that rotates in a circular direction. This time we are going to make one that flips through a stack of Polaroid …
CSS Infinite Slider Flipping Through Polaroid Images originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animated Background Stripes That Transition on Hover]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375697</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/animated-background-stripes-transition-hover/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T15:36:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How often to do you reach for the CSS background-size property? If you’re like me — and probably lots of other front-end folks — then it’s usually when you background-size: cover an image to fill the space of an entire …
Animated Background Stripes That Transition on Hover originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Here! “Understanding Privacy,” A New Smashing Book Is Shipping Now]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/understanding-privacy-new-smashing-book/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/understanding-privacy-new-smashing-book/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Understanding Privacy,” the new Smashing Book by Heather Burns, will help you create inclusive, safe and privacy-aware digital experiences. Print books are now shipping! [Jump to details](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/understanding-privacy-new-smashing-book/#about-the-book) and [get the book right away](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/printed-books/understanding-privacy/).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding Box Shadows to WordPress Blocks and Elements]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375412</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/adding-box-shadows-to-wordpress-blocks-and-elements/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T13:59:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS box-shadow and outline properties gained theme.json support in WordPress 6.1. Let's look at a few examples of how it works in real themes, and what options we have to apply these styles to WordPress blocks and elements.
Adding Box Shadows to WordPress Blocks and Elements originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ganesh Dahal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advent Calendars For Web Designers And Developers (2022 Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/tech-advent-calendars-web-developers-web-designers-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/tech-advent-calendars-web-developers-web-designers-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready for the countdown to Christmas? This year, the web community was once again busy creating tech advent calendars jam-packed with fantastic content to sweeten your days. But which ones to follow? We help you find the right one, whether you’re a front-end dev, UX designer, or content strategist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible Front-End Patterns For Responsive Tables (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/accessible-front-end-patterns-responsive-tables-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/accessible-front-end-patterns-responsive-tables-part1/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-06T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no universal solution for making every kind of table responsive and usable on smaller screens, so we have to rely on various patterns, which Adrian explains in this two-part series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>