<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-06-19T00:11:13.808Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-06-19T00:11:13.808Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use GitHub Copilot to Become a Happier and More Productive Developer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/developer-productivity-with-github-copilot/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/developer-productivity-with-github-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T17:02:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a number of AI tools for developers emerging on the market. But in my mind GitHub Copilot stands above the rest because of its usability, seamless IDE integration, and remarkable enhancements to developer productivity. Copilot offers a variety of AI tools that have radically streamlined my experience as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Kleier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Was SmashingConf In San Franciso Like?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/smashingconf-sanfrancisco2023-recap/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/smashingconf-sanfrancisco2023-recap/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One way of getting a more behind-the-scenes experience of any Smashing event is to apply as a volunteer, and Ren did just that! The SmashingConf team organized a conference in good ol’ San Francisco this year, and here’s pretty much how it went down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ren Chen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock the Mysteries of Pointers in C]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/finally-understand-pointers-in-c/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/finally-understand-pointers-in-c/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T15:14:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are few things in the programming universe that seem as daunting to beginners as pointers in C. Many new programmers shy away from tackling this essential component of the C programming language, which can leave a critical gap in their knowledge. We just posted a full course on the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Infrastructure as Code? Explained for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/infrastructure-as-code-basics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/infrastructure-as-code-basics/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T14:32:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Infrastructure as Code (IaC) is a way of managing your infrastructure like it was code. This gives you all the benefits of using code to create your infrastructure, like version control, faster and safer infrastructure deployments across different environments, and having up to date documentation of your infrastructure. The article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adetunji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Codux: The React Visual Editor That Improves Developer Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/codux-react-visual-editor-improves-developer-experience/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/codux-react-visual-editor-improves-developer-experience/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[Codux](https://codux.hopp.to/smashing) is a new visual IDE brought to you by the fine folks over at[ Wix](https://www.wix.com/). It’s got a lot of low-code features that level the playing field for app development but is really designed for React developers. How so, you ask? That’s what we’re going to explore in this article.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build Server-Side Rendered (SSR) Svelte Apps With SvelteKit]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/build-server-side-rendered-svelte-apps-sveltekit/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/build-server-side-rendered-svelte-apps-sveltekit/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SvelteKit is a framework for building apps using Svelte. In this article, Sriram shows you how to build a server-side rendered (SSR) SvelteKit application and deploy it to Netlify by following this step-by-step guide.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sriram Thiagarajan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Page Elements – Explained for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-page-elements/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-page-elements/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T21:01:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML, which stands for Hypertext Markup Language, is the standard markup language used for creating web pages and structuring their content on the World Wide Web.  HTML serves as the backbone of web development and acts as a fundamental building block for creating web-based documents. Let's take a quick]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Promises Work in JavaScript – A Comprehensive Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/guide-to-javascript-promises/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/guide-to-javascript-promises/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T16:35:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript has the ability to carry out asynchronous (or async) instructions. These instructions run in the background until they have finished processing.  Asynchronous instructions do not stop the JavaScript engine from actively accepting and processing more instructions. This is why JavaScript is non-blocking in nature. There are a few]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amazing Enyichi Agu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Power Platform Fundamentals Certification (PL-900) – Pass the Exam With This Free 4-Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/microsoft-power-platform-fundamentals-certification-pl-900/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/microsoft-power-platform-fundamentals-certification-pl-900/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T14:28:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Certifications like the Microsoft Power Platform Fundamentals can help you advance in your career. You can learn everything you need to know to earn the Microsoft Power Platform Fundamentals Certification by completing this free 4-hour course that we just posted on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Andrew Brown created this course.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 62 With Slava Shestopalov: What Is Design Management?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/smashing-podcast-episode-62/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/smashing-podcast-episode-62/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of The Smashing Podcast, we ask what is a design manager? What does it take and how does it relate to the role of Designer? Vitaly talks to Slava Shestopalov to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI in Google Sheets – How to Use GPT Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-in-google-sheets/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-in-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T22:10:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seems to be the year of AI. And my favorite tool, Google Sheets, is not to be left out of the fun. 🎉 Coefficient [https://coefficient.io/gpt-google-sheets] produced a Google sheets extension with the ability to use OpenAI's GPT models from within a spreadsheet. It’s called GPT Copilot and it’s available]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use MySQL Stored Procedures to Simplify Database Operations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-simplify-database-operations-using-mysql-stored-procedures/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-simplify-database-operations-using-mysql-stored-procedures/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T22:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the realm of database management, MySQL has emerged as one of the most popular and reliable choices.  MySQL not only offers robust data storage capabilities but also provides a powerful feature called "procedures" that allows developers to streamline complex database operations.  In this tutorial, we will delve]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Upgrade Your React Skills with Three Helpful Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/upgrade-your-react-skills/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/upgrade-your-react-skills/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T21:12:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since its announcement in 2013, React.js continues to be one of the most widely used JavaScript tools, thanks to its unmatched versatility and efficiency.  Backed by its component-based architecture and virtual DOM implementation, React.js excels in building modern and dynamic web applications. It enables developers to create reusable UI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moyosore J Olaojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Streamline Your File Upload Process in Express.js with Multer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/simplify-your-file-upload-process-in-express-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/simplify-your-file-upload-process-in-express-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T21:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[File uploading is a common requirement in web development projects. But handling file uploads in Node.js can be complex and time-consuming. That's where Multer comes in.  Multer is a powerful middleware for Node.js that simplifies the file upload process by handling multipart/form-data requests. In this tutorial, you will learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelvin Moses</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Headaches And How To Cure Them: i18n (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/gatsby-headaches-i18n-part-1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/gatsby-headaches-i18n-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this first part of a two-part hands-on guide, Juan Rodriguez explains how to use several i18n plugins for Gatsby and reviews some others.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design Under Constraints: Challenges, Opportunities, And Practical Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/design-constraints-challenges-opportunities-practical-strategies/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/design-constraints-challenges-opportunities-practical-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unleash the power of creative limitation! Learn how constraints aren’t barriers but instead stepping stones to innovative design. Find out how to challenge unproductive restrictions and leverage the rest to your advantage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing Sites And Apps With Blind Users: A Cheat Sheet]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/testing-sites-apps-blind-users-cheat-sheet/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/testing-sites-apps-blind-users-cheat-sheet/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While compliance with accessibility checklists is essential, it doesn’t necessarily mean a pleasant experience. That’s why live sessions can give you lots of priceless insights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Slava Shestopalov &amp; Eugene Shykiriavyi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Universal And Cognitive-Friendly UX Design Through Pivot Tables And Grids]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/universal-cognitive-friendly-ux-design-tables-grids/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/universal-cognitive-friendly-ux-design-tables-grids/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article covers the best tips and recommendations on the elements to pay attention to, the rules to follow, and life hacks to get around certain difficulties in table design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yuliia Nikitina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Primitive Objects In JavaScript: When To Use Them (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/primitive-objects-javascript-part-2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/primitive-objects-javascript-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the second part of the series, Kirill looks at the usefulness of primitive objects, exploring how reducing capabilities could be a benefit for your project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kirill Myshkin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Enable Collaboration In A Multiparty Setting]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/enable-collaboration-multiparty-setting/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/enable-collaboration-multiparty-setting/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Artificial Intelligence becomes more widespread, so too does the adoption of digital agents and voice interactions. Explore the power of mixed reality systems and multimodal communication to enhance collaboration between consultants and clients, transforming advisory services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Hannah Kühne &amp; Madlaina Kalunder)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iA Presenter: A Case Study On Product Pricing Considerations]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/ia-presenter-case-study-product-pricing-considerations/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/ia-presenter-case-study-product-pricing-considerations/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pricing a product or service is one of the more challenging aspects of product development. Pricing is an inexact science, and chances are you will not get it right the first time. But where do you even begin? Let’s explore the important considerations that go into product pricing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced Form Control Styling With Selectmenu And Anchoring API]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/advanced-form-control-styling-selectmenu-anchoring-api/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/advanced-form-control-styling-selectmenu-anchoring-api/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to the Open UI working community group, there’s a new element on the horizon, <selectmenu>, that will make styling this type of form control a whole lot better. You’re going to walk through an early implementation of this new experimental element by creating a pattern that you would never have thought possible with CSS alone — a radial selection menu.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Brecht De Ruyte)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create Your Own Path In June (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new batch of desktop wallpapers might be for you. Designed by artists and designers from across the globe, the wallpapers in this post come in versions with and without a calendar for June 2023. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing A Better Design Handoff File In Figma]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/designing-better-design-handoff-file-figma/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/designing-better-design-handoff-file-figma/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article provides practical tips for improving the handoff process between design and development in product development. The guidance covers effective communication, documentation, design details, version control, and plugin usage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ben Shih)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Success At Scale, A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/success-at-scale-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/success-at-scale-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet “Success At Scale”, our upcoming book with best-practice case studies from industry experts. Print and eBook shipping in fall 2023. Pre-order the book.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Impact Of Agile Methodologies On Code Quality]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/impact-agile-methodologies-code-quality/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/impact-agile-methodologies-code-quality/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Say goodbye to traditional workflows and embrace Agile to unlock the power of high-quality code. Discover how Agile methodologies promote simplicity, modularization, readability, and continuous improvement, resulting in faster turnaround times, more responsive development processes, and ultimately, the creation of high-quality software that meets customer needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sarah Oke Okolo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 61 With Rachel Andrew: What Is Web Platform Baseline?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/smashing-podcast-episode-61/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/smashing-podcast-episode-61/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we’re talking about Web Platform Baseline. What is it, and how can it help determine your browser support policy? Drew McLellan talks to expert Rachel Andrew to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practical Design Tips And Guidelines For Beginner Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/practical-design-tips-guidelines-beginner-designers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/practical-design-tips-guidelines-beginner-designers/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-22T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s easy for beginner designers to get overwhelmed and lose confidence when creating presentations, landing pages, app and web design mockups, and even cards. Laurent Baumann shares a few simple guidelines and practical tips to help you in such situations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Laurent Baumann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>