<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-10-16T00:10:01.080Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-10-16T00:10:01.080Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PostgreSQL Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/posgresql-course-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/posgresql-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-13T14:02:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the realm of databases, making the right decision about which system to adopt can make or break the fluidity and efficiency of your applications. PostgreSQL, an open-source relational database, has increasingly become the go-to choice for developers worldwide.  We just posted a full PostgreSQL course on the freeCodeCamp.org]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Choose Typefaces For Fintech Products: Our Best Practices Guide (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/choose-typefaces-fintech-products-guide-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/choose-typefaces-fintech-products-guide-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-13T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fintech products are systems that are overloaded by many types of data like numerals, texts, spreadsheets, and so on. Working with these products requires the designer to pay a high level of attention and responsibility, as he becomes a provider between user and data. Daria shares her approach to digital product typography and reviews the key points to consider when choosing typefaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Daria Karpenko)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Numbers in Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/add-numbers-in-excel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/add-numbers-in-excel/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T21:02:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know you can write Python code in a spreadsheet? You'd be surprised how many different ways there are to do things in Excel. Below, I'll show you 9 ways to add two or more numbers. You can skip to a certain section if you'd like to see that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Project-Based Learning to Become a Better Developer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/project-based-learning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/project-based-learning/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T18:37:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article you’ll learn about project-based learning – how to get started, how to get ideas for a project, and more. Tutorial hell is real, and it's a terrible place to be in. Project-based learning is the best way to grow as a developer. You’ve probably heard that piece]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathanael Adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forms in HTML – How to Build Basic Forms with HTML]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-basic-forms-with-html/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-basic-forms-with-html/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T14:44:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forms are a fundamental part of web development, allowing users to input and submit data efficiently. Creating forms in HTML is a relatively straightforward process. In this article, we'll explore how to build basic forms using HTML , , and   elements. We'll also cover various input types such]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Bun, a faster Node.js alternative]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-bun-a-faster-node-js-alternative/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-bun-a-faster-node-js-alternative/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T14:39:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript has consistently evolved, always pushing the boundaries of what developers thought possible. Now, entering the spotlight is Bun, a groundbreaking runtime that promises to take JavaScript speeds to unprecedented levels. We just published a Bun crash course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Haider Malik developed this course. Haider has]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything I Know About UX Research I First Learned From Lt. Columbo]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/ux-research-learn-from-lt-columbo/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/ux-research-learn-from-lt-columbo/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working in the area of UX sometimes feels like a crime drama. Can’t believe it? Then look at these fun parallels between modern UX practices and a classical TV detective.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Slava Shestopalov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Better Java Code using Pattern Matching and Sealed Classes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/write-better-java-code-pattern-matching-sealed-classes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/write-better-java-code-pattern-matching-sealed-classes/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T15:48:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article explores how you can improve your Java code quality using Pattern Matching and Sealed Classes.  Java Pattern Matching allows you to write more concise and readable code when working with complex data structures. It simplifies extracting data from data structures and performing operations on them.  Let's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sameer Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build and Deploy a Full Stack Notion Clone with Next.js, DALL-E, Vercel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-and-deploy-a-full-stack-notion-clone-with-next-js-dall-e-vercel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-and-deploy-a-full-stack-notion-clone-with-next-js-dall-e-vercel/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T14:17:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web development has never been more exciting. The influx of new technologies and tools is reshaping the boundaries of what developers can create. At the epicenter of this transformation is the ability to integrate diverse systems seamlessly, creating powerful web applications. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prompt Engineering for Web Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prompt-engineering-for-web-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prompt-engineering-for-web-developers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T17:08:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking to supercharge your web development skills? Do you want to harness the power of AI to streamline your workflow? If so, freeCodeCamp.org's YouTube channel has just the course for you. We just posted a course that will teach you how to use prompt engineering to improve your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Stunning Animations with the Vue.js Transition API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/animations-with-vuejs-transition-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/animations-with-vuejs-transition-api/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T15:28:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m easily gripped by animations and purposeful motion on the Web – so much so that I wrote a whole article [https://favourfelix.com/stories/css-and-motion-build-animations-on-the-web/] on it.  I’m also a big fan of the Vue.js framework, and I’ve been building apps with it for three years. So it was a delightful surprise]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Favour C. Felix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A High-Level Overview Of Large Language Model Concepts, Use Cases, And Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/overview-large-language-model-concepts-use-cases-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/overview-large-language-model-concepts-use-cases-tools/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discuss the concept of large language models (LLMs) and how they are implemented with a set of data to develop an application. Joas compares a collection of no-code and low-code apps designed to help you get a feel for not only how the concept works but also to get a sense of what types of models are available to train AI on different skill sets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joas Pambou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Storage Explained – How to Use localStorage and sessionStorage in JavaScript Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-storage-localstorage-vs-sessionstorage-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-storage-localstorage-vs-sessionstorage-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T16:45:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web Storage is what the JavaScript API [https://codesweetly.com/application-programming-interface-api-explained]  browsers provide for storing data locally and securely within a user’s browser. Session and local storage are the two main types of web storage. They are similar to regular properties objects [https://codesweetly.com/javascript-properties-object], but they persist (do not disappear) when the webpage]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwatobi Sofela</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Headaches: Working With Media (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/gatsby-headaches-working-media-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/gatsby-headaches-working-media-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how to incorporate a variety of media formats, such as images, videos, GIFs, SVGs, and so on, in a Gatsby website. Juan Rodriguez shares what he’s learned about optimizing files for improved performance after working with different plugins and techniques.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Re-Creating The Pop-Out Hover Effect With Modern CSS (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/re-creating-pop-out-hover-effect-modern-css-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/re-creating-pop-out-hover-effect-modern-css-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Re-create a fancy hover effect where an avatar pops out of a starburst pattern for the frame on hover. The idea is to apply the concepts in a new context and gain another view of how trigonometric functions can influence the way we mask elements in CSS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Problem With WordPress Is Positioning, Not Plugins]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/problem-wordpress-positioning-not-plugins/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/problem-wordpress-positioning-not-plugins/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Geoff explores the often-overlooked divide between WordPress.org and WordPress.com, shedding light on the blurred lines between open-source ideals and commercial interests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WaterBear: Building A Free Platform For Impactful Documentaries (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/waterbear-building-free-platform-documentaries-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/waterbear-building-free-platform-documentaries-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this second article of a two-part series, Adrian shares insights about building WaterBear — his first project as a lead developer — discussing the challenges his team encountered while building it and various accessibility and performance improvements they’ve made. You’ll get a peek at the inner workings of a team striving to find its groove to systematize the work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dancing Leaves And Spooky Fellows (October 2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-october-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-october-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How about a little inspiration boost? Well, we might have something for you: desktop wallpapers created with love by artists and designers from across the globe. They are available in versions with and without a calendar for October and can be downloaded for free. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Re-Creating The Pop-Out Hover Effect With Modern CSS (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/re-creating-pop-out-hover-effect-css-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/re-creating-pop-out-hover-effect-css-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is all about experimenting with modern CSS features. We will combine things like CSS masks, CSS variables, trigonometric functions, `@property`, and more to create a neat hover effect that would have been extremely difficult to do even a few years ago without the latest and greatest that CSS has to offer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Enhanced Patterns In WordPress 6.3]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/exploring-enhanced-patterns-system-wordpress/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/exploring-enhanced-patterns-system-wordpress/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Ganesh Dahal explains how the features have evolved since reusable blocks were officially released in WordPress 5.0 — and how the two have converged in WordPress 6.3 to form a powerful feature capable of allowing content creators to sync content and design patterns consistently in pages and posts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ganesh Dahal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With Neon Branching]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/getting-started-with-neon-branching/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/getting-started-with-neon-branching/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Branches are a really nice (and safe) way to configure or reconfigure your database without fear of screwing up the production database. Let’s take a closer look at how branching works with [Neon](https://bit.ly/46cEgX1), and the good news is, you probably already know how it works!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 65 With Alex Older: How Do You Run A Grassroots Conference?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/smashing-podcast-episode-65/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/smashing-podcast-episode-65/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re talking about running grassroots conferences and meet-ups. What does it take to organize a small industry event for your community? Drew McLellan talks to WDC’s Alex Older to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WaterBear: Building A Free Platform For Impactful Documentaries (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/waterbear-building-free-platform-impactful-documentaries-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/waterbear-building-free-platform-impactful-documentaries-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adrian’s kicking off a two-part series, sharing his journey as a lead developer. In the process, you will learn about the lessons and insights Adrian gained at work, including the strategies that went into the technical stack of the project and what it looks like to collaborate with a team he is leading for the first time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Path To Awesome CSS Easing With The linear() Function]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/path-css-easing-linear-function/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/path-css-easing-linear-function/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the new CSS `linear()` easing function on the horizon, the possibilities of what we can do to create natural-feeling animations and transitions in the future are greatly expanded. Jhey Tompkins looks at the current state of CSS easing in this article and demonstrates what we can expect from `linear()`, including handy tools to get your hands on it today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facilitating Inclusive Online Workshops (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/facilitating-inclusive-online-workshops-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/facilitating-inclusive-online-workshops-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To help ensure the success of a workshop, Ben Shih introduces the concept of an inclusive workshop. In Part 2 of the series, you will continue to delve deeper into several key principles and guidelines that you can follow during and after the workshop to encourage an inclusive atmosphere.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ben Shih)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Smashing Magazine Uses TinaCMS To Manage An Editorial Workflow]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/smashing-magazine-tinacms-manage-editorial-workflow/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/smashing-magazine-tinacms-manage-editorial-workflow/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is a peek behind the curtain of how content is managed here at Smashing Magazine. In it, you’ll get a tour of an article’s full lifecycle, from a basic outline to the sort of thing you’re reading right this second.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>