<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-06-01T00:13:02.729Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-06-01T00:13:02.729Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Format a Date with JavaScript – Date Formatting in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-format-a-date-with-javascript-date-formatting-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-format-a-date-with-javascript-date-formatting-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T17:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dates are a fundamental part of many JavaScript applications, whether it's displaying the current date on a webpage or handling user input for scheduling events. But displaying dates in a clear and consistent format is crucial for a positive user experience. In the past, I have written two articles on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Simple Deployment Pipeline with Reusable Github Actions and Heroku]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-simple-deployment-pipeline-with-reuable-github-actions-and-heroku/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-simple-deployment-pipeline-with-reuable-github-actions-and-heroku/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T17:25:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've been using GitHub for a while, you've probably heard of or used GitHub actions.  If you haven't heard of Github Actions or used them before, you can use them for automating your build, test, or deployment pipelines. You can create workflows that will be triggered upon certain]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Temp Table – How to Create a Temporary SQL Table]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-temp-table-how-to-create-a-temporary-sql-table/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-temp-table-how-to-create-a-temporary-sql-table/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T17:22:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SQL, which stands for Structured Query Language, is a programming language specifically designed for managing and manipulating relational databases.  It provides a standardized way to interact with databases and perform tasks such as querying data, inserting, updating, and deleting records, creating and modifying database structures, and more. SQL is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use AWS Cognito for User Authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-aws-cognito-for-user-authentication/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-aws-cognito-for-user-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're building complex applications, one seemingly simple feature can be difficult to implement: user authentication.  Though some apps don't need it depending on their use case, many do. You might spend a ton of time building an authentication module to provide a secure experience to your users and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create Your Own Path In June (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new batch of desktop wallpapers might be for you. Designed by artists and designers from across the globe, the wallpapers in this post come in versions with and without a calendar for June 2023. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Playbooks to Execute an Incident Recovery Plan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-playbooks-for-incident-recovery/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-playbooks-for-incident-recovery/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T01:28:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A playbook is the official, formal written record that describes policies and processes that will reliably produce a working deployment of an organization's resource stack. When it comes to generating predictable results, the playbook is  the plan. I'll describe all the key elements of a good playbook in just]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Cookies to Customize a Web Page's Content]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-cookies-to-customize-web-page-content/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-cookies-to-customize-web-page-content/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T22:04:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you develop websites or web apps, someday you’ll have to deal with cookies. That’s why I decided to write this tutorial on how to use cookies to customize a web page according to the previous web page the user comes from.  I wrote this tutorial using PHP, but]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Venturi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Full-Stack Application with Next.js – A Step-By-Step Tutorial for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-full-stack-application-with-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-full-stack-application-with-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T21:54:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js can seem intimidating at first, with so many new concepts to grasp. But don't worry – in this step-by-step tutorial, I will provide you with all the essential information you need to create your first modern full-stack application with Next.js. In this tutorial, I will take you through the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yazdun Fadali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create and Publish a Vue Component Library – 2023 Update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-and-publish-a-vue-component-library-update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-and-publish-a-vue-component-library-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T20:11:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in 2020, I wrote a post [/news/how-to-create-and-publish-a-vue-component-library/] about building a Vue Component library. Since then the package I used has been deprecated, and the recommended way to build a library/package is to use Vite.  Getting Started I started off the project by running npm create vite@latest and naming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Barrow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Responsive Websites – Best Practices for Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/responsive-design-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/responsive-design-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T20:04:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The way we interact with the web has changed dramatically, and it will keep changing. In the past, most people used desktop computers to access the internet. But today, people are using a wide variety of devices, including laptops, tablets, and smartphones. This has resulted in a growing demand for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fakorede Damilola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does JavaScript Work Behind the Scenes? JS Engine and Runtime Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-javascript-works-behind-the-scenes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-javascript-works-behind-the-scenes/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T18:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So you may know that your code somehow compiles and executes in your browser to display the beautiful web application you’ve built. But are you aware of all the components that come into play to enable the output?  Let’s dive a little into JavaScript behind the scenes. The abstract]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esther Christopher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing A Better Design Handoff File In Figma]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/designing-better-design-handoff-file-figma/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/designing-better-design-handoff-file-figma/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article provides practical tips for improving the handoff process between design and development in product development. The guidance covers effective communication, documentation, design details, version control, and plugin usage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ben Shih)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Success At Scale, A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/success-at-scale-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/success-at-scale-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet “Success At Scale”, our upcoming book with best-practice case studies from industry experts. Print and eBook shipping in fall 2023. Pre-order the book.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Impact Of Agile Methodologies On Code Quality]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/impact-agile-methodologies-code-quality/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/impact-agile-methodologies-code-quality/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Say goodbye to traditional workflows and embrace Agile to unlock the power of high-quality code. Discover how Agile methodologies promote simplicity, modularization, readability, and continuous improvement, resulting in faster turnaround times, more responsive development processes, and ultimately, the creation of high-quality software that meets customer needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sarah Oke Okolo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 61 With Rachel Andrew: What Is Web Platform Baseline?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/smashing-podcast-episode-61/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/smashing-podcast-episode-61/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we’re talking about Web Platform Baseline. What is it, and how can it help determine your browser support policy? Drew McLellan talks to expert Rachel Andrew to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practical Design Tips And Guidelines For Beginner Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/practical-design-tips-guidelines-beginner-designers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/practical-design-tips-guidelines-beginner-designers/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-22T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s easy for beginner designers to get overwhelmed and lose confidence when creating presentations, landing pages, app and web design mockups, and even cards. Laurent Baumann shares a few simple guidelines and practical tips to help you in such situations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Laurent Baumann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Deal With Big Tooling Upgrades In Large Organizations]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/big-tooling-upgrades-large-organizations/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/big-tooling-upgrades-large-organizations/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The process of upgrading large third-party packages in equally large organizations is rarely, if ever, as easy as running an npm update and calling it a day in this context. Joran Quinten shares valuable lessons from his team’s experiences in upgrading third-party code that affects codebases across the entire organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joran Quinten)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design Patterns Are A Better Way To Collaborate On Your Design System]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/design-patterns-collaborate-design-system/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/design-patterns-collaborate-design-system/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every company and team has to have deep collaboration between engineering and design to get the value out of a design system (and not go nuts). Building design patterns first unblock people to work in parallel, keeps people synced up, and results in reusable modules that speed up your next project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ben Clemens)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solving Media Object Float Issues With CSS Block Formatting Contexts]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/media-object-float-issues-css-block-formatting-contexts/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/media-object-float-issues-css-block-formatting-contexts/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article covers common problems using CSS floats and how to solve them using a block formatting context (BFC). Whether you are a beginner or an experienced web developer, you will learn valuable insights and practical solutions for dealing with CSS float issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Gabriel Shoyombo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Sticky Menus: UX Guidelines]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/sticky-menus-ux-guidelines/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/sticky-menus-ux-guidelines/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are sticky headers always a good idea? Best practices for designing sticky headers, with examples, UX guidelines and usability considerations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Boost Your Design Workflow With Setapp]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/boost-design-workflow-setapp/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/boost-design-workflow-setapp/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, we’ll explore efficient tools to save time and speed up your workflow. Focus on what you do best — designing high-quality work, and let these tools handle the rest!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Rachel How)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Redux Toolkit With TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/guide-redux-toolkit-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/guide-redux-toolkit-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Redux Toolkit documentation calls the library a better way to write Redux logic for React apps and a simple and efficient toolkit for Redux development. In this article, you will learn about the Redux toolkit by building an app that tracks project issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Deepak Kumar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use AI Tools To Skyrocket Your Programming Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/ai-tools-skyrocket-programming-productivity/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/ai-tools-skyrocket-programming-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rise of Artificial Intelligence (AI) in recent times has incited fear in many over losing their jobs. However, that shouldn’t be the case. On the contrary, AI is an opportunity to take your programming to the next level when used tactfully with the right knowledge, as we’ll cover today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shane Duggan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Safest Way To Hide Your API Keys When Using React]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/safest-way-hide-api-keys-react/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/safest-way-hide-api-keys-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to make sure your API keys are safe and sound when working with React? Jessica Joseph’s got you covered! She will show you the best ways to hide your API keys, from using environment variables to building your own back-end proxy server.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jessica Joseph)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning JavaScript With Imagination]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/learning-javascript-with-imagination/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/learning-javascript-with-imagination/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the story of how one little octopus, explaining one beginner’s concept, carried such weight and power for Kylo that it drove his work and led him to research something that is really quite silly. And yet, it transformed how he learned to write — and finally understand — JavaScript.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kylo Robinson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Growing Need For Effective Password Management]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/effective-password-management/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/effective-password-management/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Highlighting the advantages of self-hosted solutions over cloud-based alternatives and exploring collaborative password management and more, P demonstrates how to organize convenient and secure password management in a company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iliya Garakh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>