<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-10-29T00:11:34.900Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-10-29T00:11:34.900Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Programming Language to Learn – Beginners Guide to Coding]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-best-programming-language-to-learn-beginners-guide-to-coding/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-best-programming-language-to-learn-beginners-guide-to-coding/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T21:03:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technology is changing how we live. We use and rely on web applications and electronic devices daily to complete various tasks. And behind these modern-day software programs are thousands of lines of code. Coding is one of the most valuable skills to learn today. You can not only build any]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Flexbox Explained – Complete Guide to Flexible Containers and Flex Items]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-flexbox-complete-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-flexbox-complete-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T14:28:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Flexbox gives you the tools to create basic and advanced website layouts in flexible and responsive ways. This tutorial discusses everything you need to know to use Flexbox like a pro. Table of Contents  1.  What Is Flexbox?  2.  Flex Container vs. Flex Item: What's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwatobi Sofela</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Motion Controls In The Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/motion-controls-browser/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/motion-controls-browser/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've ever wanted to build a web app that you can control with hand gestures as if by magic, this article is for you. With a couple of APIs and some JavaScript, you can build apps that behave like sorcery.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yaphi Berhanu)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fancy Image Decorations: Outlines and Complex Animations]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374302</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/fancy-image-decorations-outlines-and-complex-animations/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T12:45:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve spent the last two articles in this three-part series playing with gradients to make really neat image decorations using nothing but the <img> element. In this third and final piece, we are going to explore more techniques using the …
Fancy Image Decorations: Outlines and Complex Animations originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up a GitHub OAuth Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-a-github-oauth-application/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-a-github-oauth-application/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T21:31:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub is an incredibly useful OAuth provider, especially if you are building an application targeted toward developers.  In this article, we will give you a quick rundown of how to set up a GitHub OAuth application. Create Your Application Begin by navigating to your GitHub settings (make sure you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Naomi Carrigan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Forms in React using react-hook-form]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-forms-in-react-using-react-hook-form/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-forms-in-react-using-react-hook-form/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T19:47:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating forms in React is a complex task. It involves handling all the input states and their changes and validating that input when the form gets submitted. For simple forms, things are generally manageable. But as your form gets more complex and you need to add various validations, it becomes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yogesh Chavan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Open an XML File]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-open-an-xml-file/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-open-an-xml-file/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T18:58:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XML stands for eXtensible Markup Language. XML files are readable files that describe the structure of data. You store XML files with the .xml extension. An XML file contains tags that specify how the document should be structured and how it should be stored and transmitted over the internet. It]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Unit Tests for Python Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-unit-tests-for-python-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-unit-tests-for-python-functions/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T18:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This guide will teach you how to write unit tests for Python functions. But why should you consider writing unit tests at all? Well, when working on a large project, you'll often have to update certain modules and refactor code as needed. But such changes can have unintended consequences on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bala Priya C</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Python Programming – Everything You Need to Know (Free Book)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-python-book/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-python-book/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T16:38:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python is one of the most popular programming languages in the world today. It was created in 1991 by Guido van Rossum. According to van Rossum, Python is a: > “high-level programming language, and its core design philosophy is all about code readability and a syntax which allows programmers to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fatos Morina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Network Devices – How Hubs and Switches Work and How to Secure Them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-hub-switch-work-and-how-to-protect-them/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-hub-switch-work-and-how-to-protect-them/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous post [/news/the-complete-guide-to-the-ethernet-protocol/] I described every bit and byte of the Ethernet protocol. In this post you will learn about two network devices, how they work, and how this knowledge may be used by hackers. How Classic Ethernet Works Before describing the network devices, consider a network without]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Rosenbaum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Kotlin in 14 Hours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-kotlin-complete-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-kotlin-complete-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T14:21:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kotlin is the most popular programming language for building Android apps and it can also be can be used for any kind of development. We just published a full Kotlin course for beginners on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Alex Cristian developed this course. Alex is an experienced developer who has]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Web Pages Get Rendered on the Browser – Different Methods Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-page-rendering-on-the-browser-different-methods/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-page-rendering-on-the-browser-different-methods/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, all over the world, computers and networks are getting faster. This is good for web development and user experience in general. And the possibilities of what people can achieve have taken a massive leap forward. But although growth is evident in many places, others are left behind in this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Favour C. Felix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Holographic Trading Card Effect]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374609</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/holographic-trading-card-effect/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T17:05:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Simon Goellner (@simeydotme)’s collection of Holographic Trading Cards have captured our attention.
Under the hood there is a suite of filter(), background-blend-mode(), mix-blend-mode(), and clip-path() combinations that have been painstakingly tweaked to reach the desired effect. I …
Holographic Trading Card Effect originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bradley Kouchi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Typographic Hierarchies]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/typographic-hierarchies/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/typographic-hierarchies/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Alma Hoffmann discusses six basic variables to establish a typographic hierarchy, explains how to look at each differently, and in turn, designs pieces by intentionally modifying each variable to create a typographic hierarchy effectively.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alma Hoffmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Animated, Clickable Cards With the :has() Relational Pseudo Class]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374690</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-animated-clickable-cards-with-the-has-relational-pseudo-class/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T14:15:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS :has() pseudo class is rolling out in many browsers with Chrome and Safari already fully supporting it. It’s often referred to it as “the parent selector” — as in, we can select style a parent element from a …
Creating Animated, Clickable Cards With the :has() Relational Pseudo Class originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brecht De Ruyte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State Of CSS Survey: Influence The Future Of CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/state-css-survey-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/state-css-survey-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The annual survey for anyone who writes CSS, [State of CSS](https://stateofcss.com/en-us/?source=smashing_magazine_css_survey), is nearing the end of its response period for 2022. The survey is available in many different languages and all questions are optional.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lea Verou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is There Too Much CSS Now?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374364</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/is-there-too-much-css-now/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T12:59:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As front-end developers, we’ve wished for a lot of things over the years — ways to center things in CSS, encapsulate styles, set an element’s aspect ratio, get finer-grained control over our colors, select an element based on its children’s …
Is There Too Much CSS Now? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sacha Greif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fancy Image Decorations: Masks and Advanced Hover Effects]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374194</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/fancy-image-decorations-masks-and-advanced-hover-effects/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T12:46:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Part 2 of this three-part series! We are still decorating images without any extra elements and pseudo-elements. I hope you already took the time to digest Part 1 because we will continue working with a lot of gradients …
Fancy Image Decorations: Masks and Advanced Hover Effects originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Futuristic CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/futuristic-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/futuristic-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Sacha Greif tries to anticipate future CSS trends and takes a look at some far-fetched and futuristic CSS features that might one day make their way to the browser.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sacha Greif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instant Articles, Proprietary Syndication, and a Web Built on User Fidelity Preferences]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374470</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/instant-articles-proprietary-syndication-user-fidelity-preferences/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T19:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love it when there’s a sense of synergy in the blogosphere. First, I caught Nick Heer’s coverage of Meta ending support for Instant Articles, its proprietary format for stripped-down performant news articles. He also compares it to the similar …
Instant Articles, Proprietary Syndication, and a Web Built on User Fidelity Preferences originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New In DevTools: Halloween Edition 🎃]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/devtools-updates-halloween-edition/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/devtools-updates-halloween-edition/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Patrick Brosset gives an update on the most impactful new features that are now available in DevTools, across Firefox, Chrome, Safari, and Edge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Patrick Brosset)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsive Animations for Every Screen Size and Device]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374345</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/responsive-animations-for-every-screen-size-and-device/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T12:42:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before I career jumped into development, I did a bunch of motion graphics work in After Effects. But even with that background, I still found animating on the web pretty baffling.
Video graphics are designed within a specific ratio and …
Responsive Animations for Every Screen Size and Device originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cassie Evans</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make a Folder “Slit” Effect With CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374376</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-make-a-folder-slit-effect-with-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T12:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you put something — say a regular sheet of paper — in a manilla folder, a part of that thing might peek out of the folder a little bit. The same sort of thing with a wallet and credit …
How to Make a Folder “Slit” Effect With CSS originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Privacy: A New Smashing Book Is Here]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/understanding-privacy-book-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/understanding-privacy-book-release/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Understanding Privacy, our brand new Smashing Book to make sense of privacy, and learn how to create inclusive, safe and privacy-aware digital experiences. eBook now available, print shipping in November.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manuel Matuzovic: max() Trickery]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374466</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/manuel-matuzovic-max-trickery/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T13:54:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By way of a post by Manuel Matuzović which is by way of a demo by Temani Afif.
.wrapper {
  margin-inline: max(0px, ((100% - 64rem) / 2)); 
}
You’d be doing yourself a favor to read Manuel’s breakdown of …
Manuel Matuzovic: max() Trickery originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pure CSS Bezier Curve Motion Paths]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373600</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/pure-css-bezier-curve-motion-paths/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T15:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Besides being elegant, Bezier curves have nice mathematical properties due to their definition and construction. No wonder they are widely used in so many areas! Now, how about using Bezier curves as motion paths with CSS?
Pure CSS Bezier Curve Motion Paths originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lu Wang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Full-Site Editing: A Deep Dive Into The New Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/wordpress-full-site-editing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/wordpress-full-site-editing/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Nick Schäferhoff will take a deep dive into WordPress Full-Site Editing, examine the tools it provides for theme development, and provide a tutorial on how to use it to make changes to your site.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nick Schäferhoff)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the CSScenes, October 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374393</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/behind-the-csscenes-october-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T21:40:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, hey, welcome back to Behind the CSScenes! These posts are like little check-ins we’re doing each month to give you a peek behind what we’re doing here at CSS-Tricks, as well as a chance for us to pause …
Behind the CSScenes, October 2022 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haley Mills</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fancy Image Decorations: Single Element Magic]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373965</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/fancy-image-decorations-single-element-magic/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T15:37:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the title says, we are going to decorate images! There’s a bunch of other articles out there that talk about this, but what we’re covering here is quite a bit different because it’s more of a challenge. The challenge? …
Fancy Image Decorations: Single Element Magic originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Things I Took Away From An Event Apart 2022 in Denver]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374401</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/some-things-i-took-away-from-an-event-apart-2022-in-denver/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T20:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Event Apart 2022 Denver wrapped up yesterday. And while I was unable to make it to all three days this time, I did catch yesterday’s action — and it was awesome. I’m not very social or outgoing, but …
Some Things I Took Away From An Event Apart 2022 in Denver originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Pure CSS Gallery Focus Effect with :not]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373508</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-pure-css-gallery-focus-effect-with-not/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T15:10:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oftentimes in the past, I needed to figure out how to add styles to all elements inside the container but not the hovered one.
Demo of the expected “fade-out” effect on siblings to let users “focus” on a particular element.…
A Pure CSS Gallery Focus Effect with :not originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krzysztof Gonciarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Effective Communication For Everyday Meetings]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/effective-communication-everyday-meetings/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/effective-communication-everyday-meetings/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article about conducting productive meetings, Andrii Zhdan will give you a step-by-step guide on preparing a solid meeting structure that will let you follow the original plan and reach the meeting goals, and he will also share a few tips based on his design experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andrii Zhdan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Early Days of Container Style Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374330</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/early-days-of-container-style-queries/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T13:06:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re still in suuuuuper early days with container queries. Too early for broad browser support, but Chromium already supports it, Safari started supporting it in version 16, and Firefox is presumably not far behind.
Most early days conversations …
Early Days of Container Style Queries originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sustainable Web Development Strategies Within An Organization]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/sustainable-web-development-strategies-organization/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/sustainable-web-development-strategies-organization/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Climate change and sustainability are increasing concerns for digital organizations, as well as individuals working in tech. In this article, we’ll explore some of the ways we can raise awareness and effect change within an organization to create a more positive environmental impact.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delightful UI Animations With Shared Element Transitions API (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/ui-animations-shared-element-transitions-api-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/ui-animations-shared-element-transitions-api-part2/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Adrian Bece will show how to create same-document page transitions for Single Page Apps using Shared Element Transitions API and check out its future implementation and potential for creating cross-document transitions in Multi-Page Apps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Roadmap For Building A Business Chatbot]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/roadmap-building-business-chatbot/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/roadmap-building-business-chatbot/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Owing to tremendous advancements in Machine Learning and other technologies, chatbots have increased in popularity in the past few years. This article will show you, step by step, how to build a chatbot that meets your business goals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Devansh Bansal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js Authentication With Twilio Verify]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/nodejs-authentication-twilio-verify/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/nodejs-authentication-twilio-verify/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Integrate two-factor authentication into your Express.js app by building an application that authenticates users using password-based authentication and OTPs powered by the Twilio Verify service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alexander Godwin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easy Fluid Typography With clamp() Using Sass Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/fluid-typography-clamp-sass-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/fluid-typography-clamp-sass-functions/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We can use the `clamp()` method today because of the great browser support. In this article, Brecht De Ruyte explains how it can be a beautiful addition to your upcoming project or as an upgrade to a previous one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Brecht De Ruyte)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delightful UI Animations With Shared Element Transitions API (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/ui-animations-shared-element-transitions-api-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/ui-animations-shared-element-transitions-api-part1/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shared Element Transitions API is a game-changing feature that will enable us to create impressive and elaborate UI animations easily. In this article, Adrian Bece will explore its incredible potential by building four real-life examples from scratch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[October Vibes For Your Desktop (2022 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-october-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-october-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How about a little inspiration boost? Well, we might have something for you: desktop wallpapers created with love by artists and designers from across the globe. They are available in versions with and without a calendar for October and can be downloaded for free. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unconscious Biases That Get In The Way Of Inclusive Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/unconscious-biases-inclusive-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/unconscious-biases-inclusive-design/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Throughout the research and design processes, our unconscious biases are the greatest risk to delivering inclusive experiences. From who we include and exclude in our research to how we plan and conduct research, it’s crucial that we understand how our unacknowledged biases can perpetuate systems of exclusion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Trina Moore Pervall)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>