<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-03-15T00:09:46.351Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-03-15T00:09:46.351Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Back End Developer Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/back-end-developer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/back-end-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T14:18:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every week we publish a lot of great content on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. New people sometimes wonder where to start and what order to watch the courses. Well, if you want to become a back end developer, this is where to start. We just released our back end developer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Neovim Using the nvchad Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/install-neovim-with-nvchad/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/install-neovim-with-nvchad/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T14:17:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neovim [https://neovim.io/] is a popular IDE and is a solid alternative to VS Code. Neovim supports every major programming language and allows you to build anything, anywhere.  Neovim can be a bit problematic to start with, especially for newcomers. Writing a Neovim configuration from scratch is often difficult. To]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use and Create Streams from Scratch in Dart and Flutter – a Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-and-create-streams-in-dart-and-flutter/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-and-create-streams-in-dart-and-flutter/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T13:37:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Programming can be a rollercoaster ride. It catapults you from feeling like a genius to feeling utterly clueless, and back again — all in the blink of an eye.  What's even more wild is that this cycle repeats itself countless times throughout the day, and for the entirety of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Asaboro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Localize Your Websites with Crowdin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/localize-websites-with-crowdin/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/localize-websites-with-crowdin/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T18:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reaching a global audience is crucial for the success of any online platform, whether it is an app or a website. Understanding and implementing effective localization strategies can significantly enhance user engagement by providing content in the user's native language. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Better AI Workflows with Langchain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-better-ai-workflows-with-langchain/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-better-ai-workflows-with-langchain/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T13:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered how to use Large Language Models (LLMs) like ChatGPT in your app? Yes, there is the OpenAI API. You can use it to generate responses based on prompts. But what if you want to build a complex application with LLMs integrated tightly into the user experience?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add and Remove Elements from Arrays in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-and-remove-js-array-elements/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-and-remove-js-array-elements/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T12:34:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arrays are common data structures in JavaScript, and it is important to know how to work with them. Common operations on arrays include adding or removing elements from the beginning, end or at a specific index. In this article, you will learn how to work with the built in JavaScript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an AI-enhanced Task App with React and Appwrite]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-task-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-task-app/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T09:21:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you'll build a task manager application that has some artificial intelligence capabilities and is voice-enabled, sortable, and searchable.  As an extra, the application will have dark mode support that respects the users' system preferences. The application will be able to create, read, update and delete (CRUD)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fatuma Abdullahi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 JavaScript Algorithms for Coding Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/top-10-javascript-algorithms-for-coding-challenges/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/top-10-javascript-algorithms-for-coding-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T17:37:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you gearing up for coding interviews and looking to strengthen your grasp on JavaScript algorithms? We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp Community YouTube channel that will equip you with the essential skills to excel in Leetcode-style coding challenges. Mukhtar from Coding Monkey developed this course. The course]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethical Hacking 101 – How to Set Up Metasploitable on Your Computer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-metasploitable/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-metasploitable/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T12:39:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ladies and Gentlemen, welcome to the world of Virtual Machines 🖥️ So you’ve discovered the world of ethical hacking and you want to try your hands on something. Trouble is, doing some ‘practical application’ on the wrong thing could get you fined, arrested, and even undesired jail time. You don’t]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Iwugo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Run SQL-Like Queries on Files]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-run-sql-like-queries-on-files/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-run-sql-like-queries-on-files/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T12:33:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone! I'm a Software engineer who is interested in low-level programming, compilers, and tool development. At the end of 2023, I published my first article on freeCodeCamp about how I created a SQL-like Language to run queries on local Git repositories [/news/gql-design-and-implementation/]. If you want a bit more context,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amr Hesham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Event Calendars For Web Made Easy With These Commercial Options]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/event-calendars-web-commercial-options/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/event-calendars-web-commercial-options/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Collection of top-notch calendar components for seamless event scheduling. Whether you prefer ready-to-use setups or enjoy tweaking code for a tailored experience, these calendars have you covered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Preethi Sam)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Success At Scale: Last Chance For Pre-Sale Price]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/success-at-scale-book-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/success-at-scale-book-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our next book, “Success at Scale” is finally at the printer, which means we’ll be shipping books soon. It’s also your last chance to get the book at the presale price. Get your copy and save now!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern CSS Tooltips And Speech Bubbles (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/modern-css-tooltips-speech-bubbles-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/modern-css-tooltips-speech-bubbles-part2/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Part 1 of this series, Temani Afif explored different CSS techniques to create tooltip shapes. The main challenge was to rely on a single element and create optimized code that could easily be controlled using CSS variables to update the size, shape, and position of the tail. In this second part, you are going explore more shapes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The End Of My Gatsby Journey]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/end-of-gatsby-journey/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/end-of-gatsby-journey/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[“Gatsby headaches”](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/gatsby-headaches-i18n-part-1/) are over. Juan Diego Rodríguez reflects on his decision to stop using Gatsby as his go-to framework. Through a detailed examination of its strengths and weaknesses, he provides valuable insights and alternative options for developers navigating their tooling choices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern CSS Tooltips And Speech Bubbles (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/modern-css-tooltips-speech-bubbles-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/modern-css-tooltips-speech-bubbles-part1/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tooltips are a very common pattern used in CSS for years. There are a lot of ways to approach tooltips in CSS, though some evoke headaches with all the magic numbers they require. In this article, Temani Afif presents modern techniques to create tooltips with the smallest amount of markup and the greatest amount of flexibility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Waiting For Spring (March 2024 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-march-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-march-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new batch of desktop wallpapers is for you. Designed by artists and designers from across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar for March 2024. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reporting Core Web Vitals With The Performance API]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/reporting-core-web-vitals-performance-api/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/reporting-core-web-vitals-performance-api/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Performance API is a set of standards for measuring and evaluating performance metrics with JavaScript. This article demonstrates how to use the Performance API to generate performance metrics directly in the DOM to create your own reporting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Web Designer’s Accessibility Advocacy Toolkit]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/web-designer-accessibility-advocacy-toolkit/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/web-designer-accessibility-advocacy-toolkit/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital designer Yichan Wang has put together this collection of strategies and selling points to help you encourage and advocate for accessibility in your place of work, including useful scripts you can use as starting points.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yichan Wang)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vanilla JavaScript, Libraries, And The Quest For Stateful DOM Rendering]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/vanilla-javascript-libraries-quest-stateful-dom-rendering/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/vanilla-javascript-libraries-quest-stateful-dom-rendering/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s well-established that the web faces wide-ranging usability and performance issues, from user-hostile UI patterns and twisted search results to sluggish performance and battery-draining bloat. In this article, Frederik examines one small-but-significant aspect where developers take the reins: Painting pixels on the screen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederik Dohr)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Practical Guide To Designing For Colorblind People]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/designing-for-colorblindness/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/designing-for-colorblindness/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Color accessibility is more than just ticking boxes. Even with good contrast, some color palettes can make interfaces challenging for users. Here are some practical guidelines to ensure more inclusive design for colorblind people. An upcoming part of Smart Interface Design Patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile Accessibility Barriers For Assistive Technology Users]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/mobile-accessibility-barriers-assistive-technology-users/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/mobile-accessibility-barriers-assistive-technology-users/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility goes beyond making products user-friendly. It can significantly impact the quality of life for people with disabilities. Kate Kalcevich shares lessons she learned from assistive technology users — challenges and barriers they encounter on mobile devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kate Kalcevich)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Accessibility Standards Can Empower Better Chart Visual Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/accessibility-standards-empower-better-chart-visual-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/accessibility-standards-empower-better-chart-visual-design/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility for data visualization extends well beyond web standards, at least if you’re trying to create an experience that’s actually useful. This article focuses on techniques for creating useful and accessible visualizations that extend well beyond compliance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kent Eisenhuth)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>