<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-01-18T00:10:36.615Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-01-18T00:10:36.615Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ACID Databases – Atomicity, Consistency, Isolation & Durability Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/acid-databases-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/acid-databases-explained/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T17:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ACID stands for Atomicity, Consistency, Isolation and Durability. These are four key properties that most database management systems (DBMS) offer as guarantees when handling transactions. Most popular DBMS like MySQL [https://dev.mysql.com/doc/refman/8.0/en/mysql-acid.html], PostgresSQL [https://www.postgresql.org/about/] and Oracle [https://docs.oracle.com/cd/F51125_01/docs.85/SDS%20PI/acid-compliant-transactions.html#GUID-ECB79D66-46DE-4F48-93DC-8677E7BB44EF]  have ACID guarantees out of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adetunji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use TUI Applications with Click and Trogon – Linux Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tui-applications-with-click-and-trogon/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tui-applications-with-click-and-trogon/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T17:36:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux and terminal applications are almost synonymous. If you have used applications like grep, cat, sed, and AWK, those are command line interfaces ( CLI [https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Command-line_interface]). And when they work together, they allow you to unleash the power of your computer by mixing and matching a few commands. Sometimes the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Vicente Nunez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Custom Buttons to a Date Picker in Flatpickr]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-custom-buttons-to-flatpickr/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-custom-buttons-to-flatpickr/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T02:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've ever had to use a date picker in a web frontend project, chances are that you've used flatpickr. For the unacquainted, flatpickr [https://flatpickr.js.org/] is one of the most popular date picker libraries in the open source-verse. It's framework-agnostic, highly customizable, and lightweight. I recently had to use it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Idris Abdul-Lateef</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atomics and Concurrency in C++]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/atomics-and-concurrency-in-cpp/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/atomics-and-concurrency-in-cpp/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T23:50:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Concurrency is a programming term you'll need to be familiar with if you code in C++. It's especially relevant if you want to get more out of your available compute resources.  But concurrency comes with certain problems. Some of them can be solved using  mutexes [https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mutual_exclusion], although mutexes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaid Humayun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced Object-Oriented Programming in Java – Full Book]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/object-oriented-programming-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/object-oriented-programming-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T23:17:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Java is a go-to language for many programmers, and it's a critical skill for any software engineer. After learning Java, picking up other programming languages and advanced concepts becomes much easier.  In this book, I'll cover the practical knowledge you need to move from writing basic Java code to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vahe Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Arrow Functions vs Regular Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/regular-vs-arrow-functions-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/regular-vs-arrow-functions-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T22:19:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, there are two main ways of writing functions. You can create functions using the regular function syntax. Or you can use the arrow function syntax.  In this article, you will learn how to use both options. You'll also learn about the differences between the two and when]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Semah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the Essentials of Data Engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-essentials-of-data-engineering/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-essentials-of-data-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T21:52:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to freeCodeCamp's Data Engineering Video Course Data Engineering is a vital field in the tech industry focused on designing, building, and maintaining systems that collect, process, and analyze large volumes of data. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel all about data engineering, designed to cater]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Optimize AWS Simple Storage Service for Better Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-optimize-aws-s3-for-performance/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-optimize-aws-s3-for-performance/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T21:36:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[S3 is an Amazon Web Service that provides data storage and retrieval in the cloud. ‌‌ This article will discuss the common S3 performance bottlenecks and how they impact the service's overall performance. It will also share some best practices to serve as guidelines for optimising the performance of your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Feyijimi Erinle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How File Ownership and Permissions Work in RHEL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/file-ownership-permissions-rhel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/file-ownership-permissions-rhel/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T20:56:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux commands give you precise control over file ownership and permissions, ensuring data security and access control.  This guide will delve into several essential commands: chown, chgrp, chmod, and  umask. The examples will showcase their functionality, variations, and practical applications. Table Of Contents Here's what we'll cover in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kedar Makode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Engine and Runtime Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-engine-and-runtime-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-engine-and-runtime-explained/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T19:03:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A JavaScript engine is simply a computer program that executes JavaScript code. It's responsible for translating human-readable JavaScript code into machine-readable instructions that the computer's hardware can execute. When you write JavaScript code and run it in a browser, the code doesn't directly interact with your computer's hardware. Instead, it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Complex But Awesome CSS border-image Property]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/css-border-image-property/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/css-border-image-property/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS `border-image` property is one of those properties you undoubtedly know exists but may not have ever reached for. In this article, Temani Afif demonstrates different approaches for using `border-image` to create clever decorative accents and shapes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Front-End Tools Of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/top-frontend-tools-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/top-frontend-tools-2023/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Useful front-end tools for CSS and JavaScript developers that were most popular last year and will help you speed up your development workflow. Let’s dive in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Louis Lazaris)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SolidStart: A Different Breed Of Meta-Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/solidstart-different-breed-meta-framework/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/solidstart-different-breed-meta-framework/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready for a little exercise of pulling a framework apart and putting the pieces back together? In this article, Atila Fassina explains how meta-frameworks have evolved around core libraries in their own unique ways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API And Delightful UI Animations (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/view-transitions-api-ui-animations-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/view-transitions-api-ui-animations-part2/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API is a new — but game-changing — feature that allows us to do the types of reactive state-based UI and page transitions that have traditionally been exclusive to JavaScript frameworks. In the second half of this mini two-part series, Adrian Bece expands on the demos from the first article to demonstrate how the View Transitions API can be used to transition not just elements between two states but the transition between full views and pages in single-page and multi-page applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Magic Of New Beginnings (January 2024 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2024/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s start into the new year with a little inspiration boost: wallpapers created with love by the community for the community. Happy 2024!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Sense Of “Senseless” JavaScript Features]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/making-sense-of-senseless-javascript-features/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/making-sense-of-senseless-javascript-features/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript may be the most popular client-side language in the world, but it’s far from perfect and not without its quirks. Juan Diego Rodriguez examines several “absurd” JavaScript eccentricities and explains how they made it into the language as well as how to avoid them in your own code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API And Delightful UI Animations (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/view-transitions-api-ui-animations-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/view-transitions-api-ui-animations-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API is a new — but game-changing — feature that allows us to do the types of reactive state-based UI and page transitions that have traditionally been exclusive to JavaScript frameworks. In the first part of this mini two-part series, Adrian Bece thoroughly explains why we need the API and demonstrates its basic usage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New CSS Viewport Units Do Not Solve The Classic Scrollbar Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/new-css-viewport-units-not-solve-classic-scrollbar-problem/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/new-css-viewport-units-not-solve-classic-scrollbar-problem/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the introduction of CSS viewport units in 2012, many of us have been using `width: 100vw` as a way to set an element’s width to the full width of the viewport. But, as Šime Vidas explains in this deep dive, `100vw` does not always represent the full width of the viewport due to differences in how browsers handle scrollbars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Šime Vidas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>