<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-01-22T00:11:37.525Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-01-22T00:11:37.525Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Data Analysis and Visualization with Python Using Astronomical Data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-data-analysis-and-visualization-with-python-using-astrongomical-data/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-data-analysis-and-visualization-with-python-using-astrongomical-data/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T19:48:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you fascinated by both Python and the night sky? We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Python to analyze and visualize astronomical Data. This course was created by Spartificial, whose mission is to provide engineering education in the most]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Secure Your Web Server with Continuous Integration Using NGINX and CircleCI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/secure-web-server-with-continuous-integration-using-nginx-and-circleci/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/secure-web-server-with-continuous-integration-using-nginx-and-circleci/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T16:46:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web servers are responsible for delivering web pages and various resources to clients through the internet. They can exist either as software or hardware components. But unfortunately, they often become targets for hackers and malicious individuals seeking to exploit any vulnerabilities to compromise data and disrupt functionality. As a result,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abraham Dahunsi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started with FPM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/getting-started-with-fpm/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/getting-started-with-fpm/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T16:42:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FPM [https://fpm.readthedocs.io/en/latest/getting-started.html] is a powerful wrapper that allows you to create packages for multiple programs in multiple operating systems.  In this tutorial I will show you how you can replace some of the tedious packaging of third party applications. What You Need to Complete this Tutorial  * A]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Vicente Nunez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use SonarLint to Write Cleaner Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-sonarlint-to-write-cleaner-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-sonarlint-to-write-cleaner-code/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T23:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're building a coding project, the better it is, the more fun it'll be to use. And the prouder you'll be of your hard work, right?  Also, writing quality and performant code helps your program or website work as expected – which should be every developer's goal. SonarLint]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okosa Leonard Onyekachukwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get a Developer Job]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-a-developer-job/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-a-developer-job/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T17:58:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The demand for skilled software developers continues to grow. However, for many self-taught developers, the path to securing a job in this competitive field can seem daunting. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that is designed to guide aspiring software engineers through the job-hunting process. Lane]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Perform CRUD Operations with Django Models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/models-in-django/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/models-in-django/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T16:10:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Django is a super useful tool for building web applications with Python. It follows the Model-View-Template (MVT) architecture, which is a popular design pattern for building web apps. In the MVT architecture, the Model refers to the internal representation of information stored, the View is responsible for processing user requests]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>chepkirui dorothy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a High-Performance Tab Component in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-high-performance-tab-component/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-high-performance-tab-component/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T16:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tabs are more than mere UI elements – they're the backbone of user navigation and content organization in many applications. In React, crafting a tabbed component that's both efficient and responsive is not just an improvement, it's a necessity. This article takes a deep dive into constructing a React tab]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaja Ibifubara David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Progressive Web Apps? PWA Guide for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-progressive-web-apps-pwa-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-progressive-web-apps-pwa-guide/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T15:56:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Progressive Web Apps (PWAs) are simply installable web applications – websites that you can install on your device, much like you would install an app from an app store.  They bring together the best parts of using a website (easy to access, no need to install anything) with the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ophy Boamah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Design and Build Sustainable Software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/design-and-build-sustainable-software/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/design-and-build-sustainable-software/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T01:28:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Electronic devices that run software are all around us. Your mobile phone, your car, your microwave, and virtually anything around you – there’s a very good chance that they have electronic components running some form of software. These devices inevitably use power and have batteries and circuits, which degrade over]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jayant Chowdhary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Validate Forms with Zod and React-Hook-Form]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-form-validation-zod-react-hook-form/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-form-validation-zod-react-hook-form/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T21:58:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forms allow you to collect user data on your websites and apps. And validation is essential to guarantee type safety and the proper format for collected data. You can perform validation on both the client and server side of the application.  This is where Zod and React-Hook-Form come in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gift Uhiene</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Complex But Awesome CSS border-image Property]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/css-border-image-property/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/css-border-image-property/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS `border-image` property is one of those properties you undoubtedly know exists but may not have ever reached for. In this article, Temani Afif demonstrates different approaches for using `border-image` to create clever decorative accents and shapes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Front-End Tools Of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/top-frontend-tools-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/top-frontend-tools-2023/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Useful front-end tools for CSS and JavaScript developers that were most popular last year and will help you speed up your development workflow. Let’s dive in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Louis Lazaris)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SolidStart: A Different Breed Of Meta-Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/solidstart-different-breed-meta-framework/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/solidstart-different-breed-meta-framework/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready for a little exercise of pulling a framework apart and putting the pieces back together? In this article, Atila Fassina explains how meta-frameworks have evolved around core libraries in their own unique ways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API And Delightful UI Animations (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/view-transitions-api-ui-animations-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/view-transitions-api-ui-animations-part2/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API is a new — but game-changing — feature that allows us to do the types of reactive state-based UI and page transitions that have traditionally been exclusive to JavaScript frameworks. In the second half of this mini two-part series, Adrian Bece expands on the demos from the first article to demonstrate how the View Transitions API can be used to transition not just elements between two states but the transition between full views and pages in single-page and multi-page applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Magic Of New Beginnings (January 2024 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2024/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s start into the new year with a little inspiration boost: wallpapers created with love by the community for the community. Happy 2024!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Sense Of “Senseless” JavaScript Features]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/making-sense-of-senseless-javascript-features/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/making-sense-of-senseless-javascript-features/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript may be the most popular client-side language in the world, but it’s far from perfect and not without its quirks. Juan Diego Rodriguez examines several “absurd” JavaScript eccentricities and explains how they made it into the language as well as how to avoid them in your own code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>