<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-08-07T00:10:38.617Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-08-07T00:10:38.617Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Accessible Text Over Images: Best Practices, Techniques, And Resources (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/designing-accessible-text-over-images-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/designing-accessible-text-over-images-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this two-part series of articles, Hannah Milan covers the best practices when using various accessible text over images techniques for designing your web and mobile app content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Hannah Milan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Perform CRUD Operations – JavaScript and SQL Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-perform-crud-operations-js-and-sql/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-perform-crud-operations-js-and-sql/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T20:41:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the most part, interactive website architectures will involve generating or dispensing data of one sort or another. You can certainly use HTML forms to collect user input. But the kind of web form that's described here [/news/creating-html-forms/] will only take you so far.  What we really need is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Dynamic Wordpress Site with Advanced Custom Fields and Custom Post Types]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-dynamic-wordpress-website/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-dynamic-wordpress-website/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T20:36:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, fellow WordPress enthusiasts! Today, I want to share with you an exciting journey I took while building Honeymoons.com [https://honeymoons.com]. It's a dynamic website that uses Advanced Custom Fields (ACF) [https://www.advancedcustomfields.com/] and Custom Post Types [https://developer.wordpress.org/plugins/post-types/registering-custom-post-types/] .  As a travel company specializing in dreamy honeymoon destinations, it was crucial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Campbell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETL vs ELT – Which Data Integration Technique Should You Choose?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/etl-vs-elt-which-data-integration-technique-should-you-choose/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/etl-vs-elt-which-data-integration-technique-should-you-choose/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T16:04:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days, organizations are collecting large volumes of data from diverse sources. And their data teams need to harness the power of that data efficiently. Both ETL (Extract, Transform, Load) and ELT (Extract, Load, Transform) pipelines play pivotal roles in integrating data from various sources into a centralized data repository.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bala Priya C</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Data Structure For Storing Non-Duplicate Items In Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-best-data-structure-for-storing-non-duplicate-items-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-best-data-structure-for-storing-non-duplicate-items-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T15:08:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're coding in Python and you need to store non-duplicate items while ensuring each item is unique, which data structure should you use?  I'd recommend the set data structure. It's an unordered collection of unique elements, meaning it cannot contain any duplicate items.  When you add elements]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Medical AI Models with TensorFlow – Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/medical-ai-models-with-tensorflow-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/medical-ai-models-with-tensorflow-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T13:20:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Machine learning is transforming many industries, including healthcare. Artificial intelligence is playing a pivotal role in saving lives and improving patient outcomes. And it is easier than you may think to start applying AI models to medical imaging. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Safe AI – Reducing Existential Risks in Machine Learning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/building-safe-ai-reducing-existential-risks-in-machine-learning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/building-safe-ai-reducing-existential-risks-in-machine-learning/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T12:38:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As technology advances at an unprecedented pace, so does the development of Machine Learning (ML) and Artificial Intelligence (AI) systems. These systems have grown exponentially in size, capability, and are now being deployed in critical and high-stakes environments. As with any powerful technology, safety becomes an important concern. We just]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Optimized Performance To Serve A Global Audience]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/optimize-performance-serve-global-audience/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/optimize-performance-serve-global-audience/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liran Cohen and the team at Bookaway, a travel booking service, dramatically improved their site’s performance by auditing Core Web Vitals. In this article, Liran shares his team’s process for auditing and monitoring Web Vitals and the effort it took to dramatically improve Bookaway’s performance — and the benefits that came with it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Liran Cohen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a WhatsApp Dictionary Chatbot using Twilio, FastAPI, and MongoDB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-whatsapp-dictionary-chatbot-using-twilio-fast-api-and-mongodb/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-whatsapp-dictionary-chatbot-using-twilio-fast-api-and-mongodb/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T23:47:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes you want to check what a word means while chatting with someone in WhatsApp. But you don't want to exit or minimize the app.  Well, how about building a WhatsApp bot that can give you the meaning of words you want to know? In this tutorial, you will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adejumo Ridwan Suleiman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp is Launching a Podcast in Chinese]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-podcast-in-chinese/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-podcast-in-chinese/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T09:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, everyone! I am Miya Liu. And I'm excited to announce the launch of the  freeCodeCamp Chinese Podcast [https://freecodecamp-in-chinese.transistor.fm/]. In this podcast, we'll bring you the inspiring learning and career development stories of developers, technical content creators, and other tech professionals We'll also share their insights into the world]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miya Liu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Got Accepted as an Author at freeCodeCamp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-i-got-accepted-as-an-author-at-freecodecamp/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-i-got-accepted-as-an-author-at-freecodecamp/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T21:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Life is full of surprises. Certain actions may lead to a chain of events and you find yourself in a completely different state.  One of my biggest achievements in 2021 was to get accepted as an author at freeCodeCamp. I have been writing articles on freeCodeCamp's community publication since]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Practical Guide to Regular Expressions – Learn RegEx with Real Life Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/practical-regex-guide-with-real-life-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/practical-regex-guide-with-real-life-examples/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T20:42:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are Regular Expressions? Regular expressions, also known as regex, work by defining patterns that you can use to search for certain characters or words inside strings. Once you define the pattern you want to use, you can make edits, delete certain characters or words, substitute one thing for another,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tasnim Ferdous</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 64 With Alvin Bryan: What Is A Headless CMS?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/smashing-podcast-episode-64/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/smashing-podcast-episode-64/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re talking about headless content management systems. What are they, and how do they differ from more traditional systems? Drew McLellan talks to Alvin Bryan to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS And Accessibility: Inclusion Through User Choice]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/css-accessibility-inclusion-user-choice/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/css-accessibility-inclusion-user-choice/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Carie Fisher outlines which CSS media features are available for detecting user preferences and how they are used to design and build more inclusive user experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carie Fisher)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Living In The Moment (August 2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T09:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New month, new wallpapers! In this post, you’ll find unique and inspiring wallpapers for August 2023. Created with love by the community for the community, they come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Define An Array Of Colors With CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/define-array-colors-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/define-array-colors-css/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join Temani Afif on experiment with modern CSS features to create an array of colors. The goal is to define a comma-separated list of colors and iterate through them using an index.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use Artificial Intelligence And Machine Learning To Summarize Chat Conversations]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/artificial-intelligence-machine-learning-summarize-chat-conversations/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/artificial-intelligence-machine-learning-summarize-chat-conversations/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll explore how to build a chat summarizer using the Cohere API and deploy it as a web application using Gradio.[ Cohere](https://cohere.com/) is an AI platform that provides state-of-the-art natural language processing models for a variety of tasks, including summarization. We’ll cover the steps involved in training the summarizer using sample chat conversations, interacting with the Cohere API to generate summaries, and creating a user-friendly interface using [Gradio](https://www.gradio.app/).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joas Pambou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern Technology And The Future Of Language Translation]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/modern-technology-future-language-translation/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/modern-technology-future-language-translation/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The field of language translation has never been more exciting. Explore the evolution of language translation platforms, how we got to where we are today, and what advancements we can look forward to in the coming years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adriano Raiano)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recreating YouTube’s Ambient Mode Glow Effect]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/recreating-youtube-ambient-mode-glow-effect/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/recreating-youtube-ambient-mode-glow-effect/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Adrian deconstructs YouTube’s “Ambient Mode” feature and how HTML `` and the `requestAnimationFrame` function are used to create the glowing effect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Art Of Looking Back: A Critical Reflection For Individual Contributors]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/critical-reflection-individual-contributors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/critical-reflection-individual-contributors/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover the importance of critical reflective practice and challenge some beliefs about reflection and its role in our work and growth. Kristian Mikhel suggests a critical reflective routine for individual contributors and gives some practical recommendations that will make reflection meaningful and actionable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kristian Mikhel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Age-Inclusive Products: Guidelines And Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/designing-age-inclusive-products-guidelines-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/designing-age-inclusive-products-guidelines-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With an estimated one in every eight individuals worldwide surpassing the age of 60, who are actively adopting online shopping, the need for user-friendly interfaces tailored to their needs becomes apparent. Explore the guidelines to help you design inclusive products for all, particularly for an older audience and your future self.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michal Halperin Ben Zvi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writing CSS In 2023: Is It Any Different Than A Few Years Ago?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/writing-css-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/writing-css-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS is evolving faster than ever. With all of the new features that are now available — and forthcoming — since we got Flexbox and Grid years ago, the way we write CSS is evolving, too. In this article, Geoff Graham shares which features have had the most influence on his current approaches to CSS, as well as those that have not (at least yet).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create A Rapid Research Program To Support Insights At Scale]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/create-rapid-research-program-support-insights-scale/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/create-rapid-research-program-support-insights-scale/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate your organization’s growth and innovation with the power of Rapid Research. From inception to implementation, here is the step-by-step roadmap on how to build the program from scratch and uncover the untapped ROI opportunities waiting to propel your initiatives to new heights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Devin Harold)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 63 With Chris Ferdinandi: What Is The Transitional Web?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/smashing-podcast-episode-63/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/smashing-podcast-episode-63/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of The Smashing Podcast, we’re talking about The Transitional Web. What is it, and how does it describe the technologies we’re using? Drew McLellan talks to Chris Ferdinandi to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Become A Better Speaker At Conferences]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/become-better-speaker-conferences/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/become-better-speaker-conferences/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Andy Budd, curator of UX London and Leading Design conferences, outlines some of the things that make a potentially amazing presentation, as well as a few big gotchas. If you’ve ever wondered what it takes to get a speaking slot at a conference, this article is for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andy Budd)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>