<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-06-06T00:10:10.360Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-06-06T00:10:10.360Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Style a React Application – Different Options Compared]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-style-a-react-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-style-a-react-app/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T21:52:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Styling plays a vital role in creating visually appealing and user-friendly web applications. When it comes to React applications, there are numerous ways to style components and UI elements.  In this article, we will explore several popular options, including pure CSS, CSS modules, CSS preprocessors, Tailwind CSS, CSS-in-JS libraries]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design Patterns for Distributed Systems – Key Concepts Every Developer Should Know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/design-patterns-for-distributed-systems/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/design-patterns-for-distributed-systems/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T20:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I first started my career as a backend engineer, I always worked with monolithic systems. The work was good but I always had this thought in the back of my mind: > "Man, I want to work on big systems such as ones for Google, Netflix, etc..." I was]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tamerlan Gudabayev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an Image Carousel Component with TypeScript and Styled-Components]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-image-carousel-component/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-image-carousel-component/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T17:28:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent years, OTT (over-the-top) video streaming platforms have become more innovative and convenient to use. In their user interfaces, movies and series titles are arranged so that the titles are clearly visible. In this tutorial, I’ll guide you through the process of creating an image carousel component that looks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keyur Paralkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Exit – How to Use an Exit Function in Python to Stop a Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-exit-how-to-use-an-exit-function-in-python-to-stop-a-program/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-exit-how-to-use-an-exit-function-in-python-to-stop-a-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T13:54:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exit() function in Python is used to exit or terminate the current running script or program. You can use it to stop the execution of the program at any point. When the exit() function is called, the program will immediately stop running and exit. The syntax of the exit()]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Primitive Objects In JavaScript: When To Use Them (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/primitive-objects-javascript-part-2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/primitive-objects-javascript-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the second part of the series, Kirill looks at the usefulness of primitive objects, exploring how reducing capabilities could be a benefit for your project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kirill Myshkin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Enable Collaboration In A Multiparty Setting]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/enable-collaboration-multiparty-setting/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/enable-collaboration-multiparty-setting/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Artificial Intelligence becomes more widespread, so too does the adoption of digital agents and voice interactions. Explore the power of mixed reality systems and multimodal communication to enhance collaboration between consultants and clients, transforming advisory services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Hannah Kühne &amp; Madlaina Kalunder)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Sheets – How to Make a Dynamic Search Bar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dynamic-search-bar-google-sheets/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dynamic-search-bar-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T13:31:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This tutorial is for when CTRL + F is not enough. 🔥 I bet I've used the CTRL + F shortcut more than any other keyboard shortcut in my life. CTRL + Z probably comes close, but I use CTRL + F to find things... 💥ALL 💥 💥💥THE 💥💥 💥💥💥TIME]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iA Presenter: A Case Study On Product Pricing Considerations]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/ia-presenter-case-study-product-pricing-considerations/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/ia-presenter-case-study-product-pricing-considerations/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pricing a product or service is one of the more challenging aspects of product development. Pricing is an inexact science, and chances are you will not get it right the first time. But where do you even begin? Let’s explore the important considerations that go into product pricing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Choose a CMS – Tips for Content Management Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-choose-a-cms/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-choose-a-cms/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T23:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're an entrepreneur or a developer, chances are you'll work with a content management systems (CMS) at some point. And knowing how to analyze the many features of the CMS options out there is important when choosing the right one for your use case. In this article, I'll explain]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Gary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build AI Apps with ChatGPT, Dall-E, and GPT-4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-ai-apps-with-chatgpt-dall-e-and-gpt-4/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-ai-apps-with-chatgpt-dall-e-and-gpt-4/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T17:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can level up your web development skills by harnessing the power of AI. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build AI apps with ChatGPT, Dall-E, and GPT-4. This course is designed to equip you with the knowledge and skills]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn to Build Graph Databases with Neo4j (Full Course)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-neo4j-database-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-neo4j-database-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T16:49:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neo4j is revolutionizing the way we handle complex relationships between data points. Its intuitive graph-based structure provides a flexible and efficient solution for various applications. We just published a Neo4j course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Whether you're a developer, a data scientist, or an aspiring technology enthusiast, this course]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LangChain Tutorial – How to Build a Custom-Knowledge Chatbot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/langchain-how-to-create-custom-knowledge-chatbots/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/langchain-how-to-create-custom-knowledge-chatbots/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T15:41:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have read about the large number of AI apps that have been released over the last couple of months. You may have even started using some of them. AI tools such as ChatPDF [https://www.chatpdf.com/] and CustomGPT AI [https://customgpt.ai/use-cases/] have become very useful to people – and for good]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shane Duggan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Data Visualization is Important for UX Design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-data-visualization-is-important-for-ux-design/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-data-visualization-is-important-for-ux-design/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T15:39:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days, we find ourselves consuming vast amounts of information, at an unprecedented rate. From online transactions, to social media interactions, to scientific research, the complexity of data grows exponentially. This reveals a challenge — how to transform this raw data to actionable insight.  This is where data visualization]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijelekhai Faith Olohijere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced Form Control Styling With Selectmenu And Anchoring API]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/advanced-form-control-styling-selectmenu-anchoring-api/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/advanced-form-control-styling-selectmenu-anchoring-api/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to the Open UI working community group, there’s a new element on the horizon, <selectmenu>, that will make styling this type of form control a whole lot better. You’re going to walk through an early implementation of this new experimental element by creating a pattern that you would never have thought possible with CSS alone — a radial selection menu.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Brecht De Ruyte)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create Your Own Path In June (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new batch of desktop wallpapers might be for you. Designed by artists and designers from across the globe, the wallpapers in this post come in versions with and without a calendar for June 2023. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing A Better Design Handoff File In Figma]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/designing-better-design-handoff-file-figma/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/designing-better-design-handoff-file-figma/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article provides practical tips for improving the handoff process between design and development in product development. The guidance covers effective communication, documentation, design details, version control, and plugin usage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ben Shih)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Success At Scale, A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/success-at-scale-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/success-at-scale-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet “Success At Scale”, our upcoming book with best-practice case studies from industry experts. Print and eBook shipping in fall 2023. Pre-order the book.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Impact Of Agile Methodologies On Code Quality]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/impact-agile-methodologies-code-quality/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/impact-agile-methodologies-code-quality/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Say goodbye to traditional workflows and embrace Agile to unlock the power of high-quality code. Discover how Agile methodologies promote simplicity, modularization, readability, and continuous improvement, resulting in faster turnaround times, more responsive development processes, and ultimately, the creation of high-quality software that meets customer needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sarah Oke Okolo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 61 With Rachel Andrew: What Is Web Platform Baseline?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/smashing-podcast-episode-61/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/smashing-podcast-episode-61/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we’re talking about Web Platform Baseline. What is it, and how can it help determine your browser support policy? Drew McLellan talks to expert Rachel Andrew to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practical Design Tips And Guidelines For Beginner Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/practical-design-tips-guidelines-beginner-designers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/practical-design-tips-guidelines-beginner-designers/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-22T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s easy for beginner designers to get overwhelmed and lose confidence when creating presentations, landing pages, app and web design mockups, and even cards. Laurent Baumann shares a few simple guidelines and practical tips to help you in such situations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Laurent Baumann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Deal With Big Tooling Upgrades In Large Organizations]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/big-tooling-upgrades-large-organizations/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/big-tooling-upgrades-large-organizations/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The process of upgrading large third-party packages in equally large organizations is rarely, if ever, as easy as running an npm update and calling it a day in this context. Joran Quinten shares valuable lessons from his team’s experiences in upgrading third-party code that affects codebases across the entire organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joran Quinten)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design Patterns Are A Better Way To Collaborate On Your Design System]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/design-patterns-collaborate-design-system/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/design-patterns-collaborate-design-system/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every company and team has to have deep collaboration between engineering and design to get the value out of a design system (and not go nuts). Building design patterns first unblock people to work in parallel, keeps people synced up, and results in reusable modules that speed up your next project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ben Clemens)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solving Media Object Float Issues With CSS Block Formatting Contexts]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/media-object-float-issues-css-block-formatting-contexts/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/media-object-float-issues-css-block-formatting-contexts/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article covers common problems using CSS floats and how to solve them using a block formatting context (BFC). Whether you are a beginner or an experienced web developer, you will learn valuable insights and practical solutions for dealing with CSS float issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Gabriel Shoyombo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Sticky Menus: UX Guidelines]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/sticky-menus-ux-guidelines/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/sticky-menus-ux-guidelines/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are sticky headers always a good idea? Best practices for designing sticky headers, with examples, UX guidelines and usability considerations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Boost Your Design Workflow With Setapp]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/boost-design-workflow-setapp/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/boost-design-workflow-setapp/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, we’ll explore efficient tools to save time and speed up your workflow. Focus on what you do best — designing high-quality work, and let these tools handle the rest!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Rachel How)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Redux Toolkit With TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/guide-redux-toolkit-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/guide-redux-toolkit-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Redux Toolkit documentation calls the library a better way to write Redux logic for React apps and a simple and efficient toolkit for Redux development. In this article, you will learn about the Redux toolkit by building an app that tracks project issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Deepak Kumar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use AI Tools To Skyrocket Your Programming Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/ai-tools-skyrocket-programming-productivity/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/ai-tools-skyrocket-programming-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rise of Artificial Intelligence (AI) in recent times has incited fear in many over losing their jobs. However, that shouldn’t be the case. On the contrary, AI is an opportunity to take your programming to the next level when used tactfully with the right knowledge, as we’ll cover today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shane Duggan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Safest Way To Hide Your API Keys When Using React]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/safest-way-hide-api-keys-react/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/safest-way-hide-api-keys-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to make sure your API keys are safe and sound when working with React? Jessica Joseph’s got you covered! She will show you the best ways to hide your API keys, from using environment variables to building your own back-end proxy server.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jessica Joseph)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>