<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-05-12T00:09:30.265Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-05-12T00:09:30.265Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Number Systems Work in Java – Decimal, Binary, Octal, and Hexadecimal Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/number-systems-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/number-systems-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T21:54:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Knowing how to work with numbers is essential in programming. Java supports four number systems that are used for various purposes – the decimal, binary, octal, and hexadecimal systems.  Understanding what these number systems are and when to use them is an important skill for any Java programmer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mikael Lassa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Merge Dictionaries – Merging Two Dicts in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-merge-dictionaries-merging-two-dicts-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-merge-dictionaries-merging-two-dicts-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T21:51:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dictionaries are one of the built-in data structures in Python. You can use them to store data in key-value pairs.  You can read about the different methods you can use to access, modify, add, and remove elements in a dictionary here [/news/python-dictionary-methods-dictionaries-in-python/].  In this article, you'll learn how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Work with Files in Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-files-in-node-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-files-in-node-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T21:16:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is a popular programming language among web developers. But when it was first released, only front end developers enjoyed all of the fun it had to offer, since you couldn't run JavaScript outside the browser. But then in 2009, the first version of Node.js was released. Node is a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwatise Okuwobi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Boost Your Design Workflow With Setapp]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/boost-design-workflow-setapp/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/boost-design-workflow-setapp/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, we’ll explore efficient tools to save time and speed up your workflow. Focus on what you do best — designing high-quality work, and let these tools handle the rest!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Rachel How)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ultimate Go Programming Video Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/go-programming-video-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/go-programming-video-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T13:53:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce a new comprehensive Go programming video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Our mission is to provide easy access to the most sought-after tech skills, and this course is our latest endeavor to fulfill that mission. Go: The Language of the Future Go, or Golang,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Difference Between AI and Machine Learning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/artificial-intelligence-vs-machine-learning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/artificial-intelligence-vs-machine-learning/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T22:37:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning are two terms that are commonly used interchangeably. But they are not the same thing. Artificial Intelligence is a field which contains a lot of sub-fields, including Machine Learning. In this article I hope to comprehensively differentiate between AI and Machine Learning. I'll explain how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Gold</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PostgreSQL and JSON – How to Use JSON Data in PostgreSQL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/postgresql-and-json-use-json-data-in-postgresql/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/postgresql-and-json-use-json-data-in-postgresql/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T20:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PostgreSQL is a powerful open-source relational database management system (RDBMS). It was initially created as a successor to the Ingres database system and was later named "PostgreSQL" (short for "Post-Ingres SQL"). PostgreSQL is known for its robustness, reliability, and scalability, making it a popular choice for large and complex database]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Faith Oyama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an Accurate Cybersecurity Risk Assessment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-accurate-cybersecurity-risk-assessment/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-accurate-cybersecurity-risk-assessment/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T19:39:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you responsible for the safety and reliability of IT infrastructure and applications? You'll absolutely need regular and accurate assessments.  Effective risk assessments are about establishing how far your organization's IT stack can be stretched before it breaks.  From a big-picture perspective, you'll need to think about how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full Stack Engineer – Career Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-stack-engineer-career-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-stack-engineer-career-guide/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T17:27:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Full-stack engineering roles have been growing in popularity over the last decade and are among the most sought-after positions in the tech job market. But what exactly are full-stack engineers? What do they do on a day-to-day basis? And how can you become a full-stack engineer yourself? In this article,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discover the Power of Functional Programming with Elixir]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/functional-programming-with-elixir/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/functional-programming-with-elixir/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T15:59:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transform your development approach and embrace the power of Elixir and functional programming with our new beginner's course. It is designed to help you build scalable, maintainable applications like never before. We just published a new course on the freeCodeCamp channel that will teach you how to build your own]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn SQL for Efficient Data Storage and Retrieval]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-sql-full-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-sql-full-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T15:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock the power of data with SQL! Master one of the most in-demand skill in the data-driven world and supercharge your career with our new video course. We just released a comprehensive video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will take you on a journey from understanding the basics]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Redux Toolkit With TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/guide-redux-toolkit-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/guide-redux-toolkit-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Redux Toolkit documentation calls the library a better way to write Redux logic for React apps and a simple and efficient toolkit for Redux development. In this article, you will learn about the Redux toolkit by building an app that tracks project issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Deepak Kumar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use AI Tools To Skyrocket Your Programming Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/ai-tools-skyrocket-programming-productivity/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/ai-tools-skyrocket-programming-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rise of Artificial Intelligence (AI) in recent times has incited fear in many over losing their jobs. However, that shouldn’t be the case. On the contrary, AI is an opportunity to take your programming to the next level when used tactfully with the right knowledge, as we’ll cover today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shane Duggan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Safest Way To Hide Your API Keys When Using React]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/safest-way-hide-api-keys-react/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/safest-way-hide-api-keys-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to make sure your API keys are safe and sound when working with React? Jessica Joseph’s got you covered! She will show you the best ways to hide your API keys, from using environment variables to building your own back-end proxy server.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jessica Joseph)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning JavaScript With Imagination]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/learning-javascript-with-imagination/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/learning-javascript-with-imagination/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the story of how one little octopus, explaining one beginner’s concept, carried such weight and power for Kylo that it drove his work and led him to research something that is really quite silly. And yet, it transformed how he learned to write — and finally understand — JavaScript.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kylo Robinson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Growing Need For Effective Password Management]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/effective-password-management/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/effective-password-management/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Highlighting the advantages of self-hosted solutions over cloud-based alternatives and exploring collaborative password management and more, P demonstrates how to organize convenient and secure password management in a company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iliya Garakh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 60 With Mei Zhang: How Do You Design A Design Process?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/smashing-podcast-episode-60/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/smashing-podcast-episode-60/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re talking about the process of design. How do you build a process to enable your best work? Vitaly Friedman talks to designer Mei Zhang to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make Your May Magnificent (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-30T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May is almost here, so what better occasion could there be for some fresh and inspiring desktop and mobile wallpapers? Created with love by artists and designers from across the globe, the wallpapers in this post come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Write Better CSS By Borrowing Ideas From JavaScript Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/write-better-css-borrow-ideas-javascript-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/write-better-css-borrow-ideas-javascript-functions/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many problems with website layouts happen when we don’t write CSS with the same care we’d use when writing a JavaScript function. Let’s look at how we can borrow best practices and ideas from writing good JavaScript functions for writing CSS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yaphi Berhanu)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible Target Sizes Cheatsheet]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/accessible-tap-target-sizes-rage-taps-clicks/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/accessible-tap-target-sizes-rage-taps-clicks/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Practical guidelines to prevent rage taps and rage clicks with accessible tap targets for icons, links and buttons — on desktop and on mobile. With useful techniques and guidelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Potentially Dangerous Non-Accessibility Of Cookie Notices]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/potentially-dangerous-non-accessibility-cookie-notices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/potentially-dangerous-non-accessibility-cookie-notices/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this piece, a Web Content Accessibility Guidelines (WCAG) auditor shares some cookie banner error patterns that can massively hurt a page’s overall conformance. Let’s explore what to look out for with this omnipresent piece of the web interface.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Marcus Herrmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring The Potential Of Web Workers For Multithreading On The Web]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/potential-web-workers-multithreading-web/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/potential-web-workers-multithreading-web/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Sarah Oke Okolo explores the importance of Web Workers for multithreading on the web, including the limitations and considerations of using them and the strategies for mitigating potential issues associated with them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sarah Oke Okolo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building And Dockerizing A Node.js App With Stateless Architecture With Help From Kinsta]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/building-dockerizing-nodejs-app-stateless-architecture-kinsta/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/building-dockerizing-nodejs-app-stateless-architecture-kinsta/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dockerizing your Node.js apps can lead to smashing success—offering consistency, easy debugging, and hassle-free dependency management. When you host this container on Kinsta, you also benefit from high-speed performance, robust security, and top-notch scalability. By combining these two, you'll surely have a whale of a time as you sail smoothly through the development seas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tejas Kumar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Color Mechanics In UI Kits]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/color-mechanics-ui-kits/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/color-mechanics-ui-kits/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Adel Khamatov shares a model of color mechanics that he came up with during research on developing UI kits and illustrates an approach to solving related problems with best practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adel Khamatov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 59 With Chiara Aliotta: What Is Design Storytelling?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/smashing-podcast-episode-59/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/smashing-podcast-episode-59/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of The Smashing Podcast, we take a look at design storytelling. What is it, and how can it help us shape digital experiences? Vitaly talks to Chiara Aliotta to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Design Thinking?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/what-is-design-thinking/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/what-is-design-thinking/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered if things could have been done differently? But not sure how? Well, then, do not fall in love with the solution, but fall in love with the problem! Here’s an article to dive deep into how design thinking could do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Krithika Subramanian)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passkeys: What the Heck and Why?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377305</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/passkeys-what-the-heck-and-why/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T17:41:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These things called passkeys sure are making the rounds these days. They were a main attraction at W3C TPAC 2022, gained support in Safari 16, are finding their way into macOS and iOS, and are slated to …
Passkeys: What the Heck and Why? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Neal Fennimore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>