<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-04-11T00:09:50.012Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-04-11T00:09:50.012Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Currency Converter GUI with Tkinter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-currency-converter-gui-with-tkinter/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-currency-converter-gui-with-tkinter/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T16:44:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tkinter is a built-in Python library for creating graphical user interfaces (GUIs). It provides a set of tools for building windows, frames, buttons, textboxes, and other GUI elements.  It is easy to use and widely available, making it a popular choice for building GUI applications in Python. It is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unleash the Power of React Native to Build Mobile Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-native-full-course-android-ios-development/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-native-full-course-android-ios-development/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T15:37:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready to dive into the world of React Native and create stunning mobile applications that work seamlessly on both Android and iOS platforms? We've got you covered! We just published a full React Native course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel.  Emma Williams created this course. She is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Reset Hard – How to Reset to Head in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-reset-hard-how-to-reset-to-head-in-git/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-reset-hard-how-to-reset-to-head-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T12:09:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is a powerful version control system for tracking and managing changes and files in your source codes and other digital assets. One of the core functionalities of Git is "commits". Commits let you create a snapshot of your code. In other words, it’s like saving your work, but with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Data Analytics with New Advanced Certifications from Google]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/starting-and-excelling-in-data-analytics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/starting-and-excelling-in-data-analytics/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T20:47:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has been growing a list of certifications for the past few years. And they've just added some advanced coursework to the repertoire.  In this article, I'll introduce you to the Google Certifications and detail what's new. I'll focus on the Data Analytics pathway, but will include resources to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is CI/CD? Learn Continuous Integration/Continuous Deployment by Building a Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-ci-cd/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-ci-cd/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T19:31:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article you're going to learn about CI/CD (continuous integration and continuous deployment).  We're going to review what this practice is about, how it compares to the previous approach in the software development industry, and finally see a practical example of how we can implement it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Docker Compose? How to Use it with an Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-docker-compose-how-to-use-it/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-docker-compose-how-to-use-it/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T19:29:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker helps you setup a development environment on your machine quickly. It only takes a couple of minutes to go through the entire process.  But let's assume you were assigned on a project which requires at least 10 different services in a running state to run your project. For]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Fundamentals – JSX, Components, and Props Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-fundamentals/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-fundamentals/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T16:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React is a popular JavaScript library for building user interfaces. And in order to create complex and efficient web applications, you'll need to understand its fundamental concepts. In this tutorial, we will be covering three essential concepts of React – JSX, components, and props. To get started, you should be]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tanishka Makode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conda Remove Environment – How to Delete an Env]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-delete-an-environment-in-conda/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-delete-an-environment-in-conda/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T05:11:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conda is an open-source package management and environment management system that can be used to create different, isolated coding environments.  With Conda, you can create separate environments for specific projects. You can have one environment for machine learning and another environment for data analytics. Each environment can have its]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Upload Files with JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/upload-files-with-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/upload-files-with-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T20:27:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently published a tutorial showing how to upload files with HTML [https://austingil.com/uploading-files-with-html/]. That's great, but it's a bit limited to using the native browser form behavior, which causes the page to refresh. In this tutorial, I want to show you how to do the same thing with JavaScript [https://austingil.com/category/javascript/]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Austin Gil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-Dimensional Arrays in Python – Matrices Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/multi-dimensional-arrays-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/multi-dimensional-arrays-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T17:28:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-dimensional arrays, also known as matrices, are a powerful data structure in Python. They allow you to store and manipulate data in multiple dimensions or axes.  You'll commonly use these types of arrays in fields such as mathematics, statistics, and computer science to represent and process structured data, such]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluseye Jeremiah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Protect Your App With A Threat Model Based On JSONDiff]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/protect-app-threat-model-jsondiff/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/protect-app-threat-model-jsondiff/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a developer who wants to concentrate on delivering a killer application rather than worrying about countless security issues, threat model documents can help you do that. With small architectural changes, we can make these threats manageable and prevent them in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zack Grossbart &amp; Terry Yao)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Algorithms: Skills Of Designers That AI Can’t Replicate]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/skills-designers-ai-cant-replicate/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/skills-designers-ai-cant-replicate/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article highlights non-technical skills like curiosity, observation, empathy, advocacy, visual communication, and collaboration that designers routinely use in their process to make a difference through design. AI can be used to augment designers’ workflow instead of replacing people.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lyndon Cerejo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swing Into April (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With April just around the corner, we have a new collection of desktop and mobile wallpapers waiting for you to celebrate the beginning of the new month. Designed by creatives from all across the globe, the wallpapers come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Comprehensive Checklist For Running Design Workshops]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/organizing-design-workshops-checklist/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/organizing-design-workshops-checklist/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Workshops are all about people: they involve people, are conducted by people, and aim to close the gaps in people’s communication. Slava Shestopalov shares a checklist with everything you need to keep in mind when running a workshop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Slava Shestopalov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fine-Grained Access Handling And Data Management With Row-Level Security]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/access-handling-data-management-row-level-security/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/access-handling-data-management-row-level-security/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dealing with sensitive data is an important topic for any app. In this article, you will find out how to handle sensitive or confidential information in your apps and what Row-Level Security means.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Handoff Is No Handoff]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/best-handoff-is-no-handoff/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/best-handoff-is-no-handoff/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design handoffs are inefficient and painful. They cause frustration, friction and a lot of back and forth. Can we avoid them altogether? Of course we can! Let’s see how to do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overcoming The Challenges Of Content Creation For Informational Websites]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/overcoming-challenges-content-creation-informational-websites/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/overcoming-challenges-content-creation-informational-websites/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Content matters! Unfortunately, when it comes to informational websites, content quality is often poor. There is no magic answer to fix that. However, there are practical techniques you can use to improve the copy on your websites and ensure your users find the content they are looking for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Cross-Browser DevTools Features You Might Not Know]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377264</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/some-cross-browser-devtools-features-you-might-not-know/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T20:22:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I spend a lot of time in DevTools, and I’m sure you do too. Sometimes I even bounce between them, especially when I’m debugging cross-browser issues. DevTools is a lot like browsers themselves — not all of the features in …
Some Cross-Browser DevTools Features You Might Not Know originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pankaj Parashar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 58 With Debbie Levitt: What Is CX Design?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/smashing-podcast-episode-58/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/smashing-podcast-episode-58/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we ask what is Customer Experience design, and how does it differ from User Experience design? Vitaly Friedman talks to expert Debbie Levitt to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Fonts For Interface Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/free-fonts-interface-designers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/free-fonts-interface-designers/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just a few beautiful, well-crafted fonts for headings and body text that you probably haven’t spotted before. Free for personal and commercial use. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Internationalization In Next.js 13 With React Server Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/internationalization-nextjs-13-react-server-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/internationalization-nextjs-13-react-server-components/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Based on an example of a multilingual app that displays street photography images from Unsplash, Jan Amann explores next-intl to implement all internationalization needs in React Server Components and shares a technique for introducing interactivity with a minimalistic client-side footprint.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jan Amann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full Stack GraphQL With Next.js, Neo4j AuraDB And Vercel]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/full-stack-graphql-nextjs-neo4j-auradb-vercel/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/full-stack-graphql-nextjs-neo4j-auradb-vercel/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, William Lyon explores how to build a full stack GraphQL application that takes advantage of the API Routes feature of Next.js API to combine your GraphQL server and front-end React applications into a single framework.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (William Lyon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Leonardo Da Vinci Can Teach Us About Web Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/leonardo-da-vinci-teach-web-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/leonardo-da-vinci-teach-web-design/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Perhaps more than any other person in history, Leonardo da Vinci showed the kind of magic that can happen in the overlap between art and science, where much of web development lives. His methods and outlooks are just as applicable to the web today as they were in Renaissance Italy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Calendars With Accessibility and Internationalization in Mind]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376950</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/making-calendars-with-accessibility-and-internationalization-in-mind/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T13:23:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Doing a quick search here on CSS-Tricks shows just how many different ways there are to approach calendars. Some show how CSS Grid can create the layout efficiently. Some attempt to bring actual data into the mix. Some …
Making Calendars With Accessibility and Internationalization in Mind originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mads Stoumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>