<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-02-22T00:10:50.733Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-02-22T00:10:50.733Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Diff and Patch – Full Tutorial for Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-diff-and-patch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-diff-and-patch/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-21T21:42:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many of the interesting processes in Git like merging, rebasing, or even committing are based on diffs and patches. Developers work with diffs all the time, whether using Git directly or relying on the IDE's diff view. In this post, you will learn what Git diffs and patches are, their]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Rosenbaum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use SQLite with Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sqlite-python-beginners-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sqlite-python-beginners-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-21T21:41:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Databases are a crucial component in software development. After all, we need to collect data in a location where we can digitally access it for reading, writing, updating, and deleting. In this tutorial, you'll learn how to use SQLite with Python. Learning SQLite is a great way to learn how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eesa Zahed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use SQL Triggers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-triggers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-triggers/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-21T20:13:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MySQL Triggers are like JavaScript event listeners. They are not executed until an action that they have been told to listen for happens.  Here's a helpful description of them from the MySQL docs: > A trigger is a named database object that is associated with a table, and that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zubair Idris Aweda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Topic Modeling Tutorial – How to Use SVD and NMF in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/advanced-topic-modeling-how-to-use-svd-nmf-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/advanced-topic-modeling-how-to-use-svd-nmf-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-21T18:32:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the context of Natural Language Processing (NLP), topic modeling is an unsupervised learning problem whose goal is to find abstract topics in a collection of documents.  Topic Modeling answers the question: "Given a text corpus of many documents, can we find the abstract topics that the text is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bala Priya C</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML & Coding Introduction – Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-coding-introduction-course-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-coding-introduction-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-21T16:49:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you interested in coding but have never tried it before? Are you curious about how to create your own website or app? If so, then this video course is for you! We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you the basics of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Internationalization (i18n) Right With Remix And Headless CMS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/internationalization-i18n-right-remix-headless-cms-storyblok/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/internationalization-i18n-right-remix-headless-cms-storyblok/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-21T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article will show you the impact of internationalization, its fundamental logic, how to approach it with Remix, and optionally, how to manage it more conveniently using a headless CMS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani &amp; Arisa Fukuzaki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 57 With Marcin Wichary: What’s The Key To A Great Keyboard?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/smashing-podcast-episode-57/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/smashing-podcast-episode-57/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we ask what’s the key to a great keyboard? Is this essential part of our daily toolkit easily overlooked? Vitaly Friedman talks to expert Marcin Wichary to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Code Pong in Python – a Step-By-Step Tutorial with Turtle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-code-pong-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-code-pong-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-20T21:01:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pong is a classic video game that has stood the test of time. It's a crowd favorite that many among you might recognise.  For the programmers out there, coding Pong in Python is a fun and challenging way to learn the language and basic concepts of game development. But]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shane Duggan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started with MongoDB in Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mongodb-in-rust/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mongodb-in-rust/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-20T20:41:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MongoDB is a popular NoSQL database that has been gaining increasing popularity in recent years. It offers developers a flexible, scalable, and high-performance database solution, which can be used for a wide range of applications.  For Rust programmers, MongoDB provides an excellent option for storing and retrieving data in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chigozie Oduah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Test User Interactions Using the React Testing Library]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-test-user-interactions-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-test-user-interactions-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-20T19:12:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're testing different components in React, you’ll need to simulate user interactions with various parts of each component. In this tutorial, I am going to show you some methods to simulate user interactions with different interactive elements. Before getting started, make sure you know how to structure a test]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use MySQL Common Table Expressions – with Example Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mysql-common-table-expressions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mysql-common-table-expressions/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-20T17:52:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In your day to day job as a Software Engineer or Database Administrator, you'll likely have to write long complex queries, often with some subqueries.  These queries over time become less performant, difficult to read and understand, and even more difficult to manage. And no one wants to do]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zubair Idris Aweda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL SELECT Statement – How to Select Data from a Database]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-select-statement-how-to-select-data-from-a-database/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-select-statement-how-to-select-data-from-a-database/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-20T16:56:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn about the SQL SELECT statement. We'll discuss its syntax, how to use it, and how to use the SELECT statement with the WHERE clause. You will also learn how to use it with the ORDER BY clause. Introduction to the SQL SELECT Statement The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Annoh Karlgusta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keys To An Accessibility Mindset]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/keys-accessibility-mindset/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/keys-accessibility-mindset/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-20T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An accessible product can be daunting to build as there’s so much nuance and technical depth to consider. In this article, Daniel Yuschick demonstrates three keys for approaching and developing accessible content without leaving you lost in the weeds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Daniel Yuschick)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Step-By-Step Guide To Building Accessible Carousels]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/guide-building-accessible-carousels/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/guide-building-accessible-carousels/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-17T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most carousels come along with usability and accessibility issues. To avoid these issues, this article addresses step-by-step design considerations as well as semantic requirements for carousels to be accessible. It is intended to create an in-depth understanding of the implementation and its impact on users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sonja Weckenmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Putting Gears In Motion: Animating Cars With HTML And SVG]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/putting-gears-motion-animating-cars-with-html-svg/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/putting-gears-motion-animating-cars-with-html-svg/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SVG `` provides a way to define how an element moves along a motion path. In this article, Paul Scanlon shares an idea of how to use it by animating race cars in an infinite loop as easy as one-two-three!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five Steps To Design Your Product With Powerful Storytelling]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/sell-product-powerful-storytelling/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/sell-product-powerful-storytelling/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to apply powerful storytelling to design a compelling and memorable digital experience on a landing page. A case study of the [Smart Interface Design Patterns landing page](https://smart-interface-design-patterns.com/).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Chiara Aliotta)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Approach to Lazy Loading Custom Elements]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376991</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/an-approach-to-lazy-loading-custom-elements/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-13T15:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re fans of Custom Elements around here. Their design makes them particularly amenable to lazy loading, which can be a boon for performance.
Inspired by a colleague’s experiments, I recently set about writing a simple auto-loader: Whenever a custom …
An Approach to Lazy Loading Custom Elements originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frederik Dohr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Different Ways to Get CSS Gradient Shadows]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376764</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/different-ways-to-get-css-gradient-shadows/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-10T15:13:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s a question I hear asked quite often: Is it possible to create shadows from gradients instead of solid colors? There is no specific CSS property that does this (believe me, I’ve looked) and any blog post you find about …
Different Ways to Get CSS Gradient Shadows originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discovering Primitive Objects In JavaScript (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/discovering-primitive-objects-javascript-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/discovering-primitive-objects-javascript-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-10T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first part of the series, Kirill Myshkin covers some aspects of JavaScript that help bring objects closer to primitive values, which allow benefiting from common language features that aren’t usually associated with an object, like comparisons and arithmetic operators.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kirill Myshkin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Healthcare, Selling Lemons, and the Price of Developer Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377169</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/healthcare-selling-lemons-and-the-price-of-developer-experience/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T19:45:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every now and then, a one blog post is published and it spurs a reaction or response in others that are, in turn, published as blogs posts, and a theme starts to emerge. That’s what happened this past week and …
Healthcare, Selling Lemons, and the Price of Developer Experience originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moving Backgrounds]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376723</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/moving-backgrounds/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T15:03:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We often think of background images as texture or something that provides contrast for legible content — in other words, not really content. If it was content, you’d probably reach for an <img> anyway, accessibility and whatnot.
But there are …
Moving Backgrounds originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saleh Mubashar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Picture Perfect: Meet Pixo, A Photo Editor For Your End Users]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/pixo-photo-editor/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/pixo-photo-editor/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-09T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With so many image editing services available nowadays, it’s good to have one good solution that is applicable for all websites and web apps that need to provide image editing as a feature. Hristo Chakarov explains how Pixo Editor’s easy integration (just a few JavaScript lines) and rich API can save your time and improve your end users’ workflow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Hristo Chakarov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Designers Should Ask For (And Receive) High-Quality Feedback]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/designers-ask-receive-high-quality-feedback/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/designers-ask-receive-high-quality-feedback/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Andy Budd shares his way of requesting feedback: rather than sharing a linear case study that explains every design revision, the first thing to do would be to better frame the problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andy Budd)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The truth about CSS selector performance]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376659</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-truth-about-css-selector-performance/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T15:59:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Geez, leave it to Patrick Brosset to talk CSS performance in the most approachable and practical way possible. Not that CSS is always what’s gunking up the speed, or even the lowest hanging fruit when it comes to improving …
The truth about CSS selector performance originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 56 With Veerle Pieters: How Has The Design Industry Changed?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/smashing-podcast-episode-56/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/smashing-podcast-episode-56/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-07T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast we ask how has the design industry changed? Is technology making our work easier? Vitaly Friedman talks to veteran designer Veerle Pieters to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Double Emphasis Thing]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376548</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-double-emphasis-thing/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-06T15:06:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I used to have this boss who loved, loved, loved, loved to emphasize words. This was way back before we used a WYSIWYG editors and I’d have to handcode that crap.
<pI used to have this 
…
The Double Emphasis Thing originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Magazine Layout With CSS Grid Areas]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/build-magazine-layout-css-grid-areas/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/build-magazine-layout-css-grid-areas/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web development, especially what you can do with CSS, has become increasingly complex. With the added capabilities of CSS Grid, it is now possible to achieve layouts that look like they were laid out by hand. Let’s tackle a practical example of how to do something like that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jennifer Brehm)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Fancy Hover Effect For Your Avatar]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376676</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-fancy-hover-effect-for-your-avatar/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-03T15:11:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you know that kind of effect where someone’s head is poking through a circle or hole? The famous Porky Pig animation where he waves goodbye while popping out of a series of red rings is the perfect example, and …
A Fancy Hover Effect For Your Avatar originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UX Podcasts For Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/podcasts-ux-designers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/podcasts-ux-designers/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Podcasts are a fantastic opportunity to get up close with the people who know their craft. In this post, we compiled podcasts that are bound to provide valuable insights into UX and new perspectives on the field. Perfect for a short coffee break or a long commute.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Host A WordPress Site On Amazon Lightsail]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/host-wordpress-site-amazon-lightsail/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/host-wordpress-site-amazon-lightsail/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-02T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lightsail provides all the power we need to host our websites, as we are used to from AWS, but making it way easier than ever before. In this article, Leonardo Losoviz explores how to launch a WordPress site in Lightsail in a quick and easy way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caching Data in SvelteKit]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376634</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/caching-data-in-sveltekit/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T15:04:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My previous post was a broad overview of SvelteKit where we saw what a great tool it is for web development. This post will fork off what we did there and dive into every developer’s favorite topic: caching. So, …
Caching Data in SvelteKit originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Rackis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding App Directory Architecture In Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/understanding-app-directory-architecture-next-js/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/understanding-app-directory-architecture-next-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new App Directory architecture has been the main character of the recent Next.js release, which keeps bringing up many questions. In this article, Atila Fassina explores the advantages and pitfalls of this new strategy and reflects on whether you should use it in production now or not.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Magic Of February (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-february-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-february-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new batch of desktop wallpapers is for you. Designed by artists and designers from across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar for February 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How B2B Sales Help Us Understand Our Role As UX Designers Better]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/b2b-sales-understand-role-ux-designers-better/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/b2b-sales-understand-role-ux-designers-better/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-31T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Throughout a customer journey (particularly in B2B), there will be interactions that are primarily between two people rather than a human and an interface. In this article, Paul Boag explains why you cannot improve the user experience without considering the entirety of the UX journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easy SVG Customization And Animation: A Practical Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/svg-customization-animation-practical-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/svg-customization-animation-practical-guide/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-30T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers often feel discouraged from editing SVG markup and experimenting with SVG animations, thinking it’s a significant time investment or they need to use a complex animation library to do so. In this article, Adrian showcases his favorite tricks, which make the process streamlined and fun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AR, VR, and a Model for 3D in HTML]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376674</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/ar-vr-and-a-model-for-3d-in-html/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-27T14:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tucked down somewhere in the Safari Technology Preview 161 release notes is a seemingly innocous line about support for a new HTML element and attribute:
Added support for <model src> and honor <source type> attributes (257518@main)
Anytime I …
AR, VR, and a Model for 3D in HTML originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build Strong Customer Relationships For User Research]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/build-strong-customer-relationships-user-research/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/build-strong-customer-relationships-user-research/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-27T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Rachel walks you through various ways that product teams can utilize to build relationships with customers. She will share some tips and tricks from her experience that have helped her nurture customer relationships and build better products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Renaissance Rachel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating A High-Contrast Design System With CSS Custom Properties]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/creating-high-contrast-design-system-css-custom-properties/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/creating-high-contrast-design-system-css-custom-properties/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing our colors can truly help people to access our content. In this article, Brecht de Ruyte takes a deep dive into how we can create a high-contrast system while maintaining a balance between designing something accessible and respecting the look and feel of a brand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Brecht De Ruyte)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better ROI For Your Digital Products: Why Continuous Research Is Key]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/better-roi-digital-products-continous-research/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/better-roi-digital-products-continous-research/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-26T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[57% of product professionals say that product research has a positive effect on customer satisfaction. 42% agree that it affects profitability. Imagine how much more successful your product would be if you did research continuously?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Suzanne Scacca)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animating CSS Grid (How To + Examples)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376528</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/animating-css-grid-how-to-examples/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T16:05:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m pleased to shine a light on the fact that the CSS grid-template-rows and grid-template-columns properties are now animatable in all major web browsers! Well, CSS Grid has technically supported animations for a long time, as it’s baked right …
Animating CSS Grid (How To + Examples) originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Schwarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Product Reviews And Ratings UX: A Designer’s Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/product-reviews-ratings-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/product-reviews-ratings-ux/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-25T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do we design effective reviews and ratings? With a distribution chart, decimal scores, tags, recommendation score and unedited product photos.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Copying Designs Doesn’t Work, And Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/copying-designs-doesnt-work/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/copying-designs-doesnt-work/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Striking the right balance between inspiration and innovation might be hard. Let’s explore how to effectively get inspiration from others without losing that magic spark, including some do’s and don’ts along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Peter Ramsey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 55 With Tejas Kumar: Is Technology Making Us Redundant?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/smashing-podcast-episode-55/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/smashing-podcast-episode-55/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-24T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we ask whether technology is making us redundant; will we all soon be replaced with AI? Vitaly Friedman talks to Tejas Kumar to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With SvelteKit]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376610</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/getting-started-with-sveltekit/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-23T13:48:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SvelteKit is the latest of what I’d call next-gen application frameworks. It, of course, scaffolds an application for you, with the file-based routing, deployment, and server-side rendering that Next has done forever. But SvelteKit also supports nested layouts, server mutations …
Getting Started With SvelteKit originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Rackis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>