<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-12-02T00:10:26.622Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-12-02T00:10:26.622Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dijkstra's Algorithm – Explained with a Pseudocode Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dijkstras-algorithm-explained-with-a-pseudocode-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dijkstras-algorithm-explained-with-a-pseudocode-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T20:57:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use algorithms in programming to solve specific problems through a set of precise instructions or procedures. Dijkstra's algorithm is one of many graph algorithms you'll come across. It is used to find the shortest path from a fixed node to all other nodes in a graph. There are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL INSERT Statement – How to Insert Data into a Table in SQL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-insert-statement/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-insert-statement/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T18:54:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you'll learn how to use the SQL INSERT statement. We'll discuss the syntax of INSERT, and then we'll use an example to show all the different ways you can use INSERT. We'll also combine it with other helpful clauses to perform more complex operations. Prerequisites  *]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Annoh Karlgusta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digging Deeper Into Container Style Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375607</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/digging-deeper-into-container-style-queries/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T13:59:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wrote up some early thoughts on container style queries a little while back. It’s still early days. They’re already defined in the CSS Containment Module Level 1 specification (currently in Editor’s Draft status) but there’s still a couple of …
Digging Deeper Into Container Style Queries originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FabUnit: A Smart Way To Control And Synchronize Typo And Space]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/fabunit-smart-way-control-synchronize-typo-space/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/fabunit-smart-way-control-synchronize-typo-space/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’ll take a look at the Sass function that does all the work for you — with no media queries, no breakpoints, and no design jumps. In this article, Fabienne Bielmann explains what FabUnit stands for and why she decided to create her very own responsive magic formula.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Fabienne Bielmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Schedule an Email in Gmail – a Step-by-Step Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/schedule-email-in-gmail/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/schedule-email-in-gmail/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T22:23:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes you might want to compose an email but send it later. Well, did you know that Gmail allows you to schedule up to 100 emails? In this article, you will learn how to schedule your emails using Gmail. There's no need to install any software or plugins. What you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Semah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript String to Boolean – How to Parse a Boolean in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-string-to-boolean/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-string-to-boolean/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T22:14:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're manipulating data, receiving values from forms, and dealing with data in other ways, these values may take the incorrect datatype. Assume you want your value to be a boolean with either true or false, but it is stored as a string – "true" or "false." It becomes challenging]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Accessibility – Best Practices and a Checklist for Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-accessibility-best-practices-and-checklist/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-accessibility-best-practices-and-checklist/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T18:40:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The World Health Organization reports [https://www.who.int/teams/noncommunicable-diseases/sensory-functions-disability-and-rehabilitation/world-report-on-disability]  that about 15% (1.2 billion) of the world's population lives with some form of disability.  This means that as developers, our focus on making websites and applications accessible helps more people use these resources.  In this article, I'll point out barriers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ophy Boamah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Principle of Least Privilege – Definition and Meaning in Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/principle-of-lease-privilege-meaning-cybersecurity/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/principle-of-lease-privilege-meaning-cybersecurity/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T18:23:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Information technology has made a profound impact on our lives over the last three decades. It has helped us create global businesses, transform industries, and build powerful connections. But it has also led to increased risks in security and privacy. Individuals and businesses are vulnerable to cyber attacks now more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install a Wifi Adapter Driver on AML-S905X-CC (Le Potato)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-wifi-adapter-driver-on-aml-s905x-cc-le-potato/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-wifi-adapter-driver-on-aml-s905x-cc-le-potato/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T17:27:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a developer, you might be familiar with Raspberry Pi. But you might not know about the Libre Computer AML-S905X-CC – also called Le Potato.  There was a chip shortage during the pandemic that has resulted in increased Raspberry Pi prices. Other world events have also skyrocketed the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Testing Library Tutorial – How to Write Unit Tests for React Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/write-unit-tests-using-react-testing-library/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/write-unit-tests-using-react-testing-library/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T16:53:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you will learn how to confidently write unit tests using the  Testing Library [https://testing-library.com/]. It is a very popular React testing library for writing unit tests. So let's get started. What We'll Cover:  1. Why Do You Need to Write Unit Tests?  2. What]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yogesh Chavan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Search Works Under the Hood – Data Structures and Search Algorithms Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-searching-works-under-the-hood/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-searching-works-under-the-hood/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T16:33:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Searching is something people do every day. Whether they're word searching in documents and databases, or pattern matching in bioinformatics to detect anomalies in DNA, the applications for search are pretty much endless. And these applications require a lot of computation. Imagine searching for a particular DNA sequence out of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Houssein Badra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn MATLAB With This Crash Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-matlab-with-this-crash-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-matlab-with-this-crash-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T14:46:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATLAB is a programming language and software suite used for data analysis, scientific computing, and visualization that is widely used in academia and industry.  We just published a MATLAB crash course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you the fundamentals of MATLAB. Phillip Parisi developed this course.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using The New Constrained Layout In WordPress Block Themes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375278</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-the-new-constrained-layout-in-wordpress-block-themes/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T14:11:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the main goals of the WordPress Site Editor (and, yes, that is now the “official” name) is to move basic block styling from CSS to structured JSON. JSON files are machine-readable, which makes it consumable by …
Using The New Constrained Layout In WordPress Block Themes originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ganesh Dahal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Endings And New Beginnings (December 2022 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-december-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-december-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December is almost here, so why not spread some holiday love across your devices? We’ve got some beautiful wallpapers to sweeten up the last days of the year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Than “Slapping Paint on a Website”]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375190</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/more-than-slapping-paint-on-a-website/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-29T15:03:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m a sucker for anything about front-end job titles.
Anselm Hannemann:
CSS evolved and we’re beyond the point where everyone can just do it as a side interest. We all can learn it and build amazing stuff with it, 
…
More Than “Slapping Paint on a Website” originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newer Things to Know About Good Ol’ HTML Lists]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375273</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/newer-things-to-know-about-good-ol-html-lists/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-28T14:05:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML lists are boring. They don’t do much, so we don’t really think about them despite how widely used they are. And we’re still able to do the same things we’ve always done to customize them, like removing markers, reversing …
Newer Things to Know About Good Ol’ HTML Lists originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Schwarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Document Object Model (DOM) Geometry: A Beginner’s Introduction And Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/document-object-model-geometry-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/document-object-model-geometry-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, Pearl Akpan analyzes the methods and properties that make user interface solutions such as infinite scrolling, animating elements on scroll, or even the popular drag and drop achievable, and afterward, dives into some practical use cases for them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Pearl Akpan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Messages & Color Contrast]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375343</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/apple-messages-color-contrast/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T14:25:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, color me this! I was griping to myself last night about just how gosh dang hard it is to read text messages in Apple Messages. You know, not the blue bubbles that you get when messaging other iPhone users. …
Apple Messages & Color Contrast originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Developer Blog]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375599</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/wordpress-developer-blog/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T18:36:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, hey check this out. Looks like there is a brand spankin’ new blog over at WordPress.org all about WordPress development. In the original proposal for the blog, Birgit Pauli-Haak writes:
The Make Core blog has a heavy 
…
WordPress Developer Blog originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing A Vue App]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/optimizing-vue-app/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/optimizing-vue-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prioritizing performance when building our web apps improves the user experience and helps ensure they can be used by as many people as possible. In this article, Michelle Barker will walk you through some of the front-end optimization tips to keep our Vue apps as efficient as possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taming the Cascade With BEM and Modern CSS Selectors]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375144</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/taming-the-cascade-with-bem-and-modern-css-selectors/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T13:59:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BEM. Like seemingly all techniques in the world of front-end development, writing CSS in a BEM format can be polarizing. But it is – at least in my Twitter bubble – one of the better-liked CSS methodologies.
Personally, I think …
Taming the Cascade With BEM and Modern CSS Selectors originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Keyboard Accessibility: JavaScript (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/guide-keyboard-accessibility-javascript-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/guide-keyboard-accessibility-javascript-part2/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is the second of two parts about a guide to making websites accessible to keyboard users. Here Cristian Diaz covers a toolset on JavaScript that you can mix into different components to create a great experience for keyboard users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cristian Díaz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Static Noise From a Weird CSS Gradient Bug]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374993</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/making-static-noise-from-a-weird-css-gradient-bug/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T13:55:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What I will be doing here is kind of an experiment to explore tricks that leverage a bug with the way CSS gradients handle sub-pixel rendering to create a static noise effect — like you might see on a TV with no signal.
Making Static Noise From a Weird CSS Gradient Bug originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 54 With Stéphanie Walter: What Is User Journey Mapping?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/smashing-podcast-episode-54/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/smashing-podcast-episode-54/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode we’re talking about User Journey Mapping. What is it, and how does it help us build better digital products? Vitaly talks to expert Stéphanie Walter to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a Settings UI for a Custom WordPress Block]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375098</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-a-settings-ui-for-a-custom-wordpress-block/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T13:48:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So far, we’ve covered how to work with data from an external API in a custom WordPress block. We walked through the process of fetching that data for use on the front end of a WordPress site, and how to …
Creating a Settings UI for a Custom WordPress Block originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manoj Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Image Optimization On Jamstack Sites]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/guide-image-optimization-jamstack-sites/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/guide-image-optimization-jamstack-sites/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Alba Silvente shows us the theoretical and practical solutions to the most common problems when working with images and how to automate them by using a headless CMS and an image CDN.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alba Silvente)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DigitalOcean Welcomes Cloudways to the Family]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375385</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/digitalocean-welcomes-cloudways-to-the-family/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T23:38:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey folks! If you’ve been keeping up with the latest DigitalOcean news, you might be aware that we recently announced our acquisition of a company called Cloudways. In case you’re curious about what this means, we thought it might …
DigitalOcean Welcomes Cloudways to the Family originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haley Mills</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding Front-End Development Scholarships]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374792</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/finding-front-end-development-scholarships/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T14:11:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m often asked where to learn web development. The answer varies, of course, and we’ve published a few posts on the topic over the years, the most recent of which was Chris taking a stab at different learning paths in …
Finding Front-End Development Scholarships originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Automated Test Results To Improve Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/automated-test-results-improve-accessibility/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/automated-test-results-improve-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Noah Mashni and Mark Steadman share their approach to how to leverage the automated test results from the accessibility checks to drive change and reach sustainable digital accessibility transformation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Noah Mashni and Mark Steadman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the CSScenes, November 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375066</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/behind-the-csscenes-november-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T15:54:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is it Fall? Winter? I don’t know, but I woke up with snow in the front yard this morning and felt like it was time to write a little update about what’s been happening around CSS-Tricks this past month, as …
Behind the CSScenes, November 2022 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Keyboard Accessibility: HTML And CSS (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/guide-keyboard-accessibility-html-css-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/guide-keyboard-accessibility-html-css-part1/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Cristian Diaz covers how to use HTML and CSS to create an accessible experience for keyboard users while mentioning what WCAG criteria we should keep into consideration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cristian Díaz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Classy and Cool Custom CSS Scrollbars: A Showcase]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375019</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/classy-and-cool-custom-css-scrollbars-a-showcase/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T13:54:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article we will be diving into the world of scrollbars. I know, it doesn’t sound too glamorous, but trust me, a well-designed page goes hand-in-hand with a matching scrollbar. The old-fashioned chrome scrollbar just doesn’t fit in as …
Classy and Cool Custom CSS Scrollbars: A Showcase originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saleh Mubashar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Grid and Custom Shapes, Part 3]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374826</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-grid-and-custom-shapes-part-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T14:42:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Part 1 and Part 2, I am back with a third article to explore more fancy shapes. Like the previous articles, we are going to combine CSS Grid with clipping and masking to create fancy layouts for image …
CSS Grid and Custom Shapes, Part 3 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Search For A Developer Job Abroad]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/search-developer-job-abroad/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/search-developer-job-abroad/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working abroad is a popular prospect, yet many people — including professionals in the tech sphere — don’t know where to start. In this article, Andrew Stetsenko gives you an ultimate step-by-step guide to finding and making international opportunities happen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andrew Stetsenko)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design Systems: Useful Examples and Resources]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/design-systems-inspiration-resources-case-studies/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/design-systems-inspiration-resources-case-studies/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything design systems on accessibility, enterprise design systems, Figma kits, data visualization, motion design, multi-lingual design, naming, ROI calculator and UX writing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What CSS Do You Absolutely Have to Know in 2022?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374775</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/what-css-do-you-absolutely-have-to-know-in-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T13:51:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sacha Greif openly wondered whether CSS has gotten to be, you know, too big. With all the goodies that’ve shipped in browsers the past couple of years — container queries! relative color syntax! cascade layers! logical properties…
What CSS Do You Absolutely Have to Know in 2022? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New In Next.js 13?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/whats-new-nextjs-13/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/whats-new-nextjs-13/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s talk about Next.js, one of the most well-known React frameworks used for production. From new components to font optimization, Atila shares a quick overview and invites you to join his [Advanced Next.js Masterclass](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/workshops/advanced-nextjs-atila-fassina) taking place later this month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practical Steps To Build Transparency In Your Remote Business]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/practical-steps-build-transparency-remote-business/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/practical-steps-build-transparency-remote-business/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transparency is part of the fabric of many remote businesses. It doesn’t, however, come naturally to everyone, especially if you’ve only recently become remote. In this article, Siobhan takes you through some of the practical ways that you can build transparency within your organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Siobhan McKeown)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Smashing Front-End & UX Workshops]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/new-frontend-coding-ux-online-workshops/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/new-frontend-coding-ux-online-workshops/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s the state of HTML Email, Vue.js and Next.js? Would you like to level up with modern CSS? What are new, smart interface design patterns we could use? Let’s figure it all out together with our [brand new online workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) alongside our free community meetups.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing The Perfect Mobile Navigation UX]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/navigation-design-mobile-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/navigation-design-mobile-ux/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When designing navigation on mobile, we don’t have to rely on slide-in-menus or nested accordions. We can also use the curtain design pattern, and show multiple levels of navigation at once.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>