<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-03-25T00:09:41.711Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-03-25T00:09:41.711Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dataframe to CSV – How to Save Pandas Dataframes by Exporting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dataframe-to-csv-how-to-save-pandas-dataframes-by-exporting/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dataframe-to-csv-how-to-save-pandas-dataframes-by-exporting/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T18:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pandas is a widely used open-source library in Python for data manipulation and analysis. It provides a range of data structures and functions for working with data, one of which is the DataFrame.  DataFrames are a powerful tool for storing and analyzing large sets of data, but they can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Scroll Animations to a Page with JavaScript's Intersection Observer API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/scroll-animations-with-javascript-intersection-observer-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/scroll-animations-with-javascript-intersection-observer-api/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T17:42:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes, when you visit a website, you'll notice that certain elements or a particular section gets revealed dynamically as you scroll.  It's like the contents of that particular section weren't available to view until you scrolled into the section – but now, because you're there, the website decides to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mwendwa Bundi Emma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Where Contains String – Substring Query Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-where-contains-string-substring-query-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-where-contains-string-substring-query-example/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T22:36:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re working with a database, whether large or small, there might be occasions when you need to search for some entries containing strings. In this article, I’ll show you how to locate strings and substrings in MySQL and SQL Server. I‘ll be using a table I call products_data in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement Reveal on Scroll in React using the Intersection Observer API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/reveal-on-scroll-in-react-using-the-intersection-observer-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/reveal-on-scroll-in-react-using-the-intersection-observer-api/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T22:20:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking for an elegant way to reveal content on your React website as users scroll down the page? Look no further than the Intersection Observer API. In this article, you’ll learn how to implement the reveal on scroll effect in React using Intersection Observer. This will allow you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaja Ibifubara David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Remove from List – How to Remove an Item from a List in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-remove-from-list-how-to-remove-an-item-from-a-list-in-python-2/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-remove-from-list-how-to-remove-an-item-from-a-list-in-python-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T18:27:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A list in Python is a collection of items that are ordered and changeable. It is one of the most versatile and frequently used data structures in Python.  A list can contain any type of data, such as integers, strings, floats, and even other lists. In Python, lists are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Undo Git Add – How to Remove Added Files in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/undo-git-add-how-to-remove-added-files-in-git/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/undo-git-add-how-to-remove-added-files-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T18:27:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is a powerful version control and collaboration tool. It allows developers to work together seamlessly on projects. But even the most experienced developers can make mistakes while using Git, such as accidentally adding files that were not meant to be committed. This can be a problem, especially if the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overcoming The Challenges Of Content Creation For Informational Websites]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/overcoming-challenges-content-creation-informational-websites/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/overcoming-challenges-content-creation-informational-websites/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Content matters! Unfortunately, when it comes to informational websites, content quality is often poor. There is no magic answer to fix that. However, there are practical techniques you can use to improve the copy on your websites and ensure your users find the content they are looking for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a Directory in Python – How to Create a Folder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/creating-a-directory-in-python-how-to-create-a-folder/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/creating-a-directory-in-python-how-to-create-a-folder/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T13:39:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn how to create new directories (which is another name for folders) in Python. You will also learn how to create a nested directory structure. To work with directories in Python, you first need to include the os module in your project, which allows you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Vite to Speed Up Web Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/complete-vite-course-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/complete-vite-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T13:20:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vite is a powerful build tool and development server designed to speed up modern web development. We just published a full Vite course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Vite effectively and efficiently to streamline your web development workflow. Arsalan Khattak developed this course.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started in Data Analytics – A Roadmap for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-analytics-roadmap/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-analytics-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T00:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello and welcome to the world of data analysis! If you're considering a career in this field, you're in good company. Data analysis is a growing and exciting field that's becoming increasingly important in today's data-driven world. Let's face it, we're all drowning in data these days. From social media]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluseye Jeremiah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Squash Commits – Squashing the Last N Commits into One Commit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-squash-commits/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-squash-commits/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T23:16:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are working on a project and trying to implement a new feature, you might commit your code a few times to test things out. This lets you see how the code works or looks. While doing this, things might get messy because you now have several commits, even]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Cross-Browser DevTools Features You Might Not Know]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377264</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/some-cross-browser-devtools-features-you-might-not-know/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T20:22:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I spend a lot of time in DevTools, and I’m sure you do too. Sometimes I even bounce between them, especially when I’m debugging cross-browser issues. DevTools is a lot like browsers themselves — not all of the features in …
Some Cross-Browser DevTools Features You Might Not Know originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pankaj Parashar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 58 With Debbie Levitt: What Is CX Design?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/smashing-podcast-episode-58/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/smashing-podcast-episode-58/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we ask what is Customer Experience design, and how does it differ from User Experience design? Vitaly Friedman talks to expert Debbie Levitt to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Fonts For Interface Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/free-fonts-interface-designers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/free-fonts-interface-designers/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just a few beautiful, well-crafted fonts for headings and body text that you probably haven’t spotted before. Free for personal and commercial use. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Internationalization In Next.js 13 With React Server Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/internationalization-nextjs-13-react-server-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/internationalization-nextjs-13-react-server-components/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Based on an example of a multilingual app that displays street photography images from Unsplash, Jan Amann explores next-intl to implement all internationalization needs in React Server Components and shares a technique for introducing interactivity with a minimalistic client-side footprint.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jan Amann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full Stack GraphQL With Next.js, Neo4j AuraDB And Vercel]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/full-stack-graphql-nextjs-neo4j-auradb-vercel/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/full-stack-graphql-nextjs-neo4j-auradb-vercel/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, William Lyon explores how to build a full stack GraphQL application that takes advantage of the API Routes feature of Next.js API to combine your GraphQL server and front-end React applications into a single framework.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (William Lyon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Leonardo Da Vinci Can Teach Us About Web Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/leonardo-da-vinci-teach-web-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/leonardo-da-vinci-teach-web-design/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Perhaps more than any other person in history, Leonardo da Vinci showed the kind of magic that can happen in the overlap between art and science, where much of web development lives. His methods and outlooks are just as applicable to the web today as they were in Renaissance Italy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Calendars With Accessibility and Internationalization in Mind]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376950</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/making-calendars-with-accessibility-and-internationalization-in-mind/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T13:23:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Doing a quick search here on CSS-Tricks shows just how many different ways there are to approach calendars. Some show how CSS Grid can create the layout efficiently. Some attempt to bring actual data into the mix. Some …
Making Calendars With Accessibility and Internationalization in Mind originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mads Stoumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Mistakes I Made When Starting My First React Project]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377098</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/5-mistakes-starting-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T16:41:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You know what it’s like to pick up a new language or framework. Sometimes there’s great documentation to help you find your way through it. But even the best documentation doesn’t cover absolutely everything. And when you work with something …
5 Mistakes I Made When Starting My First React Project originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Oliver Bray</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Pragmatist’s Guide To Lean User Research]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/pragmatists-guide-lean-user-research/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/pragmatists-guide-lean-user-research/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Instead of telling you once again what the best practice is and adding to your imposter syndrome, let’s concentrate on some practical approaches to user research that we might be able to fit into our existing projects without being left disillusioned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Complex Forms In Vue]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/building-complex-forms-vue/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/building-complex-forms-vue/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that creating a complex form can be progressively enhanced using some Vue features like the v-for and the v-model? In this article, Olufunke shares some basic Vue core features that are super useful when building out the complex form in your day-to-day Vue usage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Olufunke Moronfolu)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a Clock with the New CSS sin() and cos() Trigonometry Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377074</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-a-clock-with-the-new-css-sin-and-cos-trigonometry-functions/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-08T14:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS trigonometry functions are here! Well, they are if you’re using the latest versions of Firefox and Safari, that is. Having this sort of mathematical power in CSS opens up a whole bunch of possibilities. In this tutorial, I thought …
Creating a Clock with the New CSS sin() and cos() Trigonometry Functions originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mads Stoumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create Dynamic Donut Charts With TailwindCSS And React]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/dynamic-donut-charts-tailwind-css-react/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/dynamic-donut-charts-tailwind-css-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Paul Scanlon shares a super lightweight approach to creating a Donut chart using conic-gradient(). There are no additional libraries to install or maintain, and there’s no heavy JavaScript that needs to be downloaded by the browser in order for them to work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why You Should Consider Graphs For Your Next GraphQL Project]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/consider-graphs-graphql-project/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/consider-graphs-graphql-project/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Adam Cowley examines the Graph behind GraphQL and demonstrates why Neo4j could be the best fit for your next project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adam Cowley)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inspiring Web Design And UX Showcases]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/inspiring-web-design-ux-showcases/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/inspiring-web-design-ux-showcases/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you sometimes feel that all websites look the same? In this post, we compiled web design showcases that prove differently. They highlight some of the finest web designs, well-crafted experiences, and delightful interactions from across the web. Inspiration is guaranteed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Fonts in WordPress Block Themes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377123</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/managing-fonts-in-wordpress-block-themes/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-06T15:26:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fonts are a defining characteristic of the design of any site. That includes WordPress themes, where it’s common for theme developers to integrate a service like Google Fonts into the WordPress Customizer settings for a “classic” PHP-based theme. That hasn’t …
Managing Fonts in WordPress Block Themes originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ganesh Dahal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How AI Technology Will Transform Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/ai-technology-transform-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/ai-technology-transform-design/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Nick and Gleb cover the current state of design, answer common questions designers have about AI tools, and share practical tips on how designers can make the most of using AI tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nick Babich &amp; Gleb Kuznetsov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything You Need to Know About the Gap After the List Marker]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376748</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/everything-you-need-to-know-about-the-gap-after-the-list-marker/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-02T18:20:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was reading “Creative List Styling” on Google’s web.dev blog and noticed something odd in one of the code examples in the ::marker section of the article. The built-in list markers are bullets, ordinal numbers, and letters. The ::marker pseudo-element …
Everything You Need to Know About the Gap After the List Marker originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Šime Vidas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moving From Vue 1 To Vue 2 To Vue 3: A Case Study Of Migrating A Headless CMS System]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/vue-case-study-migrating-headless-cms-system/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/vue-case-study-migrating-headless-cms-system/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-02T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Elisabeth Wieser-Linhart explores its potential benefits and drawbacks and shares what considerations and steps were involved in the process of migrating the front-end interface of Storyblok’s headless content management system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lisi Linhart)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daydreaming In March (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-march-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-march-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-28T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s get ready for March with some fresh wallpapers! Designed with love by the community for the community, the wallpaper designs in this collection are available in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Penpot, An Open-Source Design Platform Made For Designers And Developers Alike]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/meet-penpot-open-source-design-platform-designers-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/meet-penpot-open-source-design-platform-designers-developers/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-28T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-evolving design tools landscape, it can be difficult to keep up with the latest and greatest. In this article, we’ll take a closer look at Penpot, the first design and prototyping tool that’s fully open-source and based on open web standards, making it an ideal choice for both designers and developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Accessible Form Validation]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/guide-accessible-form-validation/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/guide-accessible-form-validation/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Each time we build a field validation from scratch, accessibility doesn’t come out of the box. In this guide, Sandrina breaks down what we need to take into consideration, so that nobody gets stuck on an inaccessible invalid field.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sandrina Pereira)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>