<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-01-09T00:11:01.058Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-01-09T00:11:01.058Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use CSS Flexbox to Break Elements Out of Their Containers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/break-out-elements-from-containers-using-flexbox/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/break-out-elements-from-containers-using-flexbox/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:15:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're building a webpage, sometimes you might want images or other elements to go beyond the boundaries of a container. So in this tutorial, I'll show you a couple ways you can accomplish this. To illustrate a situation when you might find this useful, let's say we are given]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kheoh Yee Wei</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Code with AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-code-without-being-a-coder/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-code-without-being-a-coder/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:08:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever dreamt of building your own apps but felt intimidated by the complex world of programming? Or maybe you just want to quickly enhance your coding output? We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to write code using AI. Guil Hernandez teaches]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memcached Crash Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/memcached-crash-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/memcached-crash-course/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Memcached is an important technology for back end developers to understand. It is a distributed memory caching system, primarily used to speed up web applications by reducing database load. It stores data in memory, allowing quicker access compared to traditional database-driven methods. We just published a Memcached crash course on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manage Users and Groups in Red Hat Enterprise Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/manage-users-and-groups-in-rhel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/manage-users-and-groups-in-rhel/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T17:41:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To effectively safeguard your system and regulate access when working in Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL), you'll need to understand user and group management.  This is a critical component that's significant for both individual and complex network environments, as it's key to adeptly handle user accounts and groups. In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kedar Makode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gitting Things Done – A Visual and Practical Guide to Git]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/gitting-things-done-book/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/gitting-things-done-book/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T17:12:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Git is awesome. Most software developers use Git on a daily basis. But how many truly understand Git? Do you feel like you know what's going on under the hood as you use Git to perform various tasks? For example, what happens when you use git commit? What is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Rosenbaum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SolidStart: A Different Breed Of Meta-Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/solidstart-different-breed-meta-framework/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/solidstart-different-breed-meta-framework/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready for a little exercise of pulling a framework apart and putting the pieces back together? In this article, Atila Fassina explains how meta-frameworks have evolved around core libraries in their own unique ways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn React – A Guide to the Key Concepts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-react-key-concepts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-react-key-concepts/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T01:52:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to this comprehensive guide to learning React. If you're looking for an efficient and well-thought-out approach to understanding React fundamentals, you've just hit the jackpot. This guide follows the 80/20 rule – we'll focus on a few key React concepts that you'll use in the majority of your work]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankur Tyagi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Concurrency in Kotlin Server-Side Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/concurrency-in-kotlin-server-side-development/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/concurrency-in-kotlin-server-side-development/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T23:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine you're running a bustling restaurant. Orders fly in, dishes need cooking, tables require clearing, and happy customers demand attention. How can you handle all this chaos without everything turning into a total disaster? This is where concurrency comes in. In the world of server-side development, things can get just]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Faith Oyama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React Context in Your Project – Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-context/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-context/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T20:06:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As beginners, managing state in React applications can be challenging, especially when passing and utilizing props in deeply nested components.  The usual way of passing information from a main component to its smaller parts — like a parent passing data to a child, then to a grandchild — can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benedicta Onyebuchi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Template Literals in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/template-literals-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/template-literals-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T18:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Template literals are a feature in JavaScript that were introduced with ES6. They gives you a more flexible and maintainable way of working with strings in JavaScript. By the end of this article, you will know how to use template literals. You will learn the syntax, the benefits, and some]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Semah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fine-Tune EasyOCR with a Synthetic Dataset]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fine-tune-easyocr-with-a-synthetic-dataset/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fine-tune-easyocr-with-a-synthetic-dataset/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T17:48:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OCR is a valuable tool that you can use to extract text from images. But the OCR you are using may not work as intended for your specific needs. In such situations, fine-tuning your OCR engine is the way to go.  In this tutorial, I will show you how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eivind Kjosbakken</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API And Delightful UI Animations (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/view-transitions-api-ui-animations-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/view-transitions-api-ui-animations-part2/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API is a new — but game-changing — feature that allows us to do the types of reactive state-based UI and page transitions that have traditionally been exclusive to JavaScript frameworks. In the second half of this mini two-part series, Adrian Bece expands on the demos from the first article to demonstrate how the View Transitions API can be used to transition not just elements between two states but the transition between full views and pages in single-page and multi-page applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Magic Of New Beginnings (January 2024 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2024/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s start into the new year with a little inspiration boost: wallpapers created with love by the community for the community. Happy 2024!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Sense Of “Senseless” JavaScript Features]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/making-sense-of-senseless-javascript-features/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/making-sense-of-senseless-javascript-features/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript may be the most popular client-side language in the world, but it’s far from perfect and not without its quirks. Juan Diego Rodriguez examines several “absurd” JavaScript eccentricities and explains how they made it into the language as well as how to avoid them in your own code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API And Delightful UI Animations (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/view-transitions-api-ui-animations-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/view-transitions-api-ui-animations-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API is a new — but game-changing — feature that allows us to do the types of reactive state-based UI and page transitions that have traditionally been exclusive to JavaScript frameworks. In the first part of this mini two-part series, Adrian Bece thoroughly explains why we need the API and demonstrates its basic usage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New CSS Viewport Units Do Not Solve The Classic Scrollbar Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/new-css-viewport-units-not-solve-classic-scrollbar-problem/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/new-css-viewport-units-not-solve-classic-scrollbar-problem/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the introduction of CSS viewport units in 2012, many of us have been using `width: 100vw` as a way to set an element’s width to the full width of the viewport. But, as Šime Vidas explains in this deep dive, `100vw` does not always represent the full width of the viewport due to differences in how browsers handle scrollbars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Šime Vidas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Components For Consumption, Not Complexity (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/building-components-consumption-not-complexity-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/building-components-consumption-not-complexity-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part 2 concentrates on the key points from Luis’ framework and practical tips about managing a design system that should be both robust and easy to adopt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Luis Ouriach)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Scroll Snapping Aligned With Global Page Layout: A Full-Width Slider Case Study]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/css-scroll-snapping-aligned-global-page-layout-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/css-scroll-snapping-aligned-global-page-layout-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you run into a situation where you need the padding of one element to align with the padding of another element? In this article, Brecht De Ruyte demonstrates the issue with a full-width slider component that breaks out of the main page container and shares a couple of techniques to keep it visually aligned with other elements on the page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Brecht De Ruyte)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Components For Consumption, Not Complexity (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/building-components-consumption-not-complexity-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/building-components-consumption-not-complexity-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design systems can be of immense help, but failure to adopt them invalidates the hard work that goes into building the thing in the first place! In this two-part series of articles, Luis shares his experience with design systems and how you can overcome the potential pitfalls.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Luis Ouriach)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>