<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-04-12T00:09:18.399Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-04-12T00:09:18.399Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Validate Forms in React – A Step-By-Step Tutorial for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-validate-forms-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-validate-forms-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T19:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've ever worked with form validation in React, you know that it can quickly become messy and overwhelming. This is especially the case if you're just starting out with React.  In this tutorial, I will show you how to create reusable React components that allow you to build]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yazdun Fadali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Network Architecture Basics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/network-architecture-basics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/network-architecture-basics/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T19:05:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Networking is engineering, magic, and skilled trade all rolled into one. Getting all the countless pieces to talk nicely – and reliably – to each other is complicated. Troubleshooting unexpected outages is worse.  But, once you've got it all running nicely, well that's when you should really be worried:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Design An Effective User Onboarding Flow]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/design-effective-user-onboarding-flow/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/design-effective-user-onboarding-flow/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to maximize conversions or collect necessary user information for other purposes, a user onboarding flow is necessary. In this article, you will learn how, with the help of Feathery, to design an effective user onboarding flow for your app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Suzanne Scacca)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn JavaScript Object-Oriented Programming by Building a Timer Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-javascript-object-oriented-programming/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-javascript-object-oriented-programming/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T17:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn JavaScript object-oriented programming by creating a simple timer application. Object-oriented programming is an important programming paradigm. It organizes code into objects which makes it easier to manage and maintain your applications. Many articles explain in detail the benefits of object-oriented programming and how you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miya Liu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Bytes to String – How to Convert a Bytestring]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-bytes-to-string-how-to-convert-a-bytestring/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-bytes-to-string-how-to-convert-a-bytestring/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T22:52:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn how to convert a bytestring. I know the word bytestring might sound technical and difficult to understand. But trust me – we will break the process down and understand everything about bytestrings before writing the Python code that converts bytes to a string. So]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Linters and Code Formatters in Your Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/using-prettier-and-jslint/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/using-prettier-and-jslint/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T22:02:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article we're going to take a look at two very useful tools we can use to make our lives easier when writing code: linting tools and code formatters. We're going to talk about what these tools are, how they work, why are they useful, and finally]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Render Lists in React using array.map()]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-render-lists-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-render-lists-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T21:39:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working with React, you will often times need to render lists of items. With the map() method, you can create new results from your current lists or even showcase all the items in your lists. In this tutorial, you will learn how to use this method to access]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mwendwa Bundi Emma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The History of Artificial Intelligence from the 1950s to Today]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-history-of-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-history-of-ai/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T21:35:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Humans have always been interested in making machines that display intelligence.  The Ancient Egyptians and Romans were awe-struck by religious statues that were manipulated by priests behind the scenes. Medieval lore is packed with tales of items which could move and talk like their human masters. And there have]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edem Gold</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Currency Converter GUI with Tkinter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-currency-converter-gui-with-tkinter/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-currency-converter-gui-with-tkinter/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T16:44:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tkinter is a built-in Python library for creating graphical user interfaces (GUIs). It provides a set of tools for building windows, frames, buttons, textboxes, and other GUI elements.  It is easy to use and widely available, making it a popular choice for building GUI applications in Python. It is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unleash the Power of React Native to Build Mobile Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-native-full-course-android-ios-development/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-native-full-course-android-ios-development/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T15:37:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready to dive into the world of React Native and create stunning mobile applications that work seamlessly on both Android and iOS platforms? We've got you covered! We just published a full React Native course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel.  Emma Williams created this course. She is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Reset Hard – How to Reset to Head in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-reset-hard-how-to-reset-to-head-in-git/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-reset-hard-how-to-reset-to-head-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T12:09:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is a powerful version control system for tracking and managing changes and files in your source codes and other digital assets. One of the core functionalities of Git is "commits". Commits let you create a snapshot of your code. In other words, it’s like saving your work, but with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Protect Your App With A Threat Model Based On JSONDiff]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/protect-app-threat-model-jsondiff/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/protect-app-threat-model-jsondiff/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a developer who wants to concentrate on delivering a killer application rather than worrying about countless security issues, threat model documents can help you do that. With small architectural changes, we can make these threats manageable and prevent them in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zack Grossbart &amp; Terry Yao)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Algorithms: Skills Of Designers That AI Can’t Replicate]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/skills-designers-ai-cant-replicate/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/skills-designers-ai-cant-replicate/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article highlights non-technical skills like curiosity, observation, empathy, advocacy, visual communication, and collaboration that designers routinely use in their process to make a difference through design. AI can be used to augment designers’ workflow instead of replacing people.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lyndon Cerejo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swing Into April (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With April just around the corner, we have a new collection of desktop and mobile wallpapers waiting for you to celebrate the beginning of the new month. Designed by creatives from all across the globe, the wallpapers come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Comprehensive Checklist For Running Design Workshops]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/organizing-design-workshops-checklist/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/organizing-design-workshops-checklist/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Workshops are all about people: they involve people, are conducted by people, and aim to close the gaps in people’s communication. Slava Shestopalov shares a checklist with everything you need to keep in mind when running a workshop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Slava Shestopalov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fine-Grained Access Handling And Data Management With Row-Level Security]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/access-handling-data-management-row-level-security/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/access-handling-data-management-row-level-security/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dealing with sensitive data is an important topic for any app. In this article, you will find out how to handle sensitive or confidential information in your apps and what Row-Level Security means.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Handoff Is No Handoff]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/best-handoff-is-no-handoff/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/best-handoff-is-no-handoff/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design handoffs are inefficient and painful. They cause frustration, friction and a lot of back and forth. Can we avoid them altogether? Of course we can! Let’s see how to do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overcoming The Challenges Of Content Creation For Informational Websites]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/overcoming-challenges-content-creation-informational-websites/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/overcoming-challenges-content-creation-informational-websites/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Content matters! Unfortunately, when it comes to informational websites, content quality is often poor. There is no magic answer to fix that. However, there are practical techniques you can use to improve the copy on your websites and ensure your users find the content they are looking for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Cross-Browser DevTools Features You Might Not Know]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377264</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/some-cross-browser-devtools-features-you-might-not-know/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T20:22:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I spend a lot of time in DevTools, and I’m sure you do too. Sometimes I even bounce between them, especially when I’m debugging cross-browser issues. DevTools is a lot like browsers themselves — not all of the features in …
Some Cross-Browser DevTools Features You Might Not Know originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pankaj Parashar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 58 With Debbie Levitt: What Is CX Design?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/smashing-podcast-episode-58/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/smashing-podcast-episode-58/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we ask what is Customer Experience design, and how does it differ from User Experience design? Vitaly Friedman talks to expert Debbie Levitt to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Fonts For Interface Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/free-fonts-interface-designers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/free-fonts-interface-designers/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just a few beautiful, well-crafted fonts for headings and body text that you probably haven’t spotted before. Free for personal and commercial use. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Internationalization In Next.js 13 With React Server Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/internationalization-nextjs-13-react-server-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/internationalization-nextjs-13-react-server-components/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Based on an example of a multilingual app that displays street photography images from Unsplash, Jan Amann explores next-intl to implement all internationalization needs in React Server Components and shares a technique for introducing interactivity with a minimalistic client-side footprint.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jan Amann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full Stack GraphQL With Next.js, Neo4j AuraDB And Vercel]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/full-stack-graphql-nextjs-neo4j-auradb-vercel/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/full-stack-graphql-nextjs-neo4j-auradb-vercel/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, William Lyon explores how to build a full stack GraphQL application that takes advantage of the API Routes feature of Next.js API to combine your GraphQL server and front-end React applications into a single framework.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (William Lyon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Leonardo Da Vinci Can Teach Us About Web Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/leonardo-da-vinci-teach-web-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/leonardo-da-vinci-teach-web-design/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Perhaps more than any other person in history, Leonardo da Vinci showed the kind of magic that can happen in the overlap between art and science, where much of web development lives. His methods and outlooks are just as applicable to the web today as they were in Renaissance Italy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Calendars With Accessibility and Internationalization in Mind]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376950</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/making-calendars-with-accessibility-and-internationalization-in-mind/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T13:23:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Doing a quick search here on CSS-Tricks shows just how many different ways there are to approach calendars. Some show how CSS Grid can create the layout efficiently. Some attempt to bring actual data into the mix. Some …
Making Calendars With Accessibility and Internationalization in Mind originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mads Stoumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>