<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-01-16T00:10:29.223Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-01-16T00:10:29.223Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Immutability in JavaScript – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/immutability-in-javascript-with-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/immutability-in-javascript-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T23:21:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We often hear the terms: immutable and immutability. But what do they mean, and, as developers, why should we care? Immutable basically means something that cannot be changed. In programming, immutable is used to describe a value that cannot be changed after it's been set. But, most programs require creating,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deborah Kurata</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Callbacks and Higher Order Functions in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/callbacks-higher-order-functions-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/callbacks-higher-order-functions-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T18:07:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The way functions are treated and used in JavaScript is quite interesting. They are very flexible – we can assign a function as a value to a variable, return them as a value from another function, and pass them as an argument to another function. We can do all this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Franklin Okolie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Markdown in VSCode – Syntax and Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-markdown-in-vscode/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-markdown-in-vscode/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T17:46:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Markdown is a lightweight markup language for creating formatted text using a plain-text editor. It is widely used for creating README files, documentation, and other forms of text. Visual Studio Code (VSCode) is a popular source code editor that provides excellent support for Markdown, making it easy for developers, writers,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Poromon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Storage API – How to Store Data on the Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-storage-api-how-to-store-data-on-the-browser/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-storage-api-how-to-store-data-on-the-browser/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T17:43:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Web Storage API is a set of APIs exposed by the browser so that you can store data in the browser. The data stored in the Web Storage use the key/value pair format, and both data will be stored as strings. There are two types of storage introduced in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JS DOM Manipulation Best Practices – with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dom-manipulation-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dom-manipulation-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T17:41:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, you can manipulate the content of a web page using the Document Object Model (DOM). But how do you write code that is readable, easy to maintain, and not prone to performance issues?  That's what we'll cover in this article. I'll discuss some important best practices so]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Semah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Prepare for Data Analyst Job Interviews]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prepare-for-data-analyst-job-interview/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prepare-for-data-analyst-job-interview/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T17:31:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s digital world, every business and organization collects and uses data to build better products, target the right customers, improve efficiency, and even forecast future demand.  They say that data is the new oil – and now is the perfect time to enter the data analytics job market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jess Wilk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NGINX for Backend Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nginx/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nginx/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T16:46:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NGINX is a versatile and powerful open-source software used for web serving, reverse proxying, caching, load balancing, media streaming, and more. It's important to understand for backend developers. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you what you need to know about NGINX. Laith]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Magic Link Authentication with React, Flask, and Authsignal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/set-up-magic-link-authentication-with-react-flask-and-authsignal/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/set-up-magic-link-authentication-with-react-flask-and-authsignal/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T18:40:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authentication is the process of verifying the identity of a user or system. It ensures that only authorized individuals or systems can access certain resources or perform specific actions. Magic Link Authentication offers a simple yet secure way for users to log in without passwords. This tutorial will walk you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Front-End Tools Of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/top-frontend-tools-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/top-frontend-tools-2023/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Useful front-end tools for CSS and JavaScript developers that were most popular last year and will help you speed up your development workflow. Let’s dive in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Louis Lazaris)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Sliding Window Technique – Algorithm Example and Solution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sliding-window-technique/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sliding-window-technique/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T15:11:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I was practicing coding problems that focused on Data Structures and Algorithms in preparation for a job change.  During this process, I came across the Sliding Window technique. I found this algorithm to be very interesting, so I wanted to share my learnings with the community.  This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Optimize Search Queries in MongoDB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/optimize-search-queries-in-mongodb/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/optimize-search-queries-in-mongodb/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T21:12:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Searching through a database to extract relevant data can be quite cumbersome if you don't have – or know how to use – the right tools. MongoDB is a non-relational, no-SQL database that differs from relational SQL-based databases such as PostgresSQL, MySQL. These SQL-based databases use conventional rows and columns]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>oluwatobi Joshua</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SolidStart: A Different Breed Of Meta-Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/solidstart-different-breed-meta-framework/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/solidstart-different-breed-meta-framework/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready for a little exercise of pulling a framework apart and putting the pieces back together? In this article, Atila Fassina explains how meta-frameworks have evolved around core libraries in their own unique ways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API And Delightful UI Animations (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/view-transitions-api-ui-animations-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/view-transitions-api-ui-animations-part2/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API is a new — but game-changing — feature that allows us to do the types of reactive state-based UI and page transitions that have traditionally been exclusive to JavaScript frameworks. In the second half of this mini two-part series, Adrian Bece expands on the demos from the first article to demonstrate how the View Transitions API can be used to transition not just elements between two states but the transition between full views and pages in single-page and multi-page applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Magic Of New Beginnings (January 2024 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2024/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s start into the new year with a little inspiration boost: wallpapers created with love by the community for the community. Happy 2024!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Sense Of “Senseless” JavaScript Features]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/making-sense-of-senseless-javascript-features/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/making-sense-of-senseless-javascript-features/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript may be the most popular client-side language in the world, but it’s far from perfect and not without its quirks. Juan Diego Rodriguez examines several “absurd” JavaScript eccentricities and explains how they made it into the language as well as how to avoid them in your own code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API And Delightful UI Animations (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/view-transitions-api-ui-animations-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/view-transitions-api-ui-animations-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API is a new — but game-changing — feature that allows us to do the types of reactive state-based UI and page transitions that have traditionally been exclusive to JavaScript frameworks. In the first part of this mini two-part series, Adrian Bece thoroughly explains why we need the API and demonstrates its basic usage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New CSS Viewport Units Do Not Solve The Classic Scrollbar Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/new-css-viewport-units-not-solve-classic-scrollbar-problem/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/new-css-viewport-units-not-solve-classic-scrollbar-problem/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the introduction of CSS viewport units in 2012, many of us have been using `width: 100vw` as a way to set an element’s width to the full width of the viewport. But, as Šime Vidas explains in this deep dive, `100vw` does not always represent the full width of the viewport due to differences in how browsers handle scrollbars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Šime Vidas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Components For Consumption, Not Complexity (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/building-components-consumption-not-complexity-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/building-components-consumption-not-complexity-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part 2 concentrates on the key points from Luis’ framework and practical tips about managing a design system that should be both robust and easy to adopt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Luis Ouriach)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>