<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-05-25T00:10:04.862Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-05-25T00:10:04.862Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Sheets – How to Automatically Post Events to Google Calendar with Apps Script]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-sheets-automatically-post-events-to-google-calendar-with-apps-script/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-sheets-automatically-post-events-to-google-calendar-with-apps-script/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-24T21:44:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article we'll link two Google services -> Google Sheets and Google Calendar. By using a very short custom function in Google Apps Script, we can add a list of events from a Google Sheet to a Google Calendar. 🤯 And we'll even have it email our guests as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Security Analysts Can Use Artificial Intelligence (AI) in Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-artificial-intelligence-in-cybersecurity/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-artificial-intelligence-in-cybersecurity/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-24T20:58:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI) has been a game-changer in cybersecurity. It has revolutionized the approach to cybersecurity by providing advanced techniques to detect and mitigate cyber threats.  The use of AI in cybersecurity is increasing rapidly, with many companies adopting it as a key tool in their cybersecurity strategy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonya Moisset</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Responsive Navigation Bar with a Dropdown Menu using JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-responsive-navigation-bar-with-dropdown-menu-using-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-responsive-navigation-bar-with-dropdown-menu-using-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-24T20:52:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Navigation bars are essential components used a lot in websites and web apps. As a web developer, you will need to be able to customize them, either for a client project or a basic portfolio site. In this guide, you'll learn how to build a navigation bas for yourself from]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Eke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Django to Code a ChatGPT Clone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-django-to-code-a-chatgpt-clone/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-django-to-code-a-chatgpt-clone/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-24T18:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating an AI chatbot might seem like a daunting task, especially if you're not an experienced programmer. But we just launched a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will demystify the process and walk you through it step-by-step. This course focuses on using Django, a high-level Python web framework,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[120 Free Online Math Courses from the World’s Top Universities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/math-online-courses-from-worlds-top-universities/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/math-online-courses-from-worlds-top-universities/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T22:12:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I compiled 120 free online courses offered by the 60 best universities in the world for studying math in 2023. I did so by combining popular university rankings to identify the best institutions, and then I used the Class Central database [https://www.classcentral.com/subjects] to find all their math]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manoel Cortes Mendez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Stream File Uploads to S3 Object Storage and Reduce Costs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/stream-file-uploads-to-s3-object-storage-and-reduce-costs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/stream-file-uploads-to-s3-object-storage-and-reduce-costs/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T19:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To support file uploads in your application, you will have to learn how to send files from the frontend [https://austingil.com/uploading-files-with-html/] and  receive files on the backend [https://austingil.com/file-uploads-in-node/].  This tutorial is going to take a step back and explore architectural changes that'll help you reduce costs when adding file]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Austin Gil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use RabbitMQ with NodeJS to Send and Receive Messages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-rabbitmq-with-nodejs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-rabbitmq-with-nodejs/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T14:45:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're exploring the world of distributed systems and real-time data pipelines, you've probably come across the concept of message queues.  There are a number of tools in this field, but RabbitMQ and Apache Kafka are two of the most popular. While both are robust and reliable, they have]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 61 With Rachel Andrew: What Is Web Platform Baseline?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/smashing-podcast-episode-61/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/smashing-podcast-episode-61/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we’re talking about Web Platform Baseline. What is it, and how can it help determine your browser support policy? Drew McLellan talks to expert Rachel Andrew to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full-Stack Development with Next.js, TypeScript, and AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-stack-development-with-next-js-typescript-and-aws/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-stack-development-with-next-js-typescript-and-aws/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-22T18:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how create a full stack app with Next.js, TypeScript, and AWS Amplify. We just publshed a new full stack app course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Brian H. Hough, a renowned software engineer and course creator, is your guide. He'll help you build an inspirational quote generator app. You'll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Container Queries – Responsive Design Beyond the Viewport]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/container-queries-responsive-design-beyond-the-viewport/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/container-queries-responsive-design-beyond-the-viewport/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-22T16:24:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before now, making your website responsive was limited to resizing HTML elements with media queries. This was, and still is, a brilliant innovation for web development in general.  But web development has evolved with the advent of JavaScript frameworks—particularly with the use of components as building blocks in developing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Favour C. Felix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delete YouTube History – How to Delete YouTube Search and Watch Histories]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/delete-youtube-history-how-to-delete-youtube-search-and-watch-histories/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/delete-youtube-history-how-to-delete-youtube-search-and-watch-histories/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-22T14:55:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YouTube is the most popular platform for watching and discovering educational and entertainment-focused videos. But if you have a privacy concern and want to clear your YouTube history for a fresh start, deleting your YouTube search and watch histories can be an effective solution. In this article, I will guide]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practical Design Tips And Guidelines For Beginner Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/practical-design-tips-guidelines-beginner-designers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/practical-design-tips-guidelines-beginner-designers/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-22T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s easy for beginner designers to get overwhelmed and lose confidence when creating presentations, landing pages, app and web design mockups, and even cards. Laurent Baumann shares a few simple guidelines and practical tips to help you in such situations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Laurent Baumann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Deal With Big Tooling Upgrades In Large Organizations]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/big-tooling-upgrades-large-organizations/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/big-tooling-upgrades-large-organizations/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The process of upgrading large third-party packages in equally large organizations is rarely, if ever, as easy as running an npm update and calling it a day in this context. Joran Quinten shares valuable lessons from his team’s experiences in upgrading third-party code that affects codebases across the entire organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joran Quinten)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design Patterns Are A Better Way To Collaborate On Your Design System]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/design-patterns-collaborate-design-system/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/design-patterns-collaborate-design-system/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every company and team has to have deep collaboration between engineering and design to get the value out of a design system (and not go nuts). Building design patterns first unblock people to work in parallel, keeps people synced up, and results in reusable modules that speed up your next project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ben Clemens)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solving Media Object Float Issues With CSS Block Formatting Contexts]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/media-object-float-issues-css-block-formatting-contexts/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/media-object-float-issues-css-block-formatting-contexts/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article covers common problems using CSS floats and how to solve them using a block formatting context (BFC). Whether you are a beginner or an experienced web developer, you will learn valuable insights and practical solutions for dealing with CSS float issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Gabriel Shoyombo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Sticky Menus: UX Guidelines]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/sticky-menus-ux-guidelines/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/sticky-menus-ux-guidelines/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are sticky headers always a good idea? Best practices for designing sticky headers, with examples, UX guidelines and usability considerations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Boost Your Design Workflow With Setapp]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/boost-design-workflow-setapp/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/boost-design-workflow-setapp/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, we’ll explore efficient tools to save time and speed up your workflow. Focus on what you do best — designing high-quality work, and let these tools handle the rest!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Rachel How)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Redux Toolkit With TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/guide-redux-toolkit-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/guide-redux-toolkit-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Redux Toolkit documentation calls the library a better way to write Redux logic for React apps and a simple and efficient toolkit for Redux development. In this article, you will learn about the Redux toolkit by building an app that tracks project issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Deepak Kumar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use AI Tools To Skyrocket Your Programming Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/ai-tools-skyrocket-programming-productivity/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/ai-tools-skyrocket-programming-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rise of Artificial Intelligence (AI) in recent times has incited fear in many over losing their jobs. However, that shouldn’t be the case. On the contrary, AI is an opportunity to take your programming to the next level when used tactfully with the right knowledge, as we’ll cover today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shane Duggan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Safest Way To Hide Your API Keys When Using React]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/safest-way-hide-api-keys-react/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/safest-way-hide-api-keys-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to make sure your API keys are safe and sound when working with React? Jessica Joseph’s got you covered! She will show you the best ways to hide your API keys, from using environment variables to building your own back-end proxy server.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jessica Joseph)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning JavaScript With Imagination]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/learning-javascript-with-imagination/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/learning-javascript-with-imagination/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the story of how one little octopus, explaining one beginner’s concept, carried such weight and power for Kylo that it drove his work and led him to research something that is really quite silly. And yet, it transformed how he learned to write — and finally understand — JavaScript.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kylo Robinson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Growing Need For Effective Password Management]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/effective-password-management/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/effective-password-management/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Highlighting the advantages of self-hosted solutions over cloud-based alternatives and exploring collaborative password management and more, P demonstrates how to organize convenient and secure password management in a company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iliya Garakh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 60 With Mei Zhang: How Do You Design A Design Process?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/smashing-podcast-episode-60/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/smashing-podcast-episode-60/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re talking about the process of design. How do you build a process to enable your best work? Vitaly Friedman talks to designer Mei Zhang to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make Your May Magnificent (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-30T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May is almost here, so what better occasion could there be for some fresh and inspiring desktop and mobile wallpapers? Created with love by artists and designers from across the globe, the wallpapers in this post come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Write Better CSS By Borrowing Ideas From JavaScript Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/write-better-css-borrow-ideas-javascript-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/write-better-css-borrow-ideas-javascript-functions/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many problems with website layouts happen when we don’t write CSS with the same care we’d use when writing a JavaScript function. Let’s look at how we can borrow best practices and ideas from writing good JavaScript functions for writing CSS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yaphi Berhanu)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible Target Sizes Cheatsheet]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/accessible-tap-target-sizes-rage-taps-clicks/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/accessible-tap-target-sizes-rage-taps-clicks/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Practical guidelines to prevent rage taps and rage clicks with accessible tap targets for icons, links and buttons — on desktop and on mobile. With useful techniques and guidelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>