<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-10-20T00:09:49.108Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-10-20T00:09:49.108Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Your First Web Component]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-your-first-web-component/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-your-first-web-component/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T20:35:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2023, browser support for web components (also known as custom elements) is really good. There's never been a better time to start building your own custom elements. Web components, also known as custom elements, are new HTML elements that you create. These elements encapsulate some markup, style, and interactivity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Attardi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full Stack Project Tutorial – Create a Recipe App Using React, Node.js and PostgreSQL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-stack-project-create-a-recipe-app-using-react-node-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-stack-project-create-a-recipe-app-using-react-node-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T20:31:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this in-depth tutorial, we'll build a full stack recipe app from scratch, using React, Node.js, Postgres and the Spoonacular API. We'll cover features such as:  * Building an API server in Node  * Integrating securely with a 3rd party API  * Interacting with a Postgres database]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Blakely</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Animation Techniques – CSS vs JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-animation-css-vs-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-animation-css-vs-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T14:54:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hover me]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Front End Developer Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/front-end-developer-roadmap/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/front-end-developer-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T14:23:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every week we publish a lot of great content on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. New people sometimes wonder where to start and what order to watch the courses. Well, if you want to become a front end developer, this is where to start. We just released our front end developer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Handle Breaking Changes for API and Event Schemas]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-handle-breaking-changes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-handle-breaking-changes/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T14:18:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several years ago while designing APIs for an ecommerce company, I discovered the importance of API versioning. So I wrote about it in a freeCodeCamp [https://www.freecodecamp.org/news] article entitled How to Version a REST API [/news/how-to-version-a-rest-api/].  Now I find myself designing event schemas for sending messages across a distributed system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Kleier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Google Analytics to your Astro Website]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-google-analytics-to-your-astro-website/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-google-analytics-to-your-astro-website/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T18:07:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use data insights derived from your website or app to make important decisions that'll help grow your business. This information can help you improve user experience, create effective content strategies, and so on. Google Analytics is an effective tool for tracking and analyzing traffic and events on your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS Flexbox Handbook – Complete Guide with Practical Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-css-flexbox-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-css-flexbox-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T17:25:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flexbox is a useful tool for creating beautiful and responsive layouts for web pages. In this guide, you will learn everything you need to know to start using CSS Flexbox like a pro. We'll also go through loads of practice examples. This is a perfect resource for you if you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Semah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build an AI Chatbot with the MERN Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-ai-chatbot-with-the-mern-stack/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-ai-chatbot-with-the-mern-stack/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T13:30:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chatbots are being used everywhere. And an AI chatbot is a great project to help learn the MERN Stack. We just posted a new video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create an AI chatbot with the MERN Stack. This course was created by]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Animate Along A Path In CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/animate-along-path-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/animate-along-path-css/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS loaders and progress indicators are some of the most widely used examples in tutorials and documentation. In this article, Preethi demonstrates an approach using animated custom properties, a conic gradient, CSS `offset`, and emoji to create the illusion of a scooter racing along a donut track.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Preethi Sam)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Avoid Breaking Your React Application in Production]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-avoid-breaking-your-react-app-in-production/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-avoid-breaking-your-react-app-in-production/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T23:13:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that your React application that's deployed to production can crash any time because of unhandled errors? Thankfully, React Error Boundaries are here to save the day! Whenever any type of error happens during the rendering of a component or in lifecycle methods, React displays a blank page]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yogesh Chavan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Digital Products Store with Medusa and Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-digital-products-store-with-medusa-and-next-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-digital-products-store-with-medusa-and-next-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T22:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you will learn how to build an e-book online store using Medusa and Next.js. Throughout the course of the article, we will:  1. Utilize the Medusa Next.js Starter Template     [https://medusajs.com/nextjs-commerce/] along with the Digital Products     Recipe [https://docs.medusajs.com/recipes/digital-products] build]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 66 With Ethan Marcotte: What Is A Tech Union?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/smashing-podcast-episode-66/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/smashing-podcast-episode-66/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s Smashing Podcast episode, we’re talking about Tech Unions. What part can unions play in a modern tech workplace? Drew McLellan talks to Ethan Marcotte to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Headaches: Working With Media (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/gatsby-headaches-working-media-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/gatsby-headaches-working-media-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the final part of this two-part series on solving headaches when working with media files in Gatsby projects, Juan Rodriguez demonstrates strategies and techniques for handling various types of documents, including Markdown files, PDFs, and 3D models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Choose Typefaces For Fintech Products: Our Best Practices Guide (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/choose-typefaces-fintech-products-guide-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/choose-typefaces-fintech-products-guide-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-13T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fintech products are systems that are overloaded by many types of data like numerals, texts, spreadsheets, and so on. Working with these products requires the designer to pay a high level of attention and responsibility, as he becomes a provider between user and data. Daria shares her approach to digital product typography and reviews the key points to consider when choosing typefaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Daria Karpenko)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything I Know About UX Research I First Learned From Lt. Columbo]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/ux-research-learn-from-lt-columbo/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/ux-research-learn-from-lt-columbo/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working in the area of UX sometimes feels like a crime drama. Can’t believe it? Then look at these fun parallels between modern UX practices and a classical TV detective.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Slava Shestopalov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A High-Level Overview Of Large Language Model Concepts, Use Cases, And Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/overview-large-language-model-concepts-use-cases-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/overview-large-language-model-concepts-use-cases-tools/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discuss the concept of large language models (LLMs) and how they are implemented with a set of data to develop an application. Joas compares a collection of no-code and low-code apps designed to help you get a feel for not only how the concept works but also to get a sense of what types of models are available to train AI on different skill sets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joas Pambou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Headaches: Working With Media (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/gatsby-headaches-working-media-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/gatsby-headaches-working-media-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how to incorporate a variety of media formats, such as images, videos, GIFs, SVGs, and so on, in a Gatsby website. Juan Rodriguez shares what he’s learned about optimizing files for improved performance after working with different plugins and techniques.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Re-Creating The Pop-Out Hover Effect With Modern CSS (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/re-creating-pop-out-hover-effect-modern-css-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/re-creating-pop-out-hover-effect-modern-css-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Re-create a fancy hover effect where an avatar pops out of a starburst pattern for the frame on hover. The idea is to apply the concepts in a new context and gain another view of how trigonometric functions can influence the way we mask elements in CSS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Problem With WordPress Is Positioning, Not Plugins]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/problem-wordpress-positioning-not-plugins/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/problem-wordpress-positioning-not-plugins/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Geoff explores the often-overlooked divide between WordPress.org and WordPress.com, shedding light on the blurred lines between open-source ideals and commercial interests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WaterBear: Building A Free Platform For Impactful Documentaries (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/waterbear-building-free-platform-documentaries-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/waterbear-building-free-platform-documentaries-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this second article of a two-part series, Adrian shares insights about building WaterBear — his first project as a lead developer — discussing the challenges his team encountered while building it and various accessibility and performance improvements they’ve made. You’ll get a peek at the inner workings of a team striving to find its groove to systematize the work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dancing Leaves And Spooky Fellows (October 2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-october-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-october-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How about a little inspiration boost? Well, we might have something for you: desktop wallpapers created with love by artists and designers from across the globe. They are available in versions with and without a calendar for October and can be downloaded for free. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Re-Creating The Pop-Out Hover Effect With Modern CSS (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/re-creating-pop-out-hover-effect-css-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/re-creating-pop-out-hover-effect-css-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is all about experimenting with modern CSS features. We will combine things like CSS masks, CSS variables, trigonometric functions, `@property`, and more to create a neat hover effect that would have been extremely difficult to do even a few years ago without the latest and greatest that CSS has to offer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Enhanced Patterns In WordPress 6.3]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/exploring-enhanced-patterns-system-wordpress/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/exploring-enhanced-patterns-system-wordpress/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Ganesh Dahal explains how the features have evolved since reusable blocks were officially released in WordPress 5.0 — and how the two have converged in WordPress 6.3 to form a powerful feature capable of allowing content creators to sync content and design patterns consistently in pages and posts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ganesh Dahal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With Neon Branching]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/getting-started-with-neon-branching/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/getting-started-with-neon-branching/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Branches are a really nice (and safe) way to configure or reconfigure your database without fear of screwing up the production database. Let’s take a closer look at how branching works with [Neon](https://bit.ly/46cEgX1), and the good news is, you probably already know how it works!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 65 With Alex Older: How Do You Run A Grassroots Conference?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/smashing-podcast-episode-65/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/smashing-podcast-episode-65/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re talking about running grassroots conferences and meet-ups. What does it take to organize a small industry event for your community? Drew McLellan talks to WDC’s Alex Older to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WaterBear: Building A Free Platform For Impactful Documentaries (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/waterbear-building-free-platform-impactful-documentaries-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/waterbear-building-free-platform-impactful-documentaries-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adrian’s kicking off a two-part series, sharing his journey as a lead developer. In the process, you will learn about the lessons and insights Adrian gained at work, including the strategies that went into the technical stack of the project and what it looks like to collaborate with a team he is leading for the first time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Path To Awesome CSS Easing With The linear() Function]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/path-css-easing-linear-function/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/path-css-easing-linear-function/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the new CSS `linear()` easing function on the horizon, the possibilities of what we can do to create natural-feeling animations and transitions in the future are greatly expanded. Jhey Tompkins looks at the current state of CSS easing in this article and demonstrates what we can expect from `linear()`, including handy tools to get your hands on it today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facilitating Inclusive Online Workshops (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/facilitating-inclusive-online-workshops-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/facilitating-inclusive-online-workshops-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To help ensure the success of a workshop, Ben Shih introduces the concept of an inclusive workshop. In Part 2 of the series, you will continue to delve deeper into several key principles and guidelines that you can follow during and after the workshop to encourage an inclusive atmosphere.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ben Shih)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>