<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-02-28T00:09:46.014Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-02-28T00:09:46.014Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regular Expressions (RegEx) in JavaScript – A Handbook for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/regex-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/regex-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T20:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regular expressions, also known as regex, are powerful tools for pattern matching and text manipulation. Whether you're validating user input, extracting data from strings, or performing advanced text processing tasks, understanding regex is essential for developers. This comprehensive guide will walk you through the fundamentals of regular expressions in JavaScript,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samyak Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Render an Array of Components in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-render-array-of-components-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-render-array-of-components-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T19:18:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, I will show you how using indices to render an array of components in React can be problematic. I'll also teach you how to mitigate array rendering issues with unique ids. As always, we'll work on a real world example and solve problem I stumbled across while]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matéush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Generative AI in 30 Hours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-generative-ai-in/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-generative-ai-in/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T18:25:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-evolving landscape of artificial intelligence, staying ahead of the curve is important for both enthusiasts and professionals alike. And one of the most popular elements of AI right now is Generative AI. We just posted a comprehensive course about Generative AI on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This course,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How TypeScript Generics Work – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-typescript-generics-work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-typescript-generics-work/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T13:45:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript, with its powerful type system, offers a feature called Generics, which enables developers to write reusable and type-safe code. Generics allow you to create components that can work over a variety of types rather than a single one. This article delves into TypeScript Generics, providing thorough explanations and code]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Ternary Operator in JavaScript – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-ternary-operator-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-ternary-operator-explained/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T13:04:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tired of bulky if-else statements? JavaScript's ternary operator offers a powerful solution. This handy tool lets you condense complex conditional logic into a single line, making your code cleaner, more elegant, and efficient. In this article, we'll take a deep dive into the ternary operator, understanding its syntax and showcasing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Franklin Okolie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reporting Core Web Vitals With The Performance API]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/reporting-core-web-vitals-performance-api/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/reporting-core-web-vitals-performance-api/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Performance API is a set of standards for measuring and evaluating performance metrics with JavaScript. This article demonstrates how to use the Performance API to generate performance metrics directly in the DOM to create your own reporting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Tailwind CSS to Your React Native Expo App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tailwindcss-in-react-native-expo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tailwindcss-in-react-native-expo/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T09:22:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tailwind CSS has been quite popular in the web development world due to its utility-first approach and seamless integration.  However, when developing mobile apps with React Native, integrating Tailwind CSS may be challenging. But guess what? Not anymore. With the development of tools such as NativeWind [https://www.nativewind.dev/], React Native]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Caleb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Essential SQL Concepts for Data Analysts – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-concepts-for-data-analysts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-concepts-for-data-analysts/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T00:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the vast and ever-growing realm of data analytics, Structured Query Language [/news/what-is-sql-database-definition-for-beginners/] (SQL) serves as a fundamental building block.  While SQL's roots lie in database management, it has expanded its reach, becoming the go-to tool for data extraction, manipulation, and analysis.  Whether you're just starting your journey]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Hereth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Publish Google Docs to WordPress in an SEO-Optimized Way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/publish-google-docs-to-wordpress/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/publish-google-docs-to-wordpress/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T23:21:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress is a popular content management system (CMS) known for its flexibility and user-friendly interface. But its built-in editor is not ideal for collaborative editing. Many publishers who work with writers need collaborative writing and editing features. This is where Google Docs comes into the picture. It’s a collaborative platform,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikram Aruchamy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Geolocation API in JavaScript – with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-javascript-geolocation-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-javascript-geolocation-api/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T22:34:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Geolocation API is a standard API implemented in browsers to retrieve the location of the people who are interacting with a web application. This API enable users to send their location to a web application to enable relevant services, such as seeking a restaurant or hotel near the user.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Learn the Hard Parts of React – and Tips to Conquer Them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hard-parts-of-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hard-parts-of-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T21:07:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you started learning React, only to face bugs that made you contemplate a career in goat herding? Don't worry – we've all been there.  In this guide, you'll join me on a quest through the quirky wonders of React. I'll help you navigate the perplexing moments, ensuring you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaja Ibifubara David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Web Designer’s Accessibility Advocacy Toolkit]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/web-designer-accessibility-advocacy-toolkit/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/web-designer-accessibility-advocacy-toolkit/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital designer Yichan Wang has put together this collection of strategies and selling points to help you encourage and advocate for accessibility in your place of work, including useful scripts you can use as starting points.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yichan Wang)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vanilla JavaScript, Libraries, And The Quest For Stateful DOM Rendering]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/vanilla-javascript-libraries-quest-stateful-dom-rendering/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/vanilla-javascript-libraries-quest-stateful-dom-rendering/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s well-established that the web faces wide-ranging usability and performance issues, from user-hostile UI patterns and twisted search results to sluggish performance and battery-draining bloat. In this article, Frederik examines one small-but-significant aspect where developers take the reins: Painting pixels on the screen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederik Dohr)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Practical Guide To Designing For Colorblind People]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/designing-for-colorblindness/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/designing-for-colorblindness/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Color accessibility is more than just ticking boxes. Even with good contrast, some color palettes can make interfaces challenging for users. Here are some practical guidelines to ensure more inclusive design for colorblind people. An upcoming part of Smart Interface Design Patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile Accessibility Barriers For Assistive Technology Users]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/mobile-accessibility-barriers-assistive-technology-users/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/mobile-accessibility-barriers-assistive-technology-users/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility goes beyond making products user-friendly. It can significantly impact the quality of life for people with disabilities. Kate Kalcevich shares lessons she learned from assistive technology users — challenges and barriers they encounter on mobile devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kate Kalcevich)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Accessibility Standards Can Empower Better Chart Visual Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/accessibility-standards-empower-better-chart-visual-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/accessibility-standards-empower-better-chart-visual-design/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility for data visualization extends well beyond web standards, at least if you’re trying to create an experience that’s actually useful. This article focuses on techniques for creating useful and accessible visualizations that extend well beyond compliance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kent Eisenhuth)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Practical Guide To Designing For Children]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/practical-guide-design-children/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/practical-guide-design-children/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to design for children aged 3–12, with insights into user behavior, considerations for parents, and practical UX guidelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Draw Radar Charts In Web]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/draw-radar-charts-web/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/draw-radar-charts-web/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A radar chart — also commonly called a spider chart — is yet another way to visualize data and make connections. Radar charts are inherently geometric, making them both a perfect fit and fun to make with CSS, thanks to the `polygon()` function. Read along as Preethi Sam demonstrates the process and sprinkles it with a pinch of JavaScript to make a handy, reusable component.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Preethi Sam)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frequently Heard In My Beginning Front-End Web Development Class]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/frequently-heard-beginning-front-end-web-development-class/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/frequently-heard-beginning-front-end-web-development-class/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What could we learn from entry-level students in front-end web development? As seasoned professionals, you might think you’ve seen it all, but the truth is that the newcomers are asking the most intriguing questions and making connections that those of us who have spent years on the front end may have never considered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Development Is Getting Too Complex, And It May Be Our Fault]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/web-development-getting-too-complex/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/web-development-getting-too-complex/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An overwhelming number of frameworks and tooling available today gives the impression that web development has gotten perhaps too complex. Juan Diego Rodríguez explores if web development really is that complex and, most importantly, how we can prevent it from getting even more difficult than we already perceive it to be.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Designing For Older Adults]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/guide-designing-older-adults/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/guide-designing-older-adults/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With one billion people aged 60 or older worldwide, inclusivity is more important than ever. Learn how to create digital experiences that empower independence and competence for older adults while enhancing usability for all. An upcoming part of Smart Interface Design Patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Words Cannot Describe: Designing For AI Beyond Conversational Interfaces]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/designing-ai-beyond-conversational-interfaces/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/designing-ai-beyond-conversational-interfaces/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Artificial Intelligence evolves the computing paradigm, designers have an opportunity to craft more intuitive user interfaces. Maximillian Piras examines how the latest AI capabilities can reshape the future of human-computer interaction beyond conversation alone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Maximillian Piras)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[29 Days Of Inspiration (February 2024 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-february-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-february-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With February just around the corner, how about a little inspiration boost? We might have one for you: desktop wallpapers created with love by the community for the community. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Feature Trap: Why Feature Centricity Is Harming Your Product]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/feature-centricity-harming-product/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/feature-centricity-harming-product/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most product teams commonly adopt a feature-centric mindset, finding them convenient for brainstorming, drafting requirement documents, and integrating into backlogs and ticketing systems. In this article, Andy Budd shows how fixation with features might be holding you back and how making a few small tweaks to your process could make an entire world of difference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andy Budd)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>