<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-01-10T00:10:33.706Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-01-10T00:10:33.706Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Setup React and Tailwind CSS with Vite in a Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-tailwindcss-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-tailwindcss-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T18:49:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tailwind CSS is a popular CSS framework, and React is one of the most popular JavaScript libraries. And Tailwind CSS and React are a great combo to use if you're building a frontend project. In this article, you will learn how to setup your coding environment with Vite, install React]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Segun Ajibola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Synthetic Identity Theft and How to Protect Yourself]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/synthetic-identity-theft/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/synthetic-identity-theft/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T18:42:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s digital age, cybercriminals have no shortage of methods to steal people's identities and sensitive data. One such method is synthetic identity theft, which is becoming one of the most dangerous and common forms.  In fact, according to a figures published by Federal Reserve Bank of Boston [https://www.bostonfed.org/news-and-events/news/2022/08/synthetic-identity-fraud-is-not-a-victimless-crime-costs-billions-damages-lives.aspx]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dmitry Dragilev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS by Building the React Logo in Pure CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-react-logo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-react-logo/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T18:21:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the best ways to learn CSS is by creating something useful while you learn. I will show you how to use the following CSS concepts by creating the React logo:  * position: absolute  * vw (view width)  * transform: rotate()  * animation using keyframes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Bland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Email Verification in a Flask App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/setup-email-verification-in-flask-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/setup-email-verification-in-flask-app/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T17:56:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Email verification is a crucial aspect of creating a new user account or signing up for a service. It helps confirm that the email address provided is valid and belongs to the intended user. In this article, we will explore the process of handling email verification in Flask. The topic]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Google Like a Pro]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-google-like-a-pro/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-google-like-a-pro/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T15:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you tired of sifting through pages of irrelevant search results? Do you want to become more efficient at finding the information you need on the web? If so, this course is for you. We just published a video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Delete a File in Python – And Remove a Directory, Too]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-delete-a-file-in-python-and-remove-a-directory-too/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-delete-a-file-in-python-and-remove-a-directory-too/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T15:24:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python offers many standard utility modules which enable several functions in the applications we build. In this article, we'll learn about the modules for deleting files and directories. One of the most popular modules exposed in Python is the os module. This is one of the standard utility modules. This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iferror Function in Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/iferror-function-in-excel-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/iferror-function-in-excel-example/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T15:21:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use the IFERROR function to catch errors in Excel. Using the function's parameters, you can return a custom value when specific errors occur.  In this article, you'll learn how to use the IFERROR function to evaluate and handle errors in Excel. You can use the IFERROR function]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Styling Buttons in WordPress Block Themes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376237</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/styling-buttons-in-wordpress-block-themes/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T13:56:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A little while back, Ganesh Dahal penned a post here on CSS-Tricks responding to a tweet that asked about adding CSS box shadows on WordPress blocks and elements. There’s a lot of great stuff in there that leverages new features …
Styling Buttons in WordPress Block Themes originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fränk Klein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Authentication In Websites: A Banking Analogy]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/authentication-websites-banking-analogy/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/authentication-websites-banking-analogy/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is Eric Burel’s attempt at making the implementation of authentication less obscure. You’ll learn about tokens, authorization, CORS, credentials, HTTP headers, and such.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Burel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Post Request – How to Send an HTTP Post Request in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-post-request-how-to-send-an-http-post-request-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-post-request-how-to-send-an-http-post-request-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T23:40:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTTP requests allow your front-end application to interact successfully with a back-end server or database. One of the five popular HTTP methods for making requests and interacting with your servers is the POST method, which you can use to send data to a server. In this article, you will learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Ternary Operator – Syntax and Example Use Case]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-ternary-operator-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-ternary-operator-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T23:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many operators in JavaScript, one of which is the ternary operator. In this article, I'll explain what this operator is, and how it can be useful when building applications. I have a video version of this topic [https://youtu.be/MmwtZ0AwN9A] you can check out as well to supplement your learning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS by Building the Microsoft Logo 2 Different Ways in Pure CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-microsoft-logo-version-1/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-microsoft-logo-version-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-06T23:22:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the best ways to learn CSS is by creating something useful while you learn. In this article I will show you two ways that you can create the Microsoft logo.  What We Will Be Creating We will create the Microsoft logo in pure CSS. It will look]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Bland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Getting Data Visualization Right]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/guide-getting-data-visualization-right/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/guide-getting-data-visualization-right/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Sara Dholakia presents a guide on how to choose just the right type of data visualization, with guidelines and things to keep in mind.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sara Dholakia)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The State Of Usability In 2023 🎊]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/usability-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/usability-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-02T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That’s how people behave on the web in 2023. Some observations from real usability testing on what people do and what they don’t do on the web. From disabled copy-paste to magic link sign-in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opening The Doors To 2023 (January Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2023/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-31T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s start into the new year with a little inspiration boost: wallpapers created with love by the community for the community. Happy 2023!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fluid Typography: Predicting A Problem With Your User’s Zoom-In]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/fluid-typography-predict-problem-users-zoom-in/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/fluid-typography-predict-problem-users-zoom-in/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-30T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Ruslan Yevych will show you an easy way how to predict the appearance of a problem known as WCAG Failure Under 1.4.4 Resize Text (AA) while zooming the page. You will have a clear understanding of the possible risks of using responsive typography at the stage of development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ruslan Yevych)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thank You (2022 Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375486</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/thank-you-2022-edition/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-28T15:46:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You know, this is the time of year where Chris normally publishes a big ol’ reflection of the past year. The first one was published in 2007, the same year CSS-Tricks began, and it continued all the way through 2021…
Thank You (2022 Edition) originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Command-Line Data Manipulation]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/guide-command-line-data-manipulation-cli-miller/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/guide-command-line-data-manipulation-cli-miller/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-27T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No more random scripts in Python and JavaScript to transform CSV or JSON data. In this article, Alvin Bryan shows you how to use Miller, a small and powerful CLI tool, to do all your data processing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alvin Bryan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying CSS Logical Properties On Web Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/deploying-css-logical-properties-on-web-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/deploying-css-logical-properties-on-web-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have already heard of CSS logical properties or RTL adaptations but are still deciding whether to deploy them widely. To help raise your awareness of their possibilities, Nicolas Hoffmann shares his experience of how he and his team at Proton carried out a massive move from CSS logical props to production and how you can consider them from a different perspective in your very own projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nicolas Hoffmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022 Roundup of Web Research]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375869</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/2022-roundup-of-web-research/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T15:03:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve started making a tradition of rounding up the latest front-end research at the end of each year. We did it in 2020 and again in 2021. Reports are released throughout the year by a bunch of different companies …
2022 Roundup of Web Research originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Help choose the syntax for CSS Nesting]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376319</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/help-choose-the-syntax-for-css-nesting/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T16:04:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Nesting is making the rounds yet again. Remember earlier this year when Adam and Miriam put three syntax options up for a vote? Those results were tallied and it wasn’t even even close.
Now there’s another chance …
Help choose the syntax for CSS Nesting originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful Accessibility And Usability Examples To Help Improve Your Designs]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/useful-accessibility-usability-examples-help-improve-your-designs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/useful-accessibility-usability-examples-help-improve-your-designs/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Thomas Bohm shares strategies and methods to tackle some common graphic communication problems and gives you insights into how to improve accessibility and usability and make your designs much better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Thomas Bohm)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Playground: Running WordPress in the Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376297</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/wordpress-playground-run-in-browser/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T16:52:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being able to quickly spin up a WordPress instance has been the strength of WordPress ever since its famous “five-minute install”. Upload a few files, configure a few settings, and you’re off.
The friction of uploading files has gotten …
WordPress Playground: Running WordPress in the Browser originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taking The Stress Out Of Design System Management]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/taking-stress-out-design-system-management/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/taking-stress-out-design-system-management/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Masha goes over five tips that make it easier to manage a design system while increasing its effectiveness. This short guide is aimed at smaller teams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Masha Shaposhnikova)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Infinite 3D Sliders]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375621</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-infinite-3d-sliders/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T14:58:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this series, we’ve been making image sliders with nothing but HTML and CSS. The idea is that we can use the same markup but different CSS to get wildly different results, no matter how many images we toss …
CSS Infinite 3D Sliders originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boosting Productivity For Designers With Efficient Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/optimizing-design-workflow-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/optimizing-design-workflow-tools/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Ashish Bogawat shares some of his favorite ways how to boost productivity and do things faster, better, and probably more fun by using efficient tools and workflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ashish Bogawat)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So, you’d like to animate the display property]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375714</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/so-youd-like-to-animate-the-display-property/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T15:41:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS Working Group gave that a thumbs-up a couple weeks ago. The super-duper conceptual proposal being that we can animate or transition from, say, display: block to display: none.
It’s a bit of a brain-twister to reason …
So, you’d like to animate the display property originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Prioritize User Security When Collecting Offline Data]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/prioritize-user-security-collecting-offline-data/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/prioritize-user-security-collecting-offline-data/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Concerns over online privacy and security are nothing new. In this article, Suzanne Scacca explores how the right CSV importer can help businesses better prioritize user security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Suzanne Scacca)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Links on AI-Related Stuff]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376201</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/some-links-on-ai-related-stuff/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-14T21:34:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every so often, I find that the links I save to read later fall into natural groups or patterns that reveal common threads of interest. The past couple of weeks have produced a lot of thoughts about ChatGPT, an …
Some Links on AI-Related Stuff originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unchain My Inaccessibly-Labelled Heart]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375952</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/unchain-my-inaccessibly-labelled-heart/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-14T14:08:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Suzy Naschansky from the HTMHell Advent Calendar:
<h2 id="article1-heading"All About Dragons</h2<pI like dragons. Blah blah blah blah blah.</p<p<a id="article1-read-more" aria-labelledby="article1-read-more article1-heading"Read more</a</p
See that aria-labelledby attribute? It chains two IDs from the …
Unchain My Inaccessibly-Labelled Heart originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Holiday Snowtacular 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376229</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/holiday-snowtacular-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T23:03:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve got ourselves a real holiday treat! Join host Alex Trost from the Frontend Horse community for the Holiday Snowtacular 2022 this Friday, December 16.
There’s a lineup of 12 awesome speakers — including Chris Coyier, Cassidy Williams, Kevin …
Holiday Snowtacular 2022 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Privacy: Protect Your Users, Protect Yourself]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/understanding-privacy-protect-your-users-protect-yourself/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/understanding-privacy-protect-your-users-protect-yourself/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All of us want to create inclusive, safe, and privacy-aware digital experiences, but where to begin? Our brand new Smashing Book, “Understanding Privacy,” written by Heather Burns, can help you lay the ground for future developers, designers, and project managers to build a better web for tomorrow. [Jump to the details](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/understanding-privacy-new-smashing-book/#about-the-book) or [get the book right away](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/printed-books/understanding-privacy/).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Heather Burns)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible Front-End Patterns For Responsive Tables (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/accessible-front-end-patterns-responsive-tables-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/accessible-front-end-patterns-responsive-tables-part2/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no universal solution for making every kind of table responsive and usable on smaller screens, so we have to rely on various patterns, which Adrian explains in this two-part series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Few Times Container Size Queries Would Have Helped Me Out]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375728</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-few-times-container-size-queries-would-have-helped-me-out/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T13:53:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Container Queries are still gaining traction and many of us are getting our hands wet with them, even if it’s for little experiments or whatnot. They’ve got great, but not quite full, browser support — enough to justify using …
A Few Times Container Size Queries Would Have Helped Me Out originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Christofi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting up a screen reader testing environment on your computer]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375722</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/setting-up-a-screen-reader-testing-environment-on-your-computer/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-12T20:56:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sara Soueidan with everything you need, from what screen reading options are out there all the way to setting up virtual machines for them, installing them, and confguring keyboard options. It’s truly a one-stop reference that pulls together disparate …
Setting up a screen reader testing environment on your computer originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saving Settings for a Custom WordPress Block in the Block Editor]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375577</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/saving-settings-for-a-custom-wordpress-block-in-the-block-editor/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-12T14:06:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve accomplished a bunch of stuff in this series! We created a custom WordPress block that fetches data from an external API and renders it on the front end. Then we took that work and extended it so the data …
Saving Settings for a Custom WordPress Block in the Block Editor originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manoj Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Future Of Design: Human-Powered Or AI-Driven?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/future-design-human-powered-ai-driven/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/future-design-human-powered-ai-driven/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Keima Kai provides a brief history of AI in web design, explores its current implications for creativity, and offers suggestions for how web designers can stay ahead of the curve.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Keima Kai)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>