<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-01-11T00:10:39.779Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-01-11T00:10:39.779Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding DOM Events and JavaScript Event Listeners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dom-events-and-javascript-event-listeners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dom-events-and-javascript-event-listeners/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T20:38:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript code in the browser uses an event-driven programming pattern. What this means is that when a specific DOM event happens in the browser, a piece of code will be executed as a response to that action. In this article, I will help you see and understand how to listen]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyTorch vs TensorFlow – Which is Better for Deep Learning Projects?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pytorch-vs-tensorflow-for-deep-learning-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pytorch-vs-tensorflow-for-deep-learning-projects/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T18:46:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll look at two popular deep learning libraries — PyTorch and TensorFlow – and see how they compare. If you are getting started with deep learning, the available tools and frameworks will be overwhelming. Industry experts may recommend TensorFlow while hardcore ML engineers may prefer PyTorch. Both]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Stepper Component in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-stepper-component-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-stepper-component-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T15:28:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was working on a React project recently, and I realized that there were so many UI components that I had to build to get things done quickly. So I began to explore a lot of UI libraries like Material UI [https://mui.com] or Chakra UI [https://chakra-ui.com/]. Then I started wondering]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olabisi Olaoye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Work with Third-Party APIs in React by Building a Crypto Exchange Rate Web App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/work-with-third-party-libraries-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/work-with-third-party-libraries-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T15:24:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working with APIs is crucial to any web application. And as a frontend developer, knowing how to connect your apps with third-party APIs is an important skill to have. In this article, you'll learn how to connect your app and fetch data from a third-party API by building a crypto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chidera Humphrey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Document Object Model? DOM for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-the-dom/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-the-dom/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T15:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'm going to explain to you how the DOM works so that you have a clear picture of why JavaScript is needed to develop a web application. First, let's recap what we know about HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. How HTML, CSS, and JavaScript work When you want]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The JavaScript DOM Manipulation Handbook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-javascript-dom-manipulation-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-javascript-dom-manipulation-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T15:12:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DOM Manipulation is one of the most exciting topics to learn about in JavaScript. This is because one of JavaScript's main uses is to make web pages interactive – and the Document Object Model (DOM) plays a major role in this.  The DOM is a powerful tool that allows]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Semah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Custom CSS Animations with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-custom-css-animations/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-custom-css-animations/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T21:59:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animations are a crucial component of modern web design. They enable you to create dynamic and engaging web elements that attract more customers and drive more sales. In this article, we will discuss how to create cool custom animations using CSS. Prerequisites Before going forward with this article, make sure]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Hu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do Zsh Configuration Files Work?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-do-zsh-configuration-files-work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-do-zsh-configuration-files-work/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T20:37:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beginners often get confused when configuring Zsh shell on a Mac. Zsh shell offers four configuration files with no discernible differences. Particularly, ~/.zshrc and ~/.zprofile appear to be identical, leaving us wondering which one to use.  In this article, you'll learn the difference and a simple guideline for your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kehoe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Work with RESTful APIs in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-work-with-restful-apis-in-react-simplified-steps-and-practical-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-work-with-restful-apis-in-react-simplified-steps-and-practical-examples/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T19:09:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RESTful APIs are a crucial component in modern web development. They allow communication between different applications over the internet.  REST (which stands for Representational State Transfer) APIs operate on a stateless client-server architecture, providing a standardized way to create, read, update, and delete resources. Integrating RESTful APIs with React]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The React Roadmap for 2024 – How to Learn React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-react-roadmap-learn-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-react-roadmap-learn-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T18:57:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, I'll break down a complete roadmap that will cover all the concepts, libraries, and tools to help you become a React developer in 2024. My goal is to show you the happy path in React, navigating you away from pitfalls so you can spend your time on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SolidStart: A Different Breed Of Meta-Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/solidstart-different-breed-meta-framework/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/solidstart-different-breed-meta-framework/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready for a little exercise of pulling a framework apart and putting the pieces back together? In this article, Atila Fassina explains how meta-frameworks have evolved around core libraries in their own unique ways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API And Delightful UI Animations (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/view-transitions-api-ui-animations-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/view-transitions-api-ui-animations-part2/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API is a new — but game-changing — feature that allows us to do the types of reactive state-based UI and page transitions that have traditionally been exclusive to JavaScript frameworks. In the second half of this mini two-part series, Adrian Bece expands on the demos from the first article to demonstrate how the View Transitions API can be used to transition not just elements between two states but the transition between full views and pages in single-page and multi-page applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Magic Of New Beginnings (January 2024 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2024/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s start into the new year with a little inspiration boost: wallpapers created with love by the community for the community. Happy 2024!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Sense Of “Senseless” JavaScript Features]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/making-sense-of-senseless-javascript-features/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/making-sense-of-senseless-javascript-features/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript may be the most popular client-side language in the world, but it’s far from perfect and not without its quirks. Juan Diego Rodriguez examines several “absurd” JavaScript eccentricities and explains how they made it into the language as well as how to avoid them in your own code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API And Delightful UI Animations (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/view-transitions-api-ui-animations-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/view-transitions-api-ui-animations-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API is a new — but game-changing — feature that allows us to do the types of reactive state-based UI and page transitions that have traditionally been exclusive to JavaScript frameworks. In the first part of this mini two-part series, Adrian Bece thoroughly explains why we need the API and demonstrates its basic usage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New CSS Viewport Units Do Not Solve The Classic Scrollbar Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/new-css-viewport-units-not-solve-classic-scrollbar-problem/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/new-css-viewport-units-not-solve-classic-scrollbar-problem/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the introduction of CSS viewport units in 2012, many of us have been using `width: 100vw` as a way to set an element’s width to the full width of the viewport. But, as Šime Vidas explains in this deep dive, `100vw` does not always represent the full width of the viewport due to differences in how browsers handle scrollbars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Šime Vidas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Components For Consumption, Not Complexity (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/building-components-consumption-not-complexity-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/building-components-consumption-not-complexity-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part 2 concentrates on the key points from Luis’ framework and practical tips about managing a design system that should be both robust and easy to adopt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Luis Ouriach)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Scroll Snapping Aligned With Global Page Layout: A Full-Width Slider Case Study]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/css-scroll-snapping-aligned-global-page-layout-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/css-scroll-snapping-aligned-global-page-layout-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you run into a situation where you need the padding of one element to align with the padding of another element? In this article, Brecht De Ruyte demonstrates the issue with a full-width slider component that breaks out of the main page container and shares a couple of techniques to keep it visually aligned with other elements on the page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Brecht De Ruyte)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>