<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-03-06T00:10:11.684Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-03-06T00:10:11.684Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn Audio to Text using OpenAI Whisper]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-turn-audio-to-text-using-openai-whisper/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-turn-audio-to-text-using-openai-whisper/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T13:02:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you know what OpenAI Whisper is? It’s the latest AI model from OpenAI that helps you to automatically convert speech to text. Transforming audio into text is now simpler and more accurate, thanks to OpenAI’s Whisper. This article will guide you through using Whisper to convert spoken words into]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Ensure Open Source License Compliance in Your Business]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ensure-open-source-license-compliance-in-business/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ensure-open-source-license-compliance-in-business/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T11:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're using open source code in your operations, you'll want to manage things properly or potentially face legal issues, financial penalties, and damage to your reputation.  You don't need a law degree to avoid problems, but you should definitely familiarize yourself with some basic principles. This article comes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Microsoft Fabric? How to Build a Customer Segmentation Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-microsoft-fabric/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-microsoft-fabric/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T01:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Fabric is a data analytics tool that can help you streamline all your data needs and workflows, from data integration to analytics and engineering. In this guide, I'll explain what Microsoft Fabric is in more detail, how it works, and walk you through building a project with it. If]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benny Ifeanyi Iheagwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn C# Programming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-c-sharp-programming/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-c-sharp-programming/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T17:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[C# is a popular programming language used for developing a wide array of applications, including web, mobile, desktop, and gaming applications, providing a robust platform for developers to build dynamic and scalable solutions across various industries. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Solve the Producer-Consumer Problem in Java using Multithreading]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-multithreading-producer-consumer-problem/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-multithreading-producer-consumer-problem/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T17:48:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Concurrency is an important part of Java applications. Each application has multiple processes running at the same time. This helps utilize resources efficiently and improve performance. Multithreading is a method of achieving concurrency. It uses the concept of threads – lightweight processes – to execute multiple tasks in parallel. A]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practice Your Coding Skills by Building a Program in Different Ways]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/practice-coding-skills-by-building-a-program-different-ways/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/practice-coding-skills-by-building-a-program-different-ways/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T15:39:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While we have 365 days in other years, this year (2024) is special because it has one ‘extra’ day.  So in the spirit of Leap Day, let's practice some coding to understand various aspects of programming. We'll focus on the same program but from different perspectives.  Our example]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niladri S. Jyoti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up A Django Admin Site]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-a-django-admin-site/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-a-django-admin-site/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T14:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Django admin site provides developers with a simple yet effective way to manage their models and build sustainable projects. It allows you to create, view, update, and remove records from your applications.  In this article, you will learn how to register your models with your admin site, create]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Poromon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Sets in Python – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-sets-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-sets-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T12:54:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the vast landscape of Python programming, understanding data structures is akin to possessing a versatile toolkit. Among the essential tools in this arsenal is the Python set. Sets in Python offer a unique way to organize and manipulate data. Let's embark on a journey to unravel the mysteries of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BERT Explained – The Key to Advanced Language Models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/bert-explained-the-key-to-advanced-language-models/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/bert-explained-the-key-to-advanced-language-models/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T12:06:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered how Google seems to understand exactly what you mean, even when your search terms are a bit off? Or how your favorite voice assistant can comprehend complex questions? The secret behind much of this smart technology is a powerful tool called BERT. In this article, I’ll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Lists in Python – Explained with Example Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-lists-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-lists-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T20:02:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Python, lists are a cornerstones of data organization and manipulation – so I think they deserve a thorough exploration.  This article delves into how to create and manipulate lists in Python, some advanced functionalities, and some practical applications of lists. You can get all the source code from]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern CSS Tooltips And Speech Bubbles (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/modern-css-tooltips-speech-bubbles-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/modern-css-tooltips-speech-bubbles-part1/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tooltips are a very common pattern used in CSS for years. There are a lot of ways to approach tooltips in CSS, though some evoke headaches with all the magic numbers they require. In this article, Temani Afif presents modern techniques to create tooltips with the smallest amount of markup and the greatest amount of flexibility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Waiting For Spring (March 2024 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-march-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-march-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new batch of desktop wallpapers is for you. Designed by artists and designers from across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar for March 2024. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reporting Core Web Vitals With The Performance API]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/reporting-core-web-vitals-performance-api/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/reporting-core-web-vitals-performance-api/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Performance API is a set of standards for measuring and evaluating performance metrics with JavaScript. This article demonstrates how to use the Performance API to generate performance metrics directly in the DOM to create your own reporting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Web Designer’s Accessibility Advocacy Toolkit]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/web-designer-accessibility-advocacy-toolkit/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/web-designer-accessibility-advocacy-toolkit/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital designer Yichan Wang has put together this collection of strategies and selling points to help you encourage and advocate for accessibility in your place of work, including useful scripts you can use as starting points.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yichan Wang)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vanilla JavaScript, Libraries, And The Quest For Stateful DOM Rendering]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/vanilla-javascript-libraries-quest-stateful-dom-rendering/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/vanilla-javascript-libraries-quest-stateful-dom-rendering/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s well-established that the web faces wide-ranging usability and performance issues, from user-hostile UI patterns and twisted search results to sluggish performance and battery-draining bloat. In this article, Frederik examines one small-but-significant aspect where developers take the reins: Painting pixels on the screen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederik Dohr)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Practical Guide To Designing For Colorblind People]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/designing-for-colorblindness/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/designing-for-colorblindness/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Color accessibility is more than just ticking boxes. Even with good contrast, some color palettes can make interfaces challenging for users. Here are some practical guidelines to ensure more inclusive design for colorblind people. An upcoming part of Smart Interface Design Patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile Accessibility Barriers For Assistive Technology Users]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/mobile-accessibility-barriers-assistive-technology-users/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/mobile-accessibility-barriers-assistive-technology-users/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility goes beyond making products user-friendly. It can significantly impact the quality of life for people with disabilities. Kate Kalcevich shares lessons she learned from assistive technology users — challenges and barriers they encounter on mobile devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kate Kalcevich)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Accessibility Standards Can Empower Better Chart Visual Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/accessibility-standards-empower-better-chart-visual-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/accessibility-standards-empower-better-chart-visual-design/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility for data visualization extends well beyond web standards, at least if you’re trying to create an experience that’s actually useful. This article focuses on techniques for creating useful and accessible visualizations that extend well beyond compliance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kent Eisenhuth)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Practical Guide To Designing For Children]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/practical-guide-design-children/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/practical-guide-design-children/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to design for children aged 3–12, with insights into user behavior, considerations for parents, and practical UX guidelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Draw Radar Charts In Web]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/draw-radar-charts-web/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/draw-radar-charts-web/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A radar chart — also commonly called a spider chart — is yet another way to visualize data and make connections. Radar charts are inherently geometric, making them both a perfect fit and fun to make with CSS, thanks to the `polygon()` function. Read along as Preethi Sam demonstrates the process and sprinkles it with a pinch of JavaScript to make a handy, reusable component.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Preethi Sam)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frequently Heard In My Beginning Front-End Web Development Class]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/frequently-heard-beginning-front-end-web-development-class/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/frequently-heard-beginning-front-end-web-development-class/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What could we learn from entry-level students in front-end web development? As seasoned professionals, you might think you’ve seen it all, but the truth is that the newcomers are asking the most intriguing questions and making connections that those of us who have spent years on the front end may have never considered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Development Is Getting Too Complex, And It May Be Our Fault]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/web-development-getting-too-complex/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/web-development-getting-too-complex/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An overwhelming number of frameworks and tooling available today gives the impression that web development has gotten perhaps too complex. Juan Diego Rodríguez explores if web development really is that complex and, most importantly, how we can prevent it from getting even more difficult than we already perceive it to be.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Designing For Older Adults]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/guide-designing-older-adults/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/guide-designing-older-adults/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With one billion people aged 60 or older worldwide, inclusivity is more important than ever. Learn how to create digital experiences that empower independence and competence for older adults while enhancing usability for all. An upcoming part of Smart Interface Design Patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>