<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-10-22T00:16:31.029Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-10-22T00:16:31.029Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is an ORM – The Meaning of Object Relational Mapping Database Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-an-orm-the-meaning-of-object-relational-mapping-database-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-an-orm-the-meaning-of-object-relational-mapping-database-tools/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T18:18:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Object Relational Mapping (ORM) is a technique used in creating a "bridge" between object-oriented programs and, in most cases, relational databases [/news/what-is-a-relational-database-rdbms-definition/]. Put another way, you can see the ORM as the layer that connects object oriented programming [/news/four-pillars-of-object-oriented-programming/] (OOP) to relational databases.  When interacting with a database using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Ethernet Protocol Works – A Complete Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-complete-guide-to-the-ethernet-protocol/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-complete-guide-to-the-ethernet-protocol/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T17:12:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you’ve been aware of it or not, you’ve probably used the Ethernet in the past. Does this cable look familiar? (Source: Wikipedia [https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ethernet_physical_layer#/media/File:EthernetCableYellow3.jpg] )Ethernet is extremely popular, and is the most widely used Data Link Layer protocol, at least where the devices are linked by physical cables (rather than]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Rosenbaum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fancy Image Decorations: Masks and Advanced Hover Effects]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374194</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/fancy-image-decorations-masks-and-advanced-hover-effects/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T12:46:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Part 2 of this three-part series! We are still decorating images without any extra elements and pseudo-elements. I hope you already took the time to digest Part 1 because we will continue working with a lot of gradients …
Fancy Image Decorations: Masks and Advanced Hover Effects originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Futuristic CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/futuristic-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/futuristic-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Sacha Greif tries to anticipate future CSS trends and takes a look at some far-fetched and futuristic CSS features that might one day make their way to the browser.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sacha Greif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Object Oriented Programming in Python – Full Crash Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/crash-course-object-oriented-programming-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/crash-course-object-oriented-programming-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T22:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Object Oriented programming, or "OOP" for short, is a way of writing code that relies on the concepts of classes and objects.  The main benefit of writing your code in an object-oriented way is to structure your program into simple, reusable pieces of code. Stick with me through this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lane Wagner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CRUD Operations – Crud Definition in Programming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/crud-operations-crud-definition-in-programming/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/crud-operations-crud-definition-in-programming/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T21:54:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When interacting with a database or working with an API, you'll often encounter the term CRUD. It is a popular acronym for the four basic operations or functions that a model (in the case of an API) or a database management system uses. This is an acronym everyone learning computer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instant Articles, Proprietary Syndication, and a Web Built on User Fidelity Preferences]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374470</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/instant-articles-proprietary-syndication-user-fidelity-preferences/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T19:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love it when there’s a sense of synergy in the blogosphere. First, I caught Nick Heer’s coverage of Meta ending support for Instant Articles, its proprietary format for stripped-down performant news articles. He also compares it to the similar …
Instant Articles, Proprietary Syndication, and a Web Built on User Fidelity Preferences originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computer Programmer Salary – How Much Do Coders Make?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/computer-programmer-salary-how-much-do-coders-make/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/computer-programmer-salary-how-much-do-coders-make/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T19:34:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coding is one of the most popular and in-demand careers. There are many reasons why people choose a career in coding and computer science. The technology field offers promising and diverse job prospects in several industries, job security, a generally comfortable starting salary, and increased high-earning potential as developers gain]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tableau VS Power BI – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tableau-vs-power-bi-whats-the-difference/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tableau-vs-power-bi-whats-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T17:48:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tableau and Power BI are both data visualization and business intelligence tools. You can extract data with both tools, visualize the data, analyze it, and turn it into a piece of actionable information. In this article, you will learn what both Power BI and Tableau are in detail. I will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code Google Docs with Flutter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-google-docs-with-flutter/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-google-docs-with-flutter/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T14:15:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a Google Docs clone will help you learn a lot of new concepts. We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Flutter to create a Google Docs clone. Rivaan Ranawat created this course. Rivaan has created many popular technical]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New In DevTools: Halloween Edition 🎃]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/devtools-updates-halloween-edition/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/devtools-updates-halloween-edition/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Patrick Brosset gives an update on the most impactful new features that are now available in DevTools, across Firefox, Chrome, Safari, and Edge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Patrick Brosset)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsive Animations for Every Screen Size and Device]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374345</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/responsive-animations-for-every-screen-size-and-device/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T12:42:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before I career jumped into development, I did a bunch of motion graphics work in After Effects. But even with that background, I still found animating on the web pretty baffling.
Video graphics are designed within a specific ratio and …
Responsive Animations for Every Screen Size and Device originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cassie Evans</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Reverting to Previous Commit – How to Revert to Last Commit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-reverting-to-previous-commit-how-to-revert-to-last-commit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-reverting-to-previous-commit-how-to-revert-to-last-commit/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T22:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git [/news/git-and-github-for-beginners/] is a great tool for version control. It also makes collaborating with others more efficient. In this article, you'll learn how to revert to previous commits when tracking your project with Git. The two commands we'll discuss in this article are git reset and git revert. These commands]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harvard CS50 – Free Computer Science University Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/harvard-cs50/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/harvard-cs50/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T14:07:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Harvard University's CS50 is one of the most popular beginner computer science courses in the world.  We just released the entire CS50 course–all 25 hours–on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. David J. Malan is widely considered to be one of the best computer science instructors. He teaches this course. This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make a Folder “Slit” Effect With CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374376</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-make-a-folder-slit-effect-with-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T12:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you put something — say a regular sheet of paper — in a manilla folder, a part of that thing might peek out of the folder a little bit. The same sort of thing with a wallet and credit …
How to Make a Folder “Slit” Effect With CSS originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Privacy: A New Smashing Book Is Here]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/understanding-privacy-book-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/understanding-privacy-book-release/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Understanding Privacy, our brand new Smashing Book to make sense of privacy, and learn how to create inclusive, safe and privacy-aware digital experiences. eBook now available, print shipping in November.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Command Line Tutorial – How to Use Common Terminal Commands]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linux-command-line-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linux-command-line-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T23:33:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An operating system is a set of software layers between you and your computer's hardware.  The operating system (or OS) is a piece of software that controls all other application programs and helps you manage the hardware and software of your computer. Examples of popular operating systems are Windows,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Destiny Erhabor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manuel Matuzovic: max() Trickery]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374466</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/manuel-matuzovic-max-trickery/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T13:54:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By way of a post by Manuel Matuzović which is by way of a demo by Temani Afif.
.wrapper {
  margin-inline: max(0px, ((100% - 64rem) / 2)); 
}
You’d be doing yourself a favor to read Manuel’s breakdown of …
Manuel Matuzovic: max() Trickery originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pure CSS Bezier Curve Motion Paths]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373600</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/pure-css-bezier-curve-motion-paths/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T15:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Besides being elegant, Bezier curves have nice mathematical properties due to their definition and construction. No wonder they are widely used in so many areas! Now, how about using Bezier curves as motion paths with CSS?
Pure CSS Bezier Curve Motion Paths originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lu Wang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Full-Site Editing: A Deep Dive Into The New Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/wordpress-full-site-editing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/wordpress-full-site-editing/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Nick Schäferhoff will take a deep dive into WordPress Full-Site Editing, examine the tools it provides for theme development, and provide a tutorial on how to use it to make changes to your site.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nick Schäferhoff)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the CSScenes, October 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374393</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/behind-the-csscenes-october-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T21:40:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, hey, welcome back to Behind the CSScenes! These posts are like little check-ins we’re doing each month to give you a peek behind what we’re doing here at CSS-Tricks, as well as a chance for us to pause …
Behind the CSScenes, October 2022 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haley Mills</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fancy Image Decorations: Single Element Magic]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373965</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/fancy-image-decorations-single-element-magic/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T15:37:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the title says, we are going to decorate images! There’s a bunch of other articles out there that talk about this, but what we’re covering here is quite a bit different because it’s more of a challenge. The challenge? …
Fancy Image Decorations: Single Element Magic originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Things I Took Away From An Event Apart 2022 in Denver]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374401</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/some-things-i-took-away-from-an-event-apart-2022-in-denver/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T20:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Event Apart 2022 Denver wrapped up yesterday. And while I was unable to make it to all three days this time, I did catch yesterday’s action — and it was awesome. I’m not very social or outgoing, but …
Some Things I Took Away From An Event Apart 2022 in Denver originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Pure CSS Gallery Focus Effect with :not]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373508</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-pure-css-gallery-focus-effect-with-not/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T15:10:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oftentimes in the past, I needed to figure out how to add styles to all elements inside the container but not the hovered one.
Demo of the expected “fade-out” effect on siblings to let users “focus” on a particular element.…
A Pure CSS Gallery Focus Effect with :not originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krzysztof Gonciarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Effective Communication For Everyday Meetings]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/effective-communication-everyday-meetings/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/effective-communication-everyday-meetings/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article about conducting productive meetings, Andrii Zhdan will give you a step-by-step guide on preparing a solid meeting structure that will let you follow the original plan and reach the meeting goals, and he will also share a few tips based on his design experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andrii Zhdan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Early Days of Container Style Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374330</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/early-days-of-container-style-queries/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T13:06:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re still in suuuuuper early days with container queries. Too early for broad browser support, but Chromium already supports it, Safari started supporting it in version 16, and Firefox is presumably not far behind.
Most early days conversations …
Early Days of Container Style Queries originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rendering External API Data in WordPress Blocks on the Front End]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373952</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/rendering-external-api-data-in-wordpress-blocks-on-the-front-end/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T16:15:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’ve been some new tutorials popping here on CSS-Tricks for working with WordPress blocks. One of them is an introduction to WordPress block development and it’s a good place to learn what blocks are and to register them in WordPress …
Rendering External API Data in WordPress Blocks on the Front End originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manoj Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sustainable Web Development Strategies Within An Organization]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/sustainable-web-development-strategies-organization/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/sustainable-web-development-strategies-organization/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Climate change and sustainability are increasing concerns for digital organizations, as well as individuals working in tech. In this article, we’ll explore some of the ways we can raise awareness and effect change within an organization to create a more positive environmental impact.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delightful UI Animations With Shared Element Transitions API (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/ui-animations-shared-element-transitions-api-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/ui-animations-shared-element-transitions-api-part2/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Adrian Bece will show how to create same-document page transitions for Single Page Apps using Shared Element Transitions API and check out its future implementation and potential for creating cross-document transitions in Multi-Page Apps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding Fluid Typography Support to WordPress Block Themes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373905</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/fluid-typography-wordpress-block-themes/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T13:19:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fluid typography is a fancy way of “describing font properties, such as size or line height, that scale fluidly according to the size of the viewport”. It’s also known by other names, like responsive typography, flexible type, fluid type, …
Adding Fluid Typography Support to WordPress Block Themes originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ganesh Dahal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Roadmap For Building A Business Chatbot]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/roadmap-building-business-chatbot/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/roadmap-building-business-chatbot/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Owing to tremendous advancements in Machine Learning and other technologies, chatbots have increased in popularity in the past few years. This article will show you, step by step, how to build a chatbot that meets your business goals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Devansh Bansal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js Authentication With Twilio Verify]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/nodejs-authentication-twilio-verify/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/nodejs-authentication-twilio-verify/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Integrate two-factor authentication into your Express.js app by building an application that authenticates users using password-based authentication and OTPs powered by the Twilio Verify service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alexander Godwin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Safely Share Your Email Address on a Website]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373798</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-safely-share-your-email-address-on-a-website/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T12:54:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spammers are a huge deal nowadays. If you want to share your contact information without getting overwhelmed by spam email you need a solution. I run into this problem a few months ago. While I was researching how to solve …
How to Safely Share Your Email Address on a Website originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lorenzo Bonannella</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Web Components With Next (or Any SSR Framework)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373787</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-web-components-with-next-or-any-ssr-framework/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T13:05:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous post we looked at Shoelace, which is a component library with a full suite of UX components that are beautiful, accessible, and — perhaps unexpectedly — built with Web Components. This means they can be used …
Using Web Components With Next (or Any SSR Framework) originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Rackis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easy Fluid Typography With clamp() Using Sass Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/fluid-typography-clamp-sass-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/fluid-typography-clamp-sass-functions/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We can use the `clamp()` method today because of the great browser support. In this article, Brecht De Ruyte explains how it can be a beautiful addition to your upcoming project or as an upgrade to a previous one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Brecht De Ruyte)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delightful UI Animations With Shared Element Transitions API (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/ui-animations-shared-element-transitions-api-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/ui-animations-shared-element-transitions-api-part1/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shared Element Transitions API is a game-changing feature that will enable us to create impressive and elaborate UI animations easily. In this article, Adrian Bece will explore its incredible potential by building four real-life examples from scratch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[October Vibes For Your Desktop (2022 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-october-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-october-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-30T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How about a little inspiration boost? Well, we might have something for you: desktop wallpapers created with love by artists and designers from across the globe. They are available in versions with and without a calendar for October and can be downloaded for free. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unconscious Biases That Get In The Way Of Inclusive Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/unconscious-biases-inclusive-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/unconscious-biases-inclusive-design/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Throughout the research and design processes, our unconscious biases are the greatest risk to delivering inclusive experiences. From who we include and exclude in our research to how we plan and conduct research, it’s crucial that we understand how our unacknowledged biases can perpetuate systems of exclusion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Trina Moore Pervall)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Your Security Strategy (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/ten-principles-consider-building-security-strategy-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/ten-principles-consider-building-security-strategy-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Wix security experts share ten “security by design” principles that emerged from their work in keeping the Wix platform secure. If you’re a developer, these tried-and-true principles can help you build your own secure applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Wix Security Team)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phone Numbers For Web Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/phone-numbers-web-designers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/phone-numbers-web-designers/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The customer journey is not limited to a website alone. Simply by combining the world of website design and telephony, far better results can be obtained for your organization. And thanks to the similarities and mutual benefits, it is an easy step to take.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Onno Westra)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five Data-Loading Patterns To Boost Web Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/data-loading-patterns-improve-frontend-performance/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/data-loading-patterns-improve-frontend-performance/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You don’t need a framework for everything, but if you use one, this article will help you use it in the most performant way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Agustinus Theodorus)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet SmashingConf New York 🇺🇸 (Oct 10&ndash;13)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/meet-smashingconf-new-york/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/meet-smashingconf-new-york/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SmashingConf NYC is back! A friendly, inclusive conference for designers and front-end engineers who can’t wait to learn and be inspired. October 10–13, 2022. Get your ticket!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lessons Learned As A Designer-Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/lessons-learned-designer-founder/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/lessons-learned-designer-founder/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Dave Feldman shares his lessons learned and the experiments has done as a multidisciplinary designer-founder-CEO at an early-stage startup. Let’s take a look at what it is that makes a great design process for teams of any size.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Dave Feldman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Things I Wish I Had Known About Angular When I Started]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/angular-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/angular-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re considering learning Angular, this article sums up what William Juan wished he knew when he started, including the mistakes made and lessons learned the hard way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (William Juan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>