<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-08-13T00:09:45.071Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-08-13T00:09:45.071Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the WordPress Command Line Interface – WP-CLI Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-wordpress-cli/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-wordpress-cli/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T21:37:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of website development and content management, efficiency and automation are key. The WordPress Command Line Interface – or WP-CLI – is a powerful tool that can help you streamlines tasks and manage WordPress websites more effectively.  This article provides an overview of WP-CLI, focusing on its]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Venturi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Meteor Effect with React and TailwindCSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-meteor-effect-with-react-and-tailwindcss/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-meteor-effect-with-react-and-tailwindcss/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T16:14:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A while ago, I saw a post on Twitter that had some fancy beams of light emanating out from behind the main image. It looked like a meteor was blazing softly behind the card, and I thought it was a really cool UI component to have in a project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manu Arora</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Accessible Text Over Images: Best Practices, Techniques, And Resources (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/designing-accessible-text-over-images-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/designing-accessible-text-over-images-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Part 2 of the series, Hannah Milan reviews in detail various accessible text over images techniques for designing your web and mobile app content, including framing the image, soft-colored gradients technique, text styles and text position, solid color shapes, and use of colored backgrounds. And finally, the emphasis will once again be placed on the accessibility aspect, which needs to be “baked in” right from the start rather than being an afterthought in your design process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Hannah Milan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TCP and UDP Protocols – Explained in Plain English]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tcp-and-udp-protocols/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tcp-and-udp-protocols/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T22:19:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that it's thanks to the TCP and UDP protocols that the internet works? But what do these acronyms mean? Well, TCP stands for Transmission Control Protocol and UDP stands for User Datagram Protocol Ok, but what are they? Why are they useful? Why is it thanks to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Optimize Your WordPress Site for Search Engine Visibility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/wordpress-seo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/wordpress-seo/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T14:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's digital landscape, where online presence is key to success, Search Engine Optimization (SEO) [/news/tag/seo/] plays a pivotal role in driving organic traffic to your website.  Among various content management systems, WordPress is a popular choice due to its user-friendly interface and flexibility.  But having a WordPress]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Campbell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harvard CS50's Introduction to Artificial Intelligence with Python – Free University Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/harvard-cs50s-ai-python-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/harvard-cs50s-ai-python-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T14:36:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Harvard University's CS50 is one of the most popular beginner computer science courses in the world. And Harvard also has versions of CS50 with different focusses, all perfect for beginners. We just released Harvard CS50's Introduction to Artificial Intelligence with Python on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. If you are new]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deliver Powerful Tech Conference Talks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tips-for-speaking-at-tech-conferences/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tips-for-speaking-at-tech-conferences/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T14:24:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wanted to share your expertise at conferences, but something inside you is holding you back?  Perhaps it's the fear of speaking in front of a large audience, the worry of forgetting your words, or the challenge of finding the perfect topic to discuss. You're not alone]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shruti Kapoor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running A Page Speed Test: Monitoring vs. Measuring]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/running-page-speed-test-monitoring-versus-measuring/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/running-page-speed-test-monitoring-versus-measuring/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What does your performance “stack” look like? There are all kinds of tools available for measuring page speed, but what data and assumptions do they use to measure performance? And speaking of *measuring* performance, there’s quite a difference between that and *monitoring* performance. Let’s dig in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Minimum Stability In Composer?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-minimum-stability-in-composer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-minimum-stability-in-composer/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T17:31:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Composer is a dependency management tool for projects running on PHP. PHP frameworks like Laravel, Symfony, and CodeIgniter use Composer to manage libraries and packages. In this tutorial, you’ll learn the following:  * Introduction to Composer.  * Minimum stability in Composer.  * Levels of stability, and the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sule-Balogun Olanrewaju Ganiu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn End-to-End Testing with Cypress for JavaScript Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mastering-end-to-end-testing-with-cypress-for-javascript-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mastering-end-to-end-testing-with-cypress-for-javascript-applications/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T16:58:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ensuring the reliability and performance of your web applications is important. Testing is a key tool that will help with these things and more.  We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Cypress to create end-to-end tests for your JavaScript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering JavaScript Functions for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mastering-javascript-functions-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mastering-javascript-functions-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T16:40:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you new to the world of programming? Are you eager to unlock the potential of JavaScript to create more readable and maintainable code? If so, we have an excellent course for you. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you everything you need]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy Your Websites and Apps – User-Friendly Deployment Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-websites-and-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-websites-and-applications/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T14:23:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying your application is a key aspect of software development. Typically, having an app on your local system isn't enough – it needs to be accessible online. So choosing a suitable and user-friendly hosting and deployment plan is vital. The key to making the right decision lies in understanding the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijeoma Igboagu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Friction As A Feature In Machine Learning Algorithms]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/friction-feature-machine-learning-algorithms/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/friction-feature-machine-learning-algorithms/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Friction often has a negative connotation in user experience design, but it actually has many benefits. Its best-known use case is mitigating unintended consequences in high-risk scenarios, yet it has a new place in the age of artificial intelligence. Adding strategic friction to interfaces can lead to profound efficiency gains in machine learning algorithms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Maximillian Piras)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Accessible Text Over Images: Best Practices, Techniques, And Resources (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/designing-accessible-text-over-images-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/designing-accessible-text-over-images-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this two-part series of articles, Hannah Milan covers the best practices when using various accessible text over images techniques for designing your web and mobile app content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Hannah Milan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Optimized Performance To Serve A Global Audience]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/optimize-performance-serve-global-audience/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/optimize-performance-serve-global-audience/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liran Cohen and the team at Bookaway, a travel booking service, dramatically improved their site’s performance by auditing Core Web Vitals. In this article, Liran shares his team’s process for auditing and monitoring Web Vitals and the effort it took to dramatically improve Bookaway’s performance — and the benefits that came with it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Liran Cohen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 64 With Alvin Bryan: What Is A Headless CMS?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/smashing-podcast-episode-64/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/smashing-podcast-episode-64/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re talking about headless content management systems. What are they, and how do they differ from more traditional systems? Drew McLellan talks to Alvin Bryan to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS And Accessibility: Inclusion Through User Choice]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/css-accessibility-inclusion-user-choice/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/css-accessibility-inclusion-user-choice/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Carie Fisher outlines which CSS media features are available for detecting user preferences and how they are used to design and build more inclusive user experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carie Fisher)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Living In The Moment (August 2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T09:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New month, new wallpapers! In this post, you’ll find unique and inspiring wallpapers for August 2023. Created with love by the community for the community, they come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Define An Array Of Colors With CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/define-array-colors-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/define-array-colors-css/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join Temani Afif on experiment with modern CSS features to create an array of colors. The goal is to define a comma-separated list of colors and iterate through them using an index.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use Artificial Intelligence And Machine Learning To Summarize Chat Conversations]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/artificial-intelligence-machine-learning-summarize-chat-conversations/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/artificial-intelligence-machine-learning-summarize-chat-conversations/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll explore how to build a chat summarizer using the Cohere API and deploy it as a web application using Gradio.[ Cohere](https://cohere.com/) is an AI platform that provides state-of-the-art natural language processing models for a variety of tasks, including summarization. We’ll cover the steps involved in training the summarizer using sample chat conversations, interacting with the Cohere API to generate summaries, and creating a user-friendly interface using [Gradio](https://www.gradio.app/).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joas Pambou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern Technology And The Future Of Language Translation]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/modern-technology-future-language-translation/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/modern-technology-future-language-translation/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The field of language translation has never been more exciting. Explore the evolution of language translation platforms, how we got to where we are today, and what advancements we can look forward to in the coming years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adriano Raiano)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recreating YouTube’s Ambient Mode Glow Effect]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/recreating-youtube-ambient-mode-glow-effect/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/recreating-youtube-ambient-mode-glow-effect/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Adrian deconstructs YouTube’s “Ambient Mode” feature and how HTML `` and the `requestAnimationFrame` function are used to create the glowing effect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Art Of Looking Back: A Critical Reflection For Individual Contributors]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/critical-reflection-individual-contributors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/critical-reflection-individual-contributors/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover the importance of critical reflective practice and challenge some beliefs about reflection and its role in our work and growth. Kristian Mikhel suggests a critical reflective routine for individual contributors and gives some practical recommendations that will make reflection meaningful and actionable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kristian Mikhel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Age-Inclusive Products: Guidelines And Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/designing-age-inclusive-products-guidelines-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/designing-age-inclusive-products-guidelines-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With an estimated one in every eight individuals worldwide surpassing the age of 60, who are actively adopting online shopping, the need for user-friendly interfaces tailored to their needs becomes apparent. Explore the guidelines to help you design inclusive products for all, particularly for an older audience and your future self.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michal Halperin Ben Zvi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>