<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-11-22T00:10:33.431Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-11-22T00:10:33.431Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Secure User Authentication Flow in Flutter with Firebase and Bloc State Management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/user-authentication-flow-in-flutter-with-firebase-and-bloc/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/user-authentication-flow-in-flutter-with-firebase-and-bloc/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T15:21:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[User authentication is critical to mobile app development. It helps make sure that only authorized users can access sensitive information and perform actions within an application. In this tutorial, we will explore how to build secure user authentication in Flutter using Firebase for authentication and the Bloc state management pattern]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justice Nwogu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating And Maintaining A Voice Of Customer Program]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/creating-maintaining-voice-customer-program/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/creating-maintaining-voice-customer-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Product teams benefit from knowing their users’ needs and how they respond to product updates as they build out the roadmap of a product. This article covers Voice of Customer programs and is aimed at those who work on a product team as well as executives who are looking for how to better inform your products using insight from users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Victor Yocco &amp; Dana Daniels)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use If Statements in JavaScript – a Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/if-statements-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/if-statements-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T21:45:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is a powerful and versatile programming language that is widely used for creating dynamic and interactive web pages.  One of the fundamental building blocks of JavaScript programming is the if  statement. if statements allow developers to control the flow of their programs by making decisions based on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build and Deploy a python-telegram-bot v20 Webhook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-and-deploy-python-telegram-bot-v20-webhooks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-and-deploy-python-telegram-bot-v20-webhooks/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T20:43:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The python-telegram-bot v20 release introduced major structural changes. According to the documentation, > “All networking and I/O-related logic now works via coroutine functions (i.e.  async def ... functions). In particular, all methods of the telegram.Bot class that make requests to the Bot API are now coroutine functions and need]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chua Hui Shun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Data Visualization with Dr. Curran Kelleher]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-data-visualization-curran-kelleher/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-data-visualization-curran-kelleher/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T21:09:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I'm joined by Dr. Curran Kelleher. He's a data visualization expert and has taught a number of in-depth data visualization courses on freeCodeCamp's YouTube channel. We talk about what it's like to get a Ph.D. under one of the pioneers of data visualization. We also talk about how he]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Efficient Design-to-Code Handoff Process Using Uno Platform For Figma]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/design-to-code-handoff-process-uno-platform-figma/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/design-to-code-handoff-process-uno-platform-figma/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Effective collaboration between designers and developers is vital to creating good user experiences. However, bridging the handoff between design and development with the many tools and workflows available today has its pitfalls. Matthew Mattei introduces you to the Uno Platform, which offers a robust set of productivity boosters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matthew Mattei)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Game Tutorial – Build a Stick Hero Clone with HTML Canvas + JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-game-tutorial-stick-hero-with-html-canvas/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-game-tutorial-stick-hero-with-html-canvas/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T19:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you'll learn how to create a game that's inspired by Stick Hero – using plain JavaScript and HTML canvas. We are going to recreate Stick Hero [https://apps.apple.com/us/app/stick-hero/id918338898], a mobile game published by KetchApp. We'll go through how the game works in general, how to use JavaScript to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hunor Márton Borbély</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Localize Your Django App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/localize-django-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/localize-django-app/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T18:07:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered how websites can offer their content in multiple languages, perfectly tailored to different cultures and regions?  Well, that magic is called localization, and it's a game-changer for web development – especially when using Django, a super versatile Python framework.  It's not just about translating]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jess Wilk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT vs BARD AI – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/chatgpt-vs-bard/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/chatgpt-vs-bard/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T17:19:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In November of 2022, Artificial Intelligence took center stage in the tech world. AI was not a new concept, but OpenAI had just released its ChatGPT Large Language Model, and devs started diving into using it.  Large Language Models, or LLMs, let users enter a prompt (some question or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maybell Obadoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React Suspense to Improve your React Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-suspense/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-suspense/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T17:04:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React's ecosystem is always growing, and it seems like there are always new features and enhancements to make development more effective and user-friendly.  React Suspense is one such feature that has become quite popular among React devs. In this guide, you'll learn all about React Suspense and examine its]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okosa Leonard Onyekachukwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master Technical Interviews]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-technical-interviews/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-technical-interviews/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T15:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You need to prepare if you want to perform well in technical developer job interviews. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will guide you through every aspect of the technical interview process, as well as prepare you for the type of questions you might get]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use TypeScript with React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-typescript-with-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-typescript-with-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T18:53:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn how to use TypeScript with React. By the end, you will have a solid understanding of how to write React code with TypeScript. Want to watch the video version of this tutorial? You can check out the video below: Table of Contents  *]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yogesh Chavan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Responsive Multi-Line Ribbon Shapes (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/css-responsive-multi-line-ribbon-shapes-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/css-responsive-multi-line-ribbon-shapes-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ribbons have been used to accent designs for many years now. But, the way we approach them in CSS has evolved with the introduction of newer features. In this article, Temani Afif combines background and gradient tricks to create ribbon shapes in CSS that are not only responsive but support multi-line text and are easily adjustable with a few CSS variables.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Web Design Documentation]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/designing-web-design-documentation/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/designing-web-design-documentation/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Words alone aren’t enough to safeguard best practices in the world of web design and development. Web design documentation must be like its medium — interactive and constantly evolving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Accessible UI Animations]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/creating-accessible-ui-animations/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/creating-accessible-ui-animations/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animation and accessibility are often seen as two separate powers at odds with one another. How is it possible to strike a balance between elements that move and the possible negative effects they expose to users who are sensitive to motion? Oriana García explains how her team at Mercado Libre tackled the challenge by creating guiding principles for applying animation to user interfaces and incorporating them into the team’s design system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Oriana García)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Playground: From 5-Minute Install To Instant Spin-Up]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/wordpress-playground-5-minute-install-instant-spin-up/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/wordpress-playground-5-minute-install-instant-spin-up/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Playground began as an experiment to see what a self-hosted WordPress experience might look like without the requirement of having to actually install WordPress. A year later, the experiment has evolved into a full-fledged project. Ganesh Dahal demonstrates how WordPress Playground works and gets deep into how it might be used.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ganesh Dahal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Addressing Accessibility Concerns With Using Fluid Type]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/addressing-accessibility-concerns-fluid-type/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/addressing-accessibility-concerns-fluid-type/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS `clamp()` function is often paired with viewport units for “fluid” font sizing that scales the text up and down at different viewport sizes. As common as this technique is, several voices warn that it opens up situations where text can fail WCAG Success Criterion 1.4.4, which specifies that text should scale up to at least 200% when the user’s browser reaches its 500% maximum zoom level. Max Barvian takes a deep look at the issue and offers ideas to help address it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Maxwell Barvian)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Search Of The Ideal Privacy Icon]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/search-ideal-privacy-icon/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/search-ideal-privacy-icon/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Icons are capable of enhancing the content that surrounds them, but they have to be self-explanatory for that to happen. We have icons for things we like (a thumbs up), things we can share (a box topped with an up arrow), and even for protection against malicious online attacks (a shield), but what are the options we have for representing “privacy”?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Preethi Sam)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Answering Common Questions About Interpreting Page Speed Reports]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/answering-questions-interpreting-page-speed-reports/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/answering-questions-interpreting-page-speed-reports/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take a closer look at how various performance tools audit and report on performance metrics, such as core web vitals. Geoff Graham answers a set of common questions that pop up during performance audits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tales Of November (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T09:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November is just around the corner, and with it, a new collection of desktop wallpapers to celebrate the beginning of the month. Designed by creatives from all across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar. Let’s make this November colorful!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passkeys: A No-Frills Explainer On The Future Of Password-Less Authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/passkeys-explainer-future-password-less-authentication/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/passkeys-explainer-future-password-less-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Passkeys are beginning to make their way into popular apps, from password managers to multi-factor authenticators, but what exactly are they? As this new technology promises to make passwords a thing of the past, Neal Fennimore explains the concepts behind passkeys, demonstrates how they work, and speculates what we might expect from them in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Neal Fennimore)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What I Wish I Knew About Working In Development Right Out Of School]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/beginner-web-development-working-career/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/beginner-web-development-working-career/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Victoria Johnson began a career in front-end development upon graduating from college. Now, roughly one year later, she reflects back on the decisions she made to crack into the field and find her first full-time job. This is her story, and she’s sharing it to provide those who are just starting out with another beginner’s perspective.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Victoria Johnson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Actionable And Reliable Usability Questionnaire With Only 7 Items: <span style="font-variant: small-caps">Inuit</span>]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/actionable-reliable-usability-questionnaire-inuit/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/actionable-reliable-usability-questionnaire-inuit/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inuit (short for “**In**terface **U**sability **I**nstrumen**t**”) is a new questionnaire you can use to assess the usability of your user interface. It has been designed to be more diagnostic than existing usability instruments like, e.g., SUS and for use with machine learning, all the while asking fewer questions than other questionnaires. This article explores how and why Inuit has been developed and why we can be sure that it actually measures usability, and reliably so.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Maximilian Speicher &amp; Johanna Jagow)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fight For The Main Thread]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/speedcurve-fight-main-thread/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/speedcurve-fight-main-thread/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having access to a free reporting tool like Lighthouse in DevTools is a great start for diagnosing performance issues by identifying bottlenecks on the main thread. Even better are paid tools like [SpeedCurve](https://www.speedcurve.com/?utm_source=smashingmag&utm_medium=magazine&utm_campaign=sm7_2023&utm_id=sm7_2023&utm_term=sm7_2023) to dig deeper into the data for more targeted insights and to produce visual reports to help make a case for performance improvements for your team and other stakeholders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Removing Object Properties Tells Us About JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/removing-object-properties-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/10/removing-object-properties-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Removing properties from an object in JavaScript might not be the most exciting job, but there are many ways to achieve it, each revealing a fundamental aspect of how JavaScript works. Juan Diego Rodríguez explores each technique in this article.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>