<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-04-06T00:09:18.137Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-04-06T00:09:18.137Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bubble Sort Algorithm - Most Asked Questions About Bubble Sort]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/most-asked-questions-about-bubble-sort/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/most-asked-questions-about-bubble-sort/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T21:40:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bubble sort is a simple sorting algorithm that repeatedly loops through a list, compares adjacent elements, and swaps them if they are in the wrong order. The bubble sort algorithm is not the most efficient sorting algorithm when it comes to time complexity. But it is still often used as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Trie Data Structures Work – Validate User Input with Automated Trie Visualization]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-validate-user-input-with-automated-trie-visualization/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-validate-user-input-with-automated-trie-visualization/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T21:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data structures play a vital role in computer science. They are essential for designing efficient software infrastructure.  Simply put, a data structure is a way of organizing and storing data in a computer so that it can be accessed and manipulated reliably. Also, it provides a set of operations]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel García Solla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Symmetric and Asymmetric Key Encryption – Explained in Plain English]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/encryption-explained-in-plain-english/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/encryption-explained-in-plain-english/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T20:09:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Encryption is a way of scrambling data so that it can only be read by the intended recipient.  Encryption is an integral part of our daily lives – whether you are sending messages to friends on WhatsApp, visiting a website and your browser is making sure it's legitimate, or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adetunji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build and Publish Python Packages With Poetry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-and-publish-python-packages-with-poetry/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-and-publish-python-packages-with-poetry/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T18:04:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Python package is a collection of Python modules that can be easily distributed and installed. It allows developers to reuse code across multiple projects and share it with others.  Python packages typically include a set of functions, classes, or other components that serve a specific purpose, such as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Personal Website with Next.js 13, Sanity.io, TailwindCSS, and TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-personal-website-with-next-js-13-sanity-io-tailwindcss-and-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-personal-website-with-next-js-13-sanity-io-tailwindcss-and-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T14:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a personal website can be an excellent way to practice various developer skills. And it can also help showcases your skills, projects, and accomplishments. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build a personal website using Next.js 13 for the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Protect Your App With A Threat Model Based On JSONDiff]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/protect-app-threat-model-jsondiff/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/protect-app-threat-model-jsondiff/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a developer who wants to concentrate on delivering a killer application rather than worrying about countless security issues, threat model documents can help you do that. With small architectural changes, we can make these threats manageable and prevent them in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zack Grossbart &amp; Terry Yao)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[850+ Online Courses with Real College Credit that You Can Access for Free]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/370-online-courses-with-real-college-credit-that-you-can-access-for-free-4fec5a28646/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/370-online-courses-with-real-college-credit-that-you-can-access-for-free-4fec5a28646/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many universities offer online courses for credit. Class Central [https://www.classcentral.com/] has already compiled 70+ MOOC-based master’s degrees [https://www.classcentral.com/report/mooc-based-masters-degree/]. Many of the courses in these online degree programs are publicly available: anyone with an internet connection can take them. Some of these courses are “freebies” meant to give prospective students a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhawal Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Signals in Angular – How to Write More Reactive Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/angular-signals/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/angular-signals/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T00:53:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An exciting new feature is coming to Angular: signals! Signals provide a new way for our code to tell our templates (and other code) that our data has changed. This improves Angular's change detection, which also improves performance, and makes our code more reactive. You can try out this powerful]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deborah Kurata</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Improve User Experience  in React Apps – Animate Routes using Framer Motion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-user-experience-in-react-by-animating-routes-using-framer-motion/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-user-experience-in-react-by-animating-routes-using-framer-motion/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T22:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the modern digital landscape, user experience (UX) has become a central focus of web development. Providing a smooth, captivating, and aesthetically pleasing interface can really influence user satisfaction and retention.  Route animation is a frequently underestimated aspect of UX that can substantially improve a website's interactivity.  In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaja Ibifubara David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python vs Pandas - Difference Between Python and Pandas]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/difference-between-python-and-pandas/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/difference-between-python-and-pandas/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T21:46:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The difference between Python and Pandas is a topic that often confuses some beginners in the Python ecosystem.  In this article, you'll learn about the differences between Python and Pandas, and what they are used for. You'll start by learning what each technology is used for, then you'll see]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Dorking for Penetration Testers — A Practical Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-dorking-for-pentesters-a-practical-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-dorking-for-pentesters-a-practical-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-04T21:10:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every day, Google processes over 8.5 billion searches. We know how much we use Google daily. With the crawling capabilities of Google, it can also be a powerful tool for pen testers. Google can help us find exposed files, scripts and other critical resources in web applications. To find this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Algorithms: Skills Of Designers That AI Can’t Replicate]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/skills-designers-ai-cant-replicate/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/skills-designers-ai-cant-replicate/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article highlights non-technical skills like curiosity, observation, empathy, advocacy, visual communication, and collaboration that designers routinely use in their process to make a difference through design. AI can be used to augment designers’ workflow instead of replacing people.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lyndon Cerejo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swing Into April (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With April just around the corner, we have a new collection of desktop and mobile wallpapers waiting for you to celebrate the beginning of the new month. Designed by creatives from all across the globe, the wallpapers come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Comprehensive Checklist For Running Design Workshops]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/organizing-design-workshops-checklist/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/organizing-design-workshops-checklist/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Workshops are all about people: they involve people, are conducted by people, and aim to close the gaps in people’s communication. Slava Shestopalov shares a checklist with everything you need to keep in mind when running a workshop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Slava Shestopalov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fine-Grained Access Handling And Data Management With Row-Level Security]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/access-handling-data-management-row-level-security/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/access-handling-data-management-row-level-security/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dealing with sensitive data is an important topic for any app. In this article, you will find out how to handle sensitive or confidential information in your apps and what Row-Level Security means.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Handoff Is No Handoff]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/best-handoff-is-no-handoff/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/best-handoff-is-no-handoff/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design handoffs are inefficient and painful. They cause frustration, friction and a lot of back and forth. Can we avoid them altogether? Of course we can! Let’s see how to do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overcoming The Challenges Of Content Creation For Informational Websites]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/overcoming-challenges-content-creation-informational-websites/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/overcoming-challenges-content-creation-informational-websites/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Content matters! Unfortunately, when it comes to informational websites, content quality is often poor. There is no magic answer to fix that. However, there are practical techniques you can use to improve the copy on your websites and ensure your users find the content they are looking for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Cross-Browser DevTools Features You Might Not Know]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377264</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/some-cross-browser-devtools-features-you-might-not-know/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T20:22:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I spend a lot of time in DevTools, and I’m sure you do too. Sometimes I even bounce between them, especially when I’m debugging cross-browser issues. DevTools is a lot like browsers themselves — not all of the features in …
Some Cross-Browser DevTools Features You Might Not Know originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pankaj Parashar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 58 With Debbie Levitt: What Is CX Design?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/smashing-podcast-episode-58/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/smashing-podcast-episode-58/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we ask what is Customer Experience design, and how does it differ from User Experience design? Vitaly Friedman talks to expert Debbie Levitt to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Fonts For Interface Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/free-fonts-interface-designers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/free-fonts-interface-designers/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just a few beautiful, well-crafted fonts for headings and body text that you probably haven’t spotted before. Free for personal and commercial use. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Internationalization In Next.js 13 With React Server Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/internationalization-nextjs-13-react-server-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/internationalization-nextjs-13-react-server-components/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Based on an example of a multilingual app that displays street photography images from Unsplash, Jan Amann explores next-intl to implement all internationalization needs in React Server Components and shares a technique for introducing interactivity with a minimalistic client-side footprint.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jan Amann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full Stack GraphQL With Next.js, Neo4j AuraDB And Vercel]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/full-stack-graphql-nextjs-neo4j-auradb-vercel/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/full-stack-graphql-nextjs-neo4j-auradb-vercel/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, William Lyon explores how to build a full stack GraphQL application that takes advantage of the API Routes feature of Next.js API to combine your GraphQL server and front-end React applications into a single framework.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (William Lyon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Leonardo Da Vinci Can Teach Us About Web Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/leonardo-da-vinci-teach-web-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/leonardo-da-vinci-teach-web-design/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-14T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Perhaps more than any other person in history, Leonardo da Vinci showed the kind of magic that can happen in the overlap between art and science, where much of web development lives. His methods and outlooks are just as applicable to the web today as they were in Renaissance Italy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Calendars With Accessibility and Internationalization in Mind]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376950</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/making-calendars-with-accessibility-and-internationalization-in-mind/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-13T13:23:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Doing a quick search here on CSS-Tricks shows just how many different ways there are to approach calendars. Some show how CSS Grid can create the layout efficiently. Some attempt to bring actual data into the mix. Some …
Making Calendars With Accessibility and Internationalization in Mind originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mads Stoumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Mistakes I Made When Starting My First React Project]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377098</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/5-mistakes-starting-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T16:41:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You know what it’s like to pick up a new language or framework. Sometimes there’s great documentation to help you find your way through it. But even the best documentation doesn’t cover absolutely everything. And when you work with something …
5 Mistakes I Made When Starting My First React Project originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Oliver Bray</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Pragmatist’s Guide To Lean User Research]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/pragmatists-guide-lean-user-research/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/pragmatists-guide-lean-user-research/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Instead of telling you once again what the best practice is and adding to your imposter syndrome, let’s concentrate on some practical approaches to user research that we might be able to fit into our existing projects without being left disillusioned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Complex Forms In Vue]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/building-complex-forms-vue/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/building-complex-forms-vue/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that creating a complex form can be progressively enhanced using some Vue features like the v-for and the v-model? In this article, Olufunke shares some basic Vue core features that are super useful when building out the complex form in your day-to-day Vue usage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Olufunke Moronfolu)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a Clock with the New CSS sin() and cos() Trigonometry Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377074</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-a-clock-with-the-new-css-sin-and-cos-trigonometry-functions/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-08T14:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS trigonometry functions are here! Well, they are if you’re using the latest versions of Firefox and Safari, that is. Having this sort of mathematical power in CSS opens up a whole bunch of possibilities. In this tutorial, I thought …
Creating a Clock with the New CSS sin() and cos() Trigonometry Functions originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mads Stoumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create Dynamic Donut Charts With TailwindCSS And React]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/dynamic-donut-charts-tailwind-css-react/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/dynamic-donut-charts-tailwind-css-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Paul Scanlon shares a super lightweight approach to creating a Donut chart using conic-gradient(). There are no additional libraries to install or maintain, and there’s no heavy JavaScript that needs to be downloaded by the browser in order for them to work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>