<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-05-11T00:09:39.222Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-05-11T00:09:39.222Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full Stack Engineer – Career Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-stack-engineer-career-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-stack-engineer-career-guide/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T17:27:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Full-stack engineering roles have been growing in popularity over the last decade and are among the most sought-after positions in the tech job market. But what exactly are full-stack engineers? What do they do on a day-to-day basis? And how can you become a full-stack engineer yourself? In this article,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discover the Power of Functional Programming with Elixir]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/functional-programming-with-elixir/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/functional-programming-with-elixir/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T15:59:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transform your development approach and embrace the power of Elixir and functional programming with our new beginner's course. It is designed to help you build scalable, maintainable applications like never before. We just published a new course on the freeCodeCamp channel that will teach you how to build your own]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn SQL for Efficient Data Storage and Retrieval]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-sql-full-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-sql-full-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T15:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock the power of data with SQL! Master one of the most in-demand skill in the data-driven world and supercharge your career with our new video course. We just released a comprehensive video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will take you on a journey from understanding the basics]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart Quotes – Single Quote and Double Quotation Mark for Copy + Paste]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/smart-quotes-single-quote-and-double-quotation-mark-for-copy-paste/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/smart-quotes-single-quote-and-double-quotation-mark-for-copy-paste/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T14:31:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart quotes are commonly used punctuation marks in HTML and in writing. Knowing how to use them correctly can make a significant difference in the clarity and professionalism of your writing. So in this article, you will get access to the commonly used quotation marks out there that you can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Redux Toolkit With TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/guide-redux-toolkit-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/guide-redux-toolkit-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Redux Toolkit documentation calls the library a better way to write Redux logic for React apps and a simple and efficient toolkit for Redux development. In this article, you will learn about the Redux toolkit by building an app that tracks project issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Deepak Kumar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Wireframing? How to Go from Paper Sketches to High Fidelity Wireframes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-wireframing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-wireframing/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T22:06:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are Wireframes? Wireframes are visual representations of the structure, layout, and functionality of a website, application, or other digital product.  You typically create them during the early stages of the design process, and they provide a simplified and focused view of the user interface and user experience. You]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijelekhai Faith Olohijere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Elastic Beanstalk to Deploy a Node.js App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-elastic-beanstalk-to-deploy-node-js-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-elastic-beanstalk-to-deploy-node-js-app/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T21:34:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building and managing applications on the cloud can be a daunting task. This is especially true when it comes to handling different environments, scaling, and deploying updates.  But there's a service in AWS that can simplify this. AWS Elastic Beanstalk is here to make your life easier. It provides]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Beginner-Friendly JavaScript Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-beginner-friendly-javascript-application/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-beginner-friendly-javascript-application/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T16:05:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is a popular programming language for building web, mobile, and desktop applications.  There are many frameworks and libraries that have been built around JavaScript, with more likely being developed even as you are reading this article. If you plan to start learning JavaScript, some of them are worth]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TAPAS ADHIKARY</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[900 Free Computer Science Courses from the World’s Top Universities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-courses-top-cs-universities/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-courses-top-cs-universities/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T13:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I compiled 900 online courses offered by the 60 best universities in the world for studying computer science in 2023. I built the list using a data-driven approach. You can find my methodology below. But if you’d rather go straight to the course list, click here. Methodology]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manoel Cortes Mendez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use AI Tools To Skyrocket Your Programming Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/ai-tools-skyrocket-programming-productivity/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/ai-tools-skyrocket-programming-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rise of Artificial Intelligence (AI) in recent times has incited fear in many over losing their jobs. However, that shouldn’t be the case. On the contrary, AI is an opportunity to take your programming to the next level when used tactfully with the right knowledge, as we’ll cover today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shane Duggan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Ethical Hacking? A Cybersecurity Definition of Ethical Hackers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-ethical-hacking/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-ethical-hacking/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T00:06:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As technology continues to advance, cyber-threats are becoming the norm. Cyber-criminals are constantly trying to find ways to exploit systems and networks, all with the purpose of stealing sensitive information or causing damage. These challenges in the tech space have led to the emergence of the term ethical hacking. The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hillary Nyakundi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google's New Cybersecurity Professional Certificate Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cybersecurity-professional-certificate-by-google/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cybersecurity-professional-certificate-by-google/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T21:38:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has released a new professional certificate in Cybersecurity. The  announcement [https://blog.google/outreach-initiatives/grow-with-google/google-cybersecurity-career-certificate/]  came on May 4th, 2023 and marks the 6th topical branch in their continually expanding certificate program. It follows five other successful entry-level certificate programs in IT Support, Data Analytics, Digital Marketing & E-commerce, Project Management]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Safest Way To Hide Your API Keys When Using React]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/safest-way-hide-api-keys-react/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/safest-way-hide-api-keys-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to make sure your API keys are safe and sound when working with React? Jessica Joseph’s got you covered! She will show you the best ways to hide your API keys, from using environment variables to building your own back-end proxy server.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jessica Joseph)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning JavaScript With Imagination]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/learning-javascript-with-imagination/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/learning-javascript-with-imagination/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the story of how one little octopus, explaining one beginner’s concept, carried such weight and power for Kylo that it drove his work and led him to research something that is really quite silly. And yet, it transformed how he learned to write — and finally understand — JavaScript.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kylo Robinson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Growing Need For Effective Password Management]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/effective-password-management/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/effective-password-management/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Highlighting the advantages of self-hosted solutions over cloud-based alternatives and exploring collaborative password management and more, P demonstrates how to organize convenient and secure password management in a company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iliya Garakh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 60 With Mei Zhang: How Do You Design A Design Process?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/smashing-podcast-episode-60/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/smashing-podcast-episode-60/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re talking about the process of design. How do you build a process to enable your best work? Vitaly Friedman talks to designer Mei Zhang to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make Your May Magnificent (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-30T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May is almost here, so what better occasion could there be for some fresh and inspiring desktop and mobile wallpapers? Created with love by artists and designers from across the globe, the wallpapers in this post come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Write Better CSS By Borrowing Ideas From JavaScript Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/write-better-css-borrow-ideas-javascript-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/write-better-css-borrow-ideas-javascript-functions/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many problems with website layouts happen when we don’t write CSS with the same care we’d use when writing a JavaScript function. Let’s look at how we can borrow best practices and ideas from writing good JavaScript functions for writing CSS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yaphi Berhanu)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible Target Sizes Cheatsheet]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/accessible-tap-target-sizes-rage-taps-clicks/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/accessible-tap-target-sizes-rage-taps-clicks/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Practical guidelines to prevent rage taps and rage clicks with accessible tap targets for icons, links and buttons — on desktop and on mobile. With useful techniques and guidelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Potentially Dangerous Non-Accessibility Of Cookie Notices]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/potentially-dangerous-non-accessibility-cookie-notices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/potentially-dangerous-non-accessibility-cookie-notices/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this piece, a Web Content Accessibility Guidelines (WCAG) auditor shares some cookie banner error patterns that can massively hurt a page’s overall conformance. Let’s explore what to look out for with this omnipresent piece of the web interface.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Marcus Herrmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring The Potential Of Web Workers For Multithreading On The Web]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/potential-web-workers-multithreading-web/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/potential-web-workers-multithreading-web/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Sarah Oke Okolo explores the importance of Web Workers for multithreading on the web, including the limitations and considerations of using them and the strategies for mitigating potential issues associated with them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sarah Oke Okolo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building And Dockerizing A Node.js App With Stateless Architecture With Help From Kinsta]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/building-dockerizing-nodejs-app-stateless-architecture-kinsta/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/building-dockerizing-nodejs-app-stateless-architecture-kinsta/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dockerizing your Node.js apps can lead to smashing success—offering consistency, easy debugging, and hassle-free dependency management. When you host this container on Kinsta, you also benefit from high-speed performance, robust security, and top-notch scalability. By combining these two, you'll surely have a whale of a time as you sail smoothly through the development seas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tejas Kumar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Color Mechanics In UI Kits]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/color-mechanics-ui-kits/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/color-mechanics-ui-kits/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Adel Khamatov shares a model of color mechanics that he came up with during research on developing UI kits and illustrates an approach to solving related problems with best practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adel Khamatov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 59 With Chiara Aliotta: What Is Design Storytelling?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/smashing-podcast-episode-59/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/smashing-podcast-episode-59/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of The Smashing Podcast, we take a look at design storytelling. What is it, and how can it help us shape digital experiences? Vitaly talks to Chiara Aliotta to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Design Thinking?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/what-is-design-thinking/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/what-is-design-thinking/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered if things could have been done differently? But not sure how? Well, then, do not fall in love with the solution, but fall in love with the problem! Here’s an article to dive deep into how design thinking could do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Krithika Subramanian)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passkeys: What the Heck and Why?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377305</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/passkeys-what-the-heck-and-why/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T17:41:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These things called passkeys sure are making the rounds these days. They were a main attraction at W3C TPAC 2022, gained support in Safari 16, are finding their way into macOS and iOS, and are slated to …
Passkeys: What the Heck and Why? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Neal Fennimore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Design An Effective User Onboarding Flow]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/design-effective-user-onboarding-flow/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/design-effective-user-onboarding-flow/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to maximize conversions or collect necessary user information for other purposes, a user onboarding flow is necessary. In this article, you will learn how, with the help of Feathery, to design an effective user onboarding flow for your app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Suzanne Scacca)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>