<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-03-02T00:09:32.339Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-03-02T00:09:32.339Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Lists in Python – Explained with Example Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-lists-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-lists-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T20:02:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Python, lists are a cornerstones of data organization and manipulation – so I think they deserve a thorough exploration.  This article delves into how to create and manipulate lists in Python, some advanced functionalities, and some practical applications of lists. You can get all the source code from]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caching vs Content Delivery Networks – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/caching-vs-content-delivery-network/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/caching-vs-content-delivery-network/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T19:27:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of network optimization, Content Delivery Networks (CDNs) and caching play a vital role in improving website performance and user experience.  And while both aim to speed up website loading times, they have distinct purposes and mechanisms.  In this tutorial, we'll dive deep into the details]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anamika Ahmed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Compress Files to ".gz" on the Windows Operating System]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-convert-files-to-gzip-on-windows/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-convert-files-to-gzip-on-windows/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T19:15:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may often need to compress files and folders for various reasons. And "Gzip" compression is a good choice for many scenarios.  Recently, I have faced an issue where I needed to compress a lot of files individually, and manual intervention to compress each file one by one using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast – AI and the Future of Education with Seth Goldin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-ai-and-the-future-of-education-with-seth-goldin/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-ai-and-the-future-of-education-with-seth-goldin/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T17:47:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson discusses AI and the future of education with Seth Goldin.  Among other things, Seth is co-founder of College Compendium, an education charity, and studies computer science at Yale. Also, the quote Quincy mentioned during the conversation about AI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern CSS Tooltips And Speech Bubbles (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/modern-css-tooltips-speech-bubbles-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/modern-css-tooltips-speech-bubbles-part1/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tooltips are a very common pattern used in CSS for years. There are a lot of ways to approach tooltips in CSS, though some evoke headaches with all the magic numbers they require. In this article, Temani Afif presents modern techniques to create tooltips with the smallest amount of markup and the greatest amount of flexibility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn React – A Handbook for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-for-beginners-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-for-beginners-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T00:34:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The goal of this handbook is to provide gentle step-by-step instructions that will help you learn the key concepts of React. Instead of covering all the theories and concepts of React in their entirety, I'll be teaching you important building blocks of the library. You'll learn about JSX, components, props,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Methods in Java – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-methods/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-methods/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T20:05:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Methods are essential for organizing Java projects, encouraging code reuse, and improving overall code structure.  In this article, we will look at what Java methods are and how they work, including their syntax, types, and examples. Here's what we'll cover:  1. What are Java Methods?  2. Types]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Syslog Handbook – How to Collect and Redirect Logs to a Remote Server]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-syslog-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-syslog-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T19:40:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're in information technology, you'll likely agree that logging is important. It helps you monitor a system, troubleshoot issues, and generally provides useful feedback about the system’s state. But it’s important to do logging right. In this handbook, I'll explain what the syslog protocol is and how it works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Serhii Orlivskyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Gemini Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-gemini-course-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-gemini-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T18:47:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Gemini is a cutting edge AI model that is a competitor of GPT-4.  We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you harness the power of the advanced AI technology. Developed by the popular instructor Ania Kubów, this beginner's course offers a deep]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Machine Learning in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-machine-learning-in-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-machine-learning-in-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T17:38:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you curious about machine learning but don't know where to start? We just published a comprehensive Machine Learning course on the freeCodeCamp.org  that will teach you how to get started in 2024. Whether you're aspiring to become a Data Scientist, a Machine Learning Engineer (MLE), a Product Manager, or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Mobile Quiz App with React Native, ChatGPT and Supabase]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-mobile-quiz-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-mobile-quiz-app/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T17:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you'll learn how to build a mobile quiz application that authenticates users, allows them to take tests, and ranks them based on their scores.  The application leverages some of Supabase's features, such as authentication and database storage, to build a secured full-stack mobile application. Additionally, you'll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Asaolu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Waiting For Spring (March 2024 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-march-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-march-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new batch of desktop wallpapers is for you. Designed by artists and designers from across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar for March 2024. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reporting Core Web Vitals With The Performance API]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/reporting-core-web-vitals-performance-api/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/reporting-core-web-vitals-performance-api/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Performance API is a set of standards for measuring and evaluating performance metrics with JavaScript. This article demonstrates how to use the Performance API to generate performance metrics directly in the DOM to create your own reporting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Web Designer’s Accessibility Advocacy Toolkit]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/web-designer-accessibility-advocacy-toolkit/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/web-designer-accessibility-advocacy-toolkit/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital designer Yichan Wang has put together this collection of strategies and selling points to help you encourage and advocate for accessibility in your place of work, including useful scripts you can use as starting points.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yichan Wang)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vanilla JavaScript, Libraries, And The Quest For Stateful DOM Rendering]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/vanilla-javascript-libraries-quest-stateful-dom-rendering/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/vanilla-javascript-libraries-quest-stateful-dom-rendering/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s well-established that the web faces wide-ranging usability and performance issues, from user-hostile UI patterns and twisted search results to sluggish performance and battery-draining bloat. In this article, Frederik examines one small-but-significant aspect where developers take the reins: Painting pixels on the screen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederik Dohr)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Practical Guide To Designing For Colorblind People]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/designing-for-colorblindness/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/designing-for-colorblindness/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Color accessibility is more than just ticking boxes. Even with good contrast, some color palettes can make interfaces challenging for users. Here are some practical guidelines to ensure more inclusive design for colorblind people. An upcoming part of Smart Interface Design Patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile Accessibility Barriers For Assistive Technology Users]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/mobile-accessibility-barriers-assistive-technology-users/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/mobile-accessibility-barriers-assistive-technology-users/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility goes beyond making products user-friendly. It can significantly impact the quality of life for people with disabilities. Kate Kalcevich shares lessons she learned from assistive technology users — challenges and barriers they encounter on mobile devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kate Kalcevich)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Accessibility Standards Can Empower Better Chart Visual Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/accessibility-standards-empower-better-chart-visual-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/accessibility-standards-empower-better-chart-visual-design/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility for data visualization extends well beyond web standards, at least if you’re trying to create an experience that’s actually useful. This article focuses on techniques for creating useful and accessible visualizations that extend well beyond compliance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kent Eisenhuth)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Practical Guide To Designing For Children]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/practical-guide-design-children/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/practical-guide-design-children/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to design for children aged 3–12, with insights into user behavior, considerations for parents, and practical UX guidelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Draw Radar Charts In Web]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/draw-radar-charts-web/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/draw-radar-charts-web/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A radar chart — also commonly called a spider chart — is yet another way to visualize data and make connections. Radar charts are inherently geometric, making them both a perfect fit and fun to make with CSS, thanks to the `polygon()` function. Read along as Preethi Sam demonstrates the process and sprinkles it with a pinch of JavaScript to make a handy, reusable component.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Preethi Sam)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frequently Heard In My Beginning Front-End Web Development Class]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/frequently-heard-beginning-front-end-web-development-class/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/frequently-heard-beginning-front-end-web-development-class/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What could we learn from entry-level students in front-end web development? As seasoned professionals, you might think you’ve seen it all, but the truth is that the newcomers are asking the most intriguing questions and making connections that those of us who have spent years on the front end may have never considered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Development Is Getting Too Complex, And It May Be Our Fault]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/web-development-getting-too-complex/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/web-development-getting-too-complex/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An overwhelming number of frameworks and tooling available today gives the impression that web development has gotten perhaps too complex. Juan Diego Rodríguez explores if web development really is that complex and, most importantly, how we can prevent it from getting even more difficult than we already perceive it to be.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Designing For Older Adults]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/guide-designing-older-adults/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/guide-designing-older-adults/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With one billion people aged 60 or older worldwide, inclusivity is more important than ever. Learn how to create digital experiences that empower independence and competence for older adults while enhancing usability for all. An upcoming part of Smart Interface Design Patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Words Cannot Describe: Designing For AI Beyond Conversational Interfaces]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/designing-ai-beyond-conversational-interfaces/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/designing-ai-beyond-conversational-interfaces/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Artificial Intelligence evolves the computing paradigm, designers have an opportunity to craft more intuitive user interfaces. Maximillian Piras examines how the latest AI capabilities can reshape the future of human-computer interaction beyond conversation alone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Maximillian Piras)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>