<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-08-10T00:10:50.906Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-08-10T00:10:50.906Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Minimum Stability In Composer?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-minimum-stability-in-composer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-minimum-stability-in-composer/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T17:31:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Composer is a dependency management tool for projects running on PHP. PHP frameworks like Laravel, Symfony, and CodeIgniter use Composer to manage libraries and packages. In this tutorial, you’ll learn the following:  * Introduction to Composer.  * Minimum stability in Composer.  * Levels of stability, and the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sule-Balogun Olanrewaju Ganiu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering End-to-End Testing with Cypress for JavaScript Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mastering-end-to-end-testing-with-cypress-for-javascript-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mastering-end-to-end-testing-with-cypress-for-javascript-applications/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T16:58:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ensuring the reliability and performance of your web applications is important. Testing is a key tool that will help with these things and more.  We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Cypress to create end-to-end tests for your JavaScript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering JavaScript Functions for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mastering-javascript-functions-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mastering-javascript-functions-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T16:40:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you new to the world of programming? Are you eager to unlock the potential of JavaScript to create more readable and maintainable code? If so, we have an excellent course for you. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you everything you need]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy Your Websites and Apps – User-Friendly Deployment Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-websites-and-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-websites-and-applications/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T14:23:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying your application is a key aspect of software development. Typically, having an app on your local system isn't enough – it needs to be accessible online. So choosing a suitable and user-friendly hosting and deployment plan is vital. The key to making the right decision lies in understanding the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijeoma Igboagu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy a Django App on Render]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploying-a-django-app-to-render/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploying-a-django-app-to-render/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T14:13:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Render is a hosting platform that helps you deploy your apps easily. Whether you're building web servers, static websites, cron jobs, or containers, this tool can help you streamline the process. If you're a developer early in your career and you need to build a compelling CV, résumé, or portfolio,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Iroegbu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Find Good First Issues On GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-find-good-first-issues-on-github/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-find-good-first-issues-on-github/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T23:31:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So you may have been hearing about OpenSauced’s 100 Days of Open Source challenge [https://docs.opensauced.pizza/community/100-days-of-oss/] on X (Twitter) or from your friends in an online coding group. And maybe you want to join in but don’t know where to start.  Ooh, I know the feeling. When I first joined]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CHRISTINE T. BELZIE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a JavaScript Utility Library like Lodash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-javascript-utility-library-like-lodash/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-javascript-utility-library-like-lodash/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T21:15:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A utility library is a library that helps you streamline the implementation of common coding tasks. With it, you only need to focus on writing code that makes your project unique. One of the most popular JavaScript utility libraries is Lodash. Lodash is a JS library with over 40 million]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gideon Akinsanmi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add ESLint to Your React Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-eslint-to-your-react-project/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-eslint-to-your-react-project/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T16:36:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a React developer, maintaining code quality is essential for building robust and maintainable applications. Fortunately, there's a powerful tool called ESLint that can significantly improve the quality of your React projects. In this article, we will explore how ESLint works and create a sign-up button component to demonstrate its]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isah Jacob</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Web APIs in Your Coding Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-apis-in-web-development/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-apis-in-web-development/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T16:27:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a developer, what comes to mind when you hear the word "API"? For me, I think of the word "connector", something that connects one thing to another.  So, what exactly is an API? API stands for Application Programming Interface [/news/how-apis-work/]. APIs connect different software applications, websites, and web]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juliet Ofoegbu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Application Performance Monitoring for Node.js Applications Using Elastic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-monitoring-for-nodejs-applications-using-elastic/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-monitoring-for-nodejs-applications-using-elastic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T20:57:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building features is half the equation of creating a successful product.  The other half is making something scalable and maintainable. One aspect of that is the ability to monitor your services.  This is what we will learn today using the help of software provided by Elastic. This is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tamerlan Gudabayev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Friction As A Feature In Machine Learning Algorithms]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/friction-feature-machine-learning-algorithms/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/friction-feature-machine-learning-algorithms/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Friction often has a negative connotation in user experience design, but it actually has many benefits. Its best-known use case is mitigating unintended consequences in high-risk scenarios, yet it has a new place in the age of artificial intelligence. Adding strategic friction to interfaces can lead to profound efficiency gains in machine learning algorithms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Maximillian Piras)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Accessible Text Over Images: Best Practices, Techniques, And Resources (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/designing-accessible-text-over-images-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/designing-accessible-text-over-images-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this two-part series of articles, Hannah Milan covers the best practices when using various accessible text over images techniques for designing your web and mobile app content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Hannah Milan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Optimized Performance To Serve A Global Audience]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/optimize-performance-serve-global-audience/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/optimize-performance-serve-global-audience/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liran Cohen and the team at Bookaway, a travel booking service, dramatically improved their site’s performance by auditing Core Web Vitals. In this article, Liran shares his team’s process for auditing and monitoring Web Vitals and the effort it took to dramatically improve Bookaway’s performance — and the benefits that came with it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Liran Cohen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 64 With Alvin Bryan: What Is A Headless CMS?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/smashing-podcast-episode-64/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/smashing-podcast-episode-64/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re talking about headless content management systems. What are they, and how do they differ from more traditional systems? Drew McLellan talks to Alvin Bryan to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS And Accessibility: Inclusion Through User Choice]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/css-accessibility-inclusion-user-choice/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/css-accessibility-inclusion-user-choice/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Carie Fisher outlines which CSS media features are available for detecting user preferences and how they are used to design and build more inclusive user experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carie Fisher)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Living In The Moment (August 2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T09:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New month, new wallpapers! In this post, you’ll find unique and inspiring wallpapers for August 2023. Created with love by the community for the community, they come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Define An Array Of Colors With CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/define-array-colors-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/define-array-colors-css/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join Temani Afif on experiment with modern CSS features to create an array of colors. The goal is to define a comma-separated list of colors and iterate through them using an index.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use Artificial Intelligence And Machine Learning To Summarize Chat Conversations]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/artificial-intelligence-machine-learning-summarize-chat-conversations/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/artificial-intelligence-machine-learning-summarize-chat-conversations/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll explore how to build a chat summarizer using the Cohere API and deploy it as a web application using Gradio.[ Cohere](https://cohere.com/) is an AI platform that provides state-of-the-art natural language processing models for a variety of tasks, including summarization. We’ll cover the steps involved in training the summarizer using sample chat conversations, interacting with the Cohere API to generate summaries, and creating a user-friendly interface using [Gradio](https://www.gradio.app/).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joas Pambou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern Technology And The Future Of Language Translation]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/modern-technology-future-language-translation/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/modern-technology-future-language-translation/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The field of language translation has never been more exciting. Explore the evolution of language translation platforms, how we got to where we are today, and what advancements we can look forward to in the coming years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adriano Raiano)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recreating YouTube’s Ambient Mode Glow Effect]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/recreating-youtube-ambient-mode-glow-effect/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/recreating-youtube-ambient-mode-glow-effect/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Adrian deconstructs YouTube’s “Ambient Mode” feature and how HTML `` and the `requestAnimationFrame` function are used to create the glowing effect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Art Of Looking Back: A Critical Reflection For Individual Contributors]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/critical-reflection-individual-contributors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/critical-reflection-individual-contributors/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover the importance of critical reflective practice and challenge some beliefs about reflection and its role in our work and growth. Kristian Mikhel suggests a critical reflective routine for individual contributors and gives some practical recommendations that will make reflection meaningful and actionable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kristian Mikhel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Age-Inclusive Products: Guidelines And Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/designing-age-inclusive-products-guidelines-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/designing-age-inclusive-products-guidelines-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With an estimated one in every eight individuals worldwide surpassing the age of 60, who are actively adopting online shopping, the need for user-friendly interfaces tailored to their needs becomes apparent. Explore the guidelines to help you design inclusive products for all, particularly for an older audience and your future self.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michal Halperin Ben Zvi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writing CSS In 2023: Is It Any Different Than A Few Years Ago?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/writing-css-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/writing-css-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS is evolving faster than ever. With all of the new features that are now available — and forthcoming — since we got Flexbox and Grid years ago, the way we write CSS is evolving, too. In this article, Geoff Graham shares which features have had the most influence on his current approaches to CSS, as well as those that have not (at least yet).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create A Rapid Research Program To Support Insights At Scale]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/create-rapid-research-program-support-insights-scale/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/create-rapid-research-program-support-insights-scale/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate your organization’s growth and innovation with the power of Rapid Research. From inception to implementation, here is the step-by-step roadmap on how to build the program from scratch and uncover the untapped ROI opportunities waiting to propel your initiatives to new heights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Devin Harold)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>