<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-09-16T00:09:07.024Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-09-16T00:09:07.024Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Disney Data Scientist Eric Leung on Math, Medicine, and Learning to Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-data-scientist-at-disney-eric-leung-on-math-medicine-and-learning-to-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/podcast-data-scientist-at-disney-eric-leung-on-math-medicine-and-learning-to-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T20:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I'm joined by Eric Leung, Data Scientist at Disney and long-time open source contributor to freeCodeCamp. Eric Leung grew up in Oklahoma and learned a lot of math in high school. His friends wanted to go to medical school and he originally planned to join them. But instead]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the Solana Curriculum: Smart Contracts, dApps, and Command Line Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/solana-curriculum/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/solana-curriculum/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Solana Curriculum is live. You can now learn Solana's blockchain protocol and the Solana tool ecosystem interactively by building a series of projects. This curriculum is made possible by The Solana Foundation, who gave our charity a grant to 100% fund development of this curriculum. What will this curriculum]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Mondloch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Quick Look at Bun 1.0 – The Node.js Alternative]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-quick-look-at-bun-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-quick-look-at-bun-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T07:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A wise man once told me, "When you start eating Bun, Node.js will feel bland". But why is that relevant? JavaScript got way faster with a new JavaScript runtime called Bun, which is now production-ready with its version 1.0 release. But how and why is it faster than Node.js? A]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nishant Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revealing Images With CSS Mask Animations]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/revealing-images-css-mask-animations/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/revealing-images-css-mask-animations/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s play with images and experiment with CSS masks. The idea is fairly simple: take a single `` tag and harness the power of CSS to accomplish complex hover transitions. Through different demos, you will see how CSS masks combined with gradients allow us to create fancy effects — with efficient, reusable code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Contribute to Open Source Projects – Non-Technical Things You Should Know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-contribute-to-open-source/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-contribute-to-open-source/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T17:34:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've contributed to open-source projects for a few years and learned a lot from the process. These experiences allowed me to look closer at the open source flow, from the technical, such as Git and GitHub, to the non-technical aspects. Although they are as important as the technical sides, the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ayu Adiati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Return Results from a Python Function to Your Program When a Library is Blocking the Way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/return-results-from-a-python-function-when-library-is-blocking-the-way/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/return-results-from-a-python-function-when-library-is-blocking-the-way/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T10:46:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Usually a Python function passes its results back using a return statement. The problem is that sometimes it can't, so you need to figure out a different way to return those results.  This happens, most often, when someone else's library's interface is in the way, and you can't change]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David A. Kra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Vector Embeddings to Create an AI Assistant]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vector-embeddings-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vector-embeddings-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T02:18:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vector embeddings are a key concept in the realm of machine learning and artificial intelligence. They bridge the gap between human language and machine understanding. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach out about vector embeddings and how to create an AI assistant. Ania]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Dynamic Programming Techniques in Java]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-dynamic-programming-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-dynamic-programming-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T02:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic programming is a powerful technique that has been a cornerstone in the world of algorithms and computer science. It's a method that breaks down problems into smaller, more manageable sub-problems, solving each one only once and storing their solutions in case they're needed again. This approach is particularly useful]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Things to Consider When Picking Fonts for your Next Project – An In-Depth Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/things-to-consider-when-picking-fonts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/things-to-consider-when-picking-fonts/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T11:18:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the modern web, we've normalized fetching fonts from client-side, or embedding fonts in resources that are served to users. While this may be tempting, it actually makes very little sense for most use-cases. This isn't suggesting to never use external fonts. Just a reminder that fonts aren't free, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Falco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facilitating Inclusive Online Workshops (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/facilitating-inclusive-online-workshops-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/facilitating-inclusive-online-workshops-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Running a workshop can be an effective alternative to traditional, long-standing meetings. To help ensure its success, Ben Shih introduces the concept of an inclusive workshop. In Part 1 of the series, you discover the fundamentals of inclusivity and get some solid guidance on how to plan an inclusive remote workshop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ben Shih)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fine-Tune the Donut Model – With Example Use Case]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fine-tune-the-donut-model/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fine-tune-the-donut-model/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T17:59:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Donut model in Python is a model you can use to extract text from a given image. This can be useful in various scenarios, like scanning receipts, for example.  You can easily download the Donut model from GitHub [https://github.com/clovaai/donut]. But as is common with AI models, you should]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eivind Kjosbakken</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[13 Types of Cyber Attacks You Should Know in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/types-of-cyber-attacks-to-know/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/types-of-cyber-attacks-to-know/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T17:28:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2023, the digital landscape is filled with unprecedented cybersecurity risks. From phishing scams to ransomware attacks. This article outlines different types of cyber attacks that individuals and businesses should be vigilant about. Cyber-attacks are a prevalent threat in the online world. They have the potential to cause substantial difficulties]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gradients, Blend Modes, And A Really Cool Hover Effect]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/gradients-blend-modes-hover-effect/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/gradients-blend-modes-hover-effect/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gradients are a powerful CSS feature. We use them for texture, depth, and even to hide parts of elements with CSS masking. This article covers another interesting way to use gradients — as a hover effect that affects the appearance of other elements around the hovered element.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Preethi Sam)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rediscovering The Joy Of Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/rediscovering-joy-happiness-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/rediscovering-joy-happiness-design/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pratik Joglekar takes a philosophical approach to remind designers about the lost joy within themselves by effectively placing massive importance on mindfulness, introspection, and forward-looking. Without joy, the work we do would feel meaningless. To prevent it from happening, check out a few ideas that would help rediscover that spark of joy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Pratik Joglekar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Long Live The Test Pyramid]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/long-live-test-pyramid/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/long-live-test-pyramid/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is the Test Pyramid really dead? Discover the more contemporary testing strategies and evaluate the Test Pyramid’s relevance in today’s software development practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ramona Schwering)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generating Real-Time Audio Sentiment Analysis With AI]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/generating-real-time-audio-sentiment-analysis-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/09/generating-real-time-audio-sentiment-analysis-ai/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Joas Pambou builds the tool to provide a sentiment score in **real-time** with enhanced user experience by providing multilingual support. You will use an OpenAI library called Whisper that transcribes audio files into text and detects the language, and Gradio, a UI framework, to establish the interface.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joas Pambou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A September Of Never Ending Adventures (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-september-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-september-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T08:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s get ready for September with some fresh wallpaper designs! Created with love by artists and designers from across the globe, the wallpapers in this collection come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Falling For Oklch: A Love Story Of Color Spaces, Gamuts, And CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/oklch-color-spaces-gamuts-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/oklch-color-spaces-gamuts-css/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS Color Module Level 4 specification defined a slew of new color features when it became a candidate recommendation in 2022, including Oklab and Oklch, which have widened the field of color we have to work with. Explore the Oklch color space and how to start using it in CSS today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Double Diamond Design Process]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/improving-double-diamond-design-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/improving-double-diamond-design-process/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The so-called “Double Diamond” is a great way of visualizing an ideal design process — but it’s just not the way most companies deliver new projects or services. Andy Budd proposes a new “Double Diamond” idea that better aligns with the way work actually gets done and highlights the place where design has the most leverage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andy Budd)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Few Interesting Ways To Use CSS Shadows For More Than Depth]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/interesting-ways-use-css-shadows/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/interesting-ways-use-css-shadows/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We often think of shadows in CSS as something to reach for when we want to add depth to a design. But shadows can be used for more than depth. Let’s experiment with different shadows — two CSS properties and a filter — to make interesting hover effects, different text styles, and even casting shadows on other shadows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Preethi Sam)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better Context Menus With Safe Triangles]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/better-context-menus-safe-triangles/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/better-context-menus-safe-triangles/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how to improve the user experience of nested menus and tackle a minor yet common issue with them when the user’s pointer leaves the menu item for a moment, and the nested menu goes away, requiring the user to re-hover and try again. A well-known concept called the “safe triangle” solves this problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Costa Alexoglou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>