<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-05-16T00:09:47.642Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-05-16T00:09:47.642Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Networking in Flutter By Building a Simple App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-networking-in-flutter/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-networking-in-flutter/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T18:42:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Almost all apps you use today run by accessing the internet. You can hardly find an app that runs without connecting to the internet.  The internet has become an integral part of our lives, as it solves one of the most critical problems we have to handle: data transfer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caching in React – How to Use the useMemo and useCallback Hooks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/caching-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/caching-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T18:39:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As React developers become more proficient with the library, the topic of performance becomes a major focal point in their development process.  As with any tool or programming methodology, caching plays a huge role when it comes to optimizing React applications. Caching in React typically goes by the term]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Gary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the 60-30-10 Rule in Design? And How to Use it in Your Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-60-30-10-rule-in-design/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-60-30-10-rule-in-design/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T17:20:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As designers, colour is a huge component of our work. But many of us struggle with the usage of colours in our designs.  In this article, you will learn about the 60-30-10 colour rule, how it's used, and see a practical example of it. What is the 60-30-10 rule?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijelekhai Faith Olohijere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Secure Your MERN Stack App with JWT-Based User Authentication and Authorization]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-secure-your-mern-stack-application/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-secure-your-mern-stack-application/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T17:15:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MongoDB [https://www.mongodb.com/docs/], Express [https://expressjs.com/en/starter/installing.html], React [https://react.dev/learn], and Node.js [https://nodejs.org/en/docs] are the components of the MERN stack, one of the most widely used web development stacks out there today. The MERN stack enables programmers to create dependable web applications with strong capabilities. Yet, security should be a key concern with any]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FADAHUNSI SEYI SAMUEL</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Method Overloading Works in PHP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/method-overloading-in-php/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/method-overloading-in-php/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T17:11:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As software engineers, we sometimes have to perform certain tasks that can be achieved with a variable number of inputs.  To solve this problem, you can create multiple functions to solve for the different possible number of inputs. Or we can write a large function to solve this problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zubair Idris Aweda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Clean Code – Tips and Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-clean-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-clean-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T14:43:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article we're going to talk about writing "clean" code. It's a topic that used to confuse me a bit when I was starting out as a programmer, and I find that it has many nuances and possible interpretations. So in this article we'll talk about what]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solving Media Object Float Issues With CSS Block Formatting Contexts]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/media-object-float-issues-css-block-formatting-contexts/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/media-object-float-issues-css-block-formatting-contexts/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article covers common problems using CSS floats and how to solve them using a block formatting context (BFC). Whether you are a beginner or an experienced web developer, you will learn valuable insights and practical solutions for dealing with CSS float issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Gabriel Shoyombo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[URL RegEx Pattern – How to Write a Regular Expression for a URL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-a-regular-expression-for-a-url/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-a-regular-expression-for-a-url/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T12:22:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regular expressions provide a powerful and flexible way to define patterns and match specific strings, be it usernames, passwords, phone numbers, or even URLs. In this article, I'll show you the fundamentals of crafting a regular expression for URLs. Whether you need to validate user input, extract components from URLs,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced Indexing Strategies in PostgreSQL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/postgresql-indexing-strategies/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/postgresql-indexing-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T20:46:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Indexing in PostgreSQL is a process that involves creating data structures that are optimized to efficiently search and retrieve data from tables.  An index is a copy of a portion of a table, arranged in a way that enables PostgreSQL to quickly locate and retrieve rows that match a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Faith Oyama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Greedy Algorithm? Examples of Greedy Algorithms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/greedy-algorithms/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/greedy-algorithms/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T17:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the Oxford English Dictionary, "greedy" means having excessive desire for something without considering the effect or damage done.  In computer science, a greedy algorithm is an algorithm that finds a solution to problems in the shortest time possible. It picks the path that seems optimal at the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tantoluwa Heritage Alabi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does a Linked List Work? A Beginner's Guide to Linked Lists]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-linked-lists-work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-linked-lists-work/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T17:45:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Linked List is a linear data structure used for storing a collection of elements. Unlike arrays, linked lists use nodes to store elements which are not stored in contiguous memory locations.  In this article, you will learn what linked lists are, how they work, and how to build]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Palistha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Sticky Menus: UX Guidelines]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/sticky-menus-ux-guidelines/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/sticky-menus-ux-guidelines/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are sticky headers always a good idea? Best practices for designing sticky headers, with examples, UX guidelines and usability considerations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Boost Your Design Workflow With Setapp]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/boost-design-workflow-setapp/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/boost-design-workflow-setapp/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, we’ll explore efficient tools to save time and speed up your workflow. Focus on what you do best — designing high-quality work, and let these tools handle the rest!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Rachel How)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Redux Toolkit With TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/guide-redux-toolkit-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/guide-redux-toolkit-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Redux Toolkit documentation calls the library a better way to write Redux logic for React apps and a simple and efficient toolkit for Redux development. In this article, you will learn about the Redux toolkit by building an app that tracks project issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Deepak Kumar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use AI Tools To Skyrocket Your Programming Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/ai-tools-skyrocket-programming-productivity/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/ai-tools-skyrocket-programming-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rise of Artificial Intelligence (AI) in recent times has incited fear in many over losing their jobs. However, that shouldn’t be the case. On the contrary, AI is an opportunity to take your programming to the next level when used tactfully with the right knowledge, as we’ll cover today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shane Duggan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Safest Way To Hide Your API Keys When Using React]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/safest-way-hide-api-keys-react/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/safest-way-hide-api-keys-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to make sure your API keys are safe and sound when working with React? Jessica Joseph’s got you covered! She will show you the best ways to hide your API keys, from using environment variables to building your own back-end proxy server.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jessica Joseph)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning JavaScript With Imagination]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/learning-javascript-with-imagination/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/learning-javascript-with-imagination/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the story of how one little octopus, explaining one beginner’s concept, carried such weight and power for Kylo that it drove his work and led him to research something that is really quite silly. And yet, it transformed how he learned to write — and finally understand — JavaScript.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kylo Robinson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Growing Need For Effective Password Management]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/effective-password-management/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/effective-password-management/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Highlighting the advantages of self-hosted solutions over cloud-based alternatives and exploring collaborative password management and more, P demonstrates how to organize convenient and secure password management in a company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iliya Garakh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 60 With Mei Zhang: How Do You Design A Design Process?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/smashing-podcast-episode-60/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/smashing-podcast-episode-60/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re talking about the process of design. How do you build a process to enable your best work? Vitaly Friedman talks to designer Mei Zhang to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make Your May Magnificent (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-30T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May is almost here, so what better occasion could there be for some fresh and inspiring desktop and mobile wallpapers? Created with love by artists and designers from across the globe, the wallpapers in this post come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Write Better CSS By Borrowing Ideas From JavaScript Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/write-better-css-borrow-ideas-javascript-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/write-better-css-borrow-ideas-javascript-functions/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many problems with website layouts happen when we don’t write CSS with the same care we’d use when writing a JavaScript function. Let’s look at how we can borrow best practices and ideas from writing good JavaScript functions for writing CSS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yaphi Berhanu)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible Target Sizes Cheatsheet]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/accessible-tap-target-sizes-rage-taps-clicks/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/accessible-tap-target-sizes-rage-taps-clicks/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Practical guidelines to prevent rage taps and rage clicks with accessible tap targets for icons, links and buttons — on desktop and on mobile. With useful techniques and guidelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Potentially Dangerous Non-Accessibility Of Cookie Notices]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/potentially-dangerous-non-accessibility-cookie-notices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/potentially-dangerous-non-accessibility-cookie-notices/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this piece, a Web Content Accessibility Guidelines (WCAG) auditor shares some cookie banner error patterns that can massively hurt a page’s overall conformance. Let’s explore what to look out for with this omnipresent piece of the web interface.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Marcus Herrmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring The Potential Of Web Workers For Multithreading On The Web]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/potential-web-workers-multithreading-web/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/potential-web-workers-multithreading-web/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Sarah Oke Okolo explores the importance of Web Workers for multithreading on the web, including the limitations and considerations of using them and the strategies for mitigating potential issues associated with them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sarah Oke Okolo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building And Dockerizing A Node.js App With Stateless Architecture With Help From Kinsta]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/building-dockerizing-nodejs-app-stateless-architecture-kinsta/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/building-dockerizing-nodejs-app-stateless-architecture-kinsta/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dockerizing your Node.js apps can lead to smashing success—offering consistency, easy debugging, and hassle-free dependency management. When you host this container on Kinsta, you also benefit from high-speed performance, robust security, and top-notch scalability. By combining these two, you'll surely have a whale of a time as you sail smoothly through the development seas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tejas Kumar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Color Mechanics In UI Kits]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/color-mechanics-ui-kits/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/color-mechanics-ui-kits/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Adel Khamatov shares a model of color mechanics that he came up with during research on developing UI kits and illustrates an approach to solving related problems with best practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adel Khamatov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 59 With Chiara Aliotta: What Is Design Storytelling?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/smashing-podcast-episode-59/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/smashing-podcast-episode-59/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of The Smashing Podcast, we take a look at design storytelling. What is it, and how can it help us shape digital experiences? Vitaly talks to Chiara Aliotta to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Design Thinking?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/what-is-design-thinking/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/what-is-design-thinking/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered if things could have been done differently? But not sure how? Well, then, do not fall in love with the solution, but fall in love with the problem! Here’s an article to dive deep into how design thinking could do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Krithika Subramanian)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>