<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-09-15T00:12:28.754Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-09-15T00:12:28.754Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Evaluate Machine Learning Models using TensorBoard with TensorFlow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-evaluate-machine-learning-models-using-tensorboard/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-evaluate-machine-learning-models-using-tensorboard/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T18:31:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Improving a Machine Learning model is an iterative process. No machine learning model is ever perfect on the first attempt at training it. It usually takes a few iterations.  But a common mistake you might make as a Machine Learning practitioner is failing to realize that you need to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Salim Oyinlola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn HTML and CSS from the CEO of Scrimba]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-html-and-css-from-the-ceo-of-scrimba/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-html-and-css-from-the-ceo-of-scrimba/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T18:15:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Almost every website in the world uses HTML and CSS. So you should definitely learn them if you want to create websites. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build websites with HTML and CSS. Per Borgan created this course. Per]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel Security Check Failure – How to Restart the Kernel in Windows 10]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/kernel-security-check-failure-how-to-restart-the-kernel-in-windows-10/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/kernel-security-check-failure-how-to-restart-the-kernel-in-windows-10/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T15:41:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been a professional software engineer for many years, and I can testify that there are few things worse than getting the dreaded BSOD (Blue Screen of Death). Especially when you are about to write a piece of mind bending code at 2am to meet a looming deadline.  That’s]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gavin Lon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What I Learned Teaching 20 High School Girls How to Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-i-learned-teaching-20-hs-girls-to-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-i-learned-teaching-20-hs-girls-to-code/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T14:46:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On day 1, they barely knew what a float was. On day 14, they had programmed a game of minesweeper, a cipher decoder, or a zombie apocalypse simulation. And I helped teach them how to do it. Each summer, MIT hosts a program called WTP, or Women's Technology Program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kylie Ying</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When is it OK to Disable Text Selection?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373100</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/when-is-it-ok-to-disable-text-selection/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T13:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using CSS, it’s possible to prevent users from selecting text within an element using user-select: none. Now, it’s understandable why doing so might be considered “controversial”. I mean, should we be disabling standard user behaviors? Generally speaking, no, we …
When is it OK to Disable Text Selection? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Schwarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript APIs You Don’t Know About]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/javascript-api-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/javascript-api-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Juan Diego covers the least known yet extremely useful APIs, such as the Page Visibility API, Web Sharing API, Broadcast Channel API and Internationalization API. Together we will see what they are, where we should use them, and how to use them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL vs NoSQL: When to Use Which]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-vs-nosql-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-vs-nosql-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T03:38:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When should you use a SQL database and when should you use a NoSQL database? We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you the differences between NoSQL and SQL databases as well as when and why to use each kind of database. Ania Kubow]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Static Markdown Blog with Deno and Deploy It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-blog-with-deno/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-blog-with-deno/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T16:46:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deno is a runtime for JavaScript and TypeScript. The creator of Node.js built it, and while Node is built with C and C++, Deno is built with the Rust language. You might be wondering what some of the main differences between Node and Deno are. Well, Rust is a low-level]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebKit Features in Safari 16.0]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373367</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/webkit-features-in-safari-16-0/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T16:14:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whew boy, Safari 16 is officially out in the wild and it packs in a bunch of features, some new and exciting (Subgrid! Container Queries! Font Palettes!) and others we’ve been waiting on for better cross-browser support (Motion Path! Overscroll …
WebKit Features in Safari 16.0 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sort Dictionary by Value in Python – How to Sort a Dict]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sort-dictionary-by-value-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sort-dictionary-by-value-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T15:16:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Python, a dictionary is a fat structure that is unordered by default. So, sometimes, you'll want to sort dictionaries by key or value to make queries easier. The problem is that sorting a dictionary by value is never a straightforward thing to do. That’s because Python doesn’t have an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Basics of Remix]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373081</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-basics-of-remix/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T12:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve probably heard a lot of hype around one of the newest kids on the framework block, Remix. It may be surprising that it got its start back in 2019, but it was originally only available as a subscription-based premium …
The Basics of Remix originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brittney Postma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Sense Of WAI-ARIA: A Comprehensive Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/wai-aria-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/wai-aria-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Kate Kalcevich explains when to use ARIA and how to use it properly so that you can use ARIA in a way that’s helpful to the many disabled people who use [assistive technology](https://makeitfable.com/glossary/?utm_source=Smashing+Magazine&utm_medium=sponsored+content&utm_campaign=Upskill&utm_term=Fable&utm_content=Sept2022) to navigate the Internet. Let’s dive in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kate Kalcevich)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change Text Color in HTML – Font Style Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-change-text-color-in-html/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-change-text-color-in-html/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T20:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Text plays a significant role on our web pages. This is because it helps users learn what the web page is all about and what they can do there. When you add text to your web pages, this text defaults to a black color. But sometimes you will want to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the JavaScript DOM Works – A Practical Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-javascript-dom-a-practical-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-javascript-dom-a-practical-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T20:19:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you were listening to music on an app and you wanted to pause or skip a song, you'd have to do that through the app. This process is similar to how the Document Object Model or DOM works. Here, the music app represents the DOM because it serves as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ophy Boamah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Read and Write Data using Azure Databricks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-read-and-write-data-using-azure-databricks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-read-and-write-data-using-azure-databricks/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T18:49:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Databricks is a Microsoft Azure cloud service that provides a scalable platform for data analytics using Apache Spark. It is a fully managed, cloud-based data analytics platform that allows developers to create enterprise-grade data apps more quickly, which accelerates AI and innovation.  In this tutorial, you will cover]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Salim Oyinlola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Interactive Figma Widgets]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372991</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/building-interactive-figma-widgets/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T13:05:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Figma has always encouraged collaboration between developers and designers. It strives on an endless treasury of community-made plugins. Need 3D elements? There’s a plugin for that. Need abstract SVGs? There’s a plugin for that, too.
That said, the design part of Figma has …
Building Interactive Figma Widgets originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eluda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet “Smart Interface Design Patterns Checklists” (Deck With 166 Cards)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/smart-interface-design-checklist-cards-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/smart-interface-design-checklist-cards-release/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet “Smart Interface Design Patterns Checklists”, a deck of 166 checklist cards to help you design and build better interfaces, faster. With accordions, mega-drop-downs, data tables, carousels, and everything in-between.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Made a Pure CSS Puzzle Game]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372952</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-i-made-a-pure-css-puzzle-game/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T13:21:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently discovered the joy of creating CSS-only games. It’s always fascinating how HTML and CSS are capable of handling the logic of an entire online game, so I had to try it! Such games usually rely on the ol’ …
How I Made a Pure CSS Puzzle Game originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One Formula To Rule Them All: The ROI Of A Design System]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/formula-roi-design-system/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/formula-roi-design-system/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design systems are a crucial success factor for digital businesses, and virtually every major player works with one. Still, they can sometimes be hard to sell to management. Here’s a ready-to-use formula to calculate the ROI of any design system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Maximilian Speicher &amp; Guido Baena Wehrmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New With Forms in 2022?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372979</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/whats-new-with-forms-in-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T13:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Browsers are constantly adding new HTML, JavaScript and CSS features. Here are some useful additions to working with forms that you might have missed…
requestSubmit()
Safari 16 will be the final browser to add support for requestSubmit.
Before we …
What’s New With Forms in 2022? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ollie Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UX Checklists For Interface Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/ux-checklists-for-interface-designers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/ux-checklists-for-interface-designers/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UX checklists with best design practices, accessibility guidelines, design system checklist, tables UX checklist, UX research methods, form design UX and flowcharts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overlapping Bar Charts]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372968</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/overlapping-bar-charts/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T13:46:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the name suggests, overlapping charts visualize two different sets of data in a single diagram. The idea is that the overlapping bars allow us to compare data, say, year-over-year. They are also useful for things like tracking progress for …
Overlapping Bar Charts originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saleh Mubashar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Realities And Myths Of Contrast And Color]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/realities-myths-contrast-color/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/realities-myths-contrast-color/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Andrew Somers, a 35-year veteran of the Hollywood film and television industry, shares his experience about the hard-fought battles and lessons learned designing for illuminated presentations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andrew Somers)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacking CSS Animation State and Playback Time]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372850</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/hacking-css-animation-state-and-playback-time/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T18:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS-only Wolfenstein is a little project that I made a few weeks ago. It was an experiment with CSS 3D transformations and animations.
Inspired by the FPS demo and another Wolfenstein CodePen, I decided to build my own version. …
Hacking CSS Animation State and Playback Time originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lu Wang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 52 With Yiying Lu: How Do You Become An NFT Artist?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/smashing-podcast-episode-52/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/smashing-podcast-episode-52/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we ask how do you go from running a creative studio to designing NFTs. Vitaly talks to artist Yiying Lu to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flutter For Front-End Web Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372853</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/flutter-for-front-end-web-developers/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T20:10:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I started as a front-end web developer and then became a Flutter developer. I think there were some concepts that helped me adopt Flutter easier. There were also some new concepts that were different.
In this article, I want to …
Flutter For Front-End Web Developers originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Obumuneme Nwabude</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Understanding Privacy, A New Smashing Book By Heather Burns]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/understanding-privacy-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/understanding-privacy-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet “Understanding Privacy”, our upcoming book on what data privacy is really about beyond scary headlines. Approx. 350 pages. eBook available in October, print shipping in November.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Accessibility And Usability Journey Of Drupal’s Primary Navigation]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/accessibility-usability-drupal-primary-navigation/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/accessibility-usability-drupal-primary-navigation/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Mike Herchel covers Drupal’s new default theme, Olivero, which is usable, accessible, robust, and beautiful and will help you improve websites’ navigation systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mike Herchel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the CSScenes, September 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373126</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/behind-the-csscenes-sept2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T20:06:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Those of you who have been reading CSS-Tricks for a while may remember that we used to publish a little thing we called CSS-Tricks Chronicles. Our friend Chris Coyier would write up a reflection from the past couple of …
Behind the CSScenes, September 2022 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haley Mills</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Brief Introduction to JAWS, NVDA, and VoiceOver]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372855</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/comparing-jaws-nvda-and-voiceover/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T17:47:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A screen reader is an important accessibility tool for people with no or limited vision. People who are blind or those with low vision can use a screen reader to navigate the computer. Screen readers will read contents on the …
A Brief Introduction to JAWS, NVDA, and VoiceOver originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilknur Eren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iShadeed’s Container Queries Lab]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=373087</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/ishadeeds-container-queries-lab/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T14:29:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahmad Shadeed got an early jump on container queries and has a growing collection of examples based on everyday patterns.
And, if you missed it, his latest post on container queries does a wonderful job covering how they work since …
iShadeed’s Container Queries Lab originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Databases For Front-End Developers: The Concepts Under The Hood (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/databases-frontend-developers-concepts-under-hood/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/databases-frontend-developers-concepts-under-hood/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the second part of “Databases For Front-End Developers” series, Atila Fassina explores concepts to equip you to have your own opinions about which kinds of databases suit your specific needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful JavaScript Data Grid Libraries]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/useful-javascript-data-grid-libraries/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/09/useful-javascript-data-grid-libraries/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Zara Cooper provides a rundown of some popular data grid libraries that would be a great addition to any data-heavy application and shares recommendations on what factors to consider when choosing a suitable data grid library.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding The Balance (September 2022 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-september-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-september-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T08:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s welcome September with some fresh desktop wallpapers. Designed by artists and designers from across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar for the month. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interpolating Numeric CSS Variables]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372839</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/interpolating-numeric-css-variables/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T13:17:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We can make variables in CSS pretty easily:
:root {
  --scale: 1;
}
And we can declare them on any element:
.thing {
  transform: scale(var(--scale));
}
Even better for an example like this is applying the variable on a user …
Interpolating Numeric CSS Variables originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Improve And Measure Your Progress Learning Web Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/improve-measure-progress-learning-web-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/improve-measure-progress-learning-web-design/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever felt overwhelmed by the number of things you need to learn? Today, we look at how [Uxcel](https://uxcel.com/) eases this transition and approaches actively learning new skills to take our careers to the next level.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shane Hudson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Makes A Great Toggle Button? (Case Study, Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/toggle-button-case-study-part-2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/toggle-button-case-study-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The problem of how to design an effective toggle button that shows the selected option clearly is a long-term open question among UI/UX designers. In this second part, Eduard Kuric explains a complex list of visual cues used by toggle buttons to communicate which of their options is active.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eduard Kuric)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Grid Named Areas to Visualize (and Reference) Your Layout]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372634</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-grid-named-areas-to-visualize-and-reference-your-layout/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T13:44:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whenever we build simple or complex layouts using CSS Grid, we’re usually positioning items with line numbers. Grid layouts contain grid lines that are automatically indexed with positive and negative line numbers (that is unless we explicitly name them). …
Using Grid Named Areas to Visualize (and Reference) Your Layout originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi Selvam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Better Error Messages UX]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/error-messages-ux-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/error-messages-ux-design/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Error messages need to be easy to spot, but they also need to be helpful. Let’s explore when error messages should live above input fields and why toast error messages are usually not a very good idea.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not Sure How to WordPress Anymore?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=372616</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/not-sure-how-to-wordpress-anymore/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T14:34:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neither do I! And that’s probably because there’s a lot happening in WordPress-land. The evolution towards full-site editing (FSE) introduces frequent changes to the way we build themes and plugins, and at such break-neck speed that the documentation itself is …
Not Sure How to WordPress Anymore? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better Video Streaming With imgix]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/better-video-streaming-with-imgix/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/better-video-streaming-with-imgix/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you need to deliver a large number of images and videos, a solution like [imgix](https://imgix.com/?utm_medium=banner&utm_source=smashingmag&utm_campaign=video-api-smashingmag-article-2022-08) can optimize and process both types of assets without you having to build it from the ground up or cobble together different solutions. Let’s take a closer look at how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Doug Sillars)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 51 With Ben Callahan: What’s The Value Of A Design System?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/smashing-podcast-episode-51/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/smashing-podcast-episode-51/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we ask how you can prove the value of a Design System and how you can pitch it effectively to stakeholders. Vitaly talks to Ben Callahan to find out more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Makes A Great Toggle Button? (Case Study, Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/toggle-button-case-study-part-1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/toggle-button-case-study-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this first part of a two-part article, Eduard Kuric analyzes the characteristics of effective toggle buttons that make it error-proof and prevent confusion and frustration of users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eduard Kuric)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing A Reset Password Feature With Next.js Dynamic Routes]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/implementing-reset-password-feature-nextjs-dynamic-routes/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/implementing-reset-password-feature-nextjs-dynamic-routes/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most users tend to forget their passwords, so create experiences that will always be valuable for people when they use your products. In this article, we’ll discuss how to implement a password-reset feature with Next.js dynamic routes while prioritizing the UX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Caleb Olojo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction To Context Propagation In JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/react-context-propagation-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/08/react-context-propagation-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React popularized context-propagation within applications with the context API. Evyatar Alush brings a brief intro to context propagation in JavaScript and how you can build React Context yourself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Evyatar Alush)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>