<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-04-20T00:09:28.600Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-04-20T00:09:28.601Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Interview Prep – How to Use a Collaborative Approach to Problem-Solving]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/collaborative-problem-solving-with-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/collaborative-problem-solving-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T21:14:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No matter how experienced of a developer you are, being interviewed for a new job is always stressful. This is certainly true from my own experience.  In my case, I have been working professionally as a Software Developer for two and a half years, and I've had to face]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alberto Gonzalez Rosales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Box Shadow Generator With React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-box-shadow-generator-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-box-shadow-generator-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T20:21:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS is a powerful language for styling web pages. But when you're designing a website, things like box shadows can be particularly difficult to get right.  In this guide, you will learn how to create your own box shadow generator with React and Vite. Here is a preview [https://shadowgen.vercel.app/]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Uzondu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Color Mechanics In UI Kits]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/color-mechanics-ui-kits/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/color-mechanics-ui-kits/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Adel Khamatov shares a model of color mechanics that he came up with during research on developing UI kits and illustrates an approach to solving related problems with best practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adel Khamatov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript in React – How to Manage State with Firebase Cloud Firestore]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-manage-state-in-react-apps-with-firebase-cloud-firestore/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-manage-state-in-react-apps-with-firebase-cloud-firestore/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T17:04:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State management is essential in today's world of web development. If you do it well, it helps you create apps that are reliable and effective. Firebase [https://firebase.google.com/] is a Backend-as-a-Service platform that has gained popularity along with the emergence of serverless architecture and cloud technologies. And Cloud Firestore [https://firebase.google.com/docs/firestore] is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olasunkanmi Balogun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT Course – Use the OpenAI API to Create Five Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/chatgpt-course-use-the-openai-api-to-create-five-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/chatgpt-course-use-the-openai-api-to-create-five-projects/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T15:15:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world of artificial intelligence is ever-evolving, and the OpenAI API is at the forefront of it. As the technology becomes more sophisticated, it's imperative for developers and enthusiasts to understand and utilize its potential in various applications. We just published an OpenAI API course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Godot for Game Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-godot-for-game-development/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-godot-for-game-development/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T15:06:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you interested in game development but don't know where to start? The Godot game engine is a popular open-source platform for game development, and our new video course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel will teach you everything you need to know to create your own platformer game. The course]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Print Methods in Java – How to Print to the Terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/print-methods-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/print-methods-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T14:28:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're learning Java, you probably started your coding journey by printing the "Hello World" program in the console. And that's a great way to begin – but after that, you need to learn how print methods and functions actually work. Well, this article will show you how those print]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does '$' Mean in RegEx?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-mean-in-regex/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-mean-in-regex/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T11:20:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The $ symbol is one of the most commonly used symbols in RegEx. It is used to match the end of a string. In this article, I’ll show you exactly what the dollar sign ($) does in RegEx and how to use it. What We'll Cover  * What is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python isEmpty() equivalent – How to Check if a List is Empty in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-check-if-a-list-is-empty-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-check-if-a-list-is-empty-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T04:52:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A list [/news/how-to-make-a-list-in-python-declare-lists-in-python-example/] is one of the data structures in Python that you can use to store a collection of variables.  In some cases, you have to iterate through and perform an operation on the elements of a list. But you can't loop/iterate through a list if it has]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy a NodeJS App with AWS CloudFormation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploy-nodejs-app-with-cloudformation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploy-nodejs-app-with-cloudformation/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T18:03:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine you have built a great product and its user base is growing rapidly. You want to scale your product to be available to people around the world. To do this, you'll need good cloud infrastructure. But managing your cloud infrastructure manually can be exhausting. You might start wondering, "how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Common Causes of Invalid HTML Syntax – and How to Fix Them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/invalid-html-syntax-examples-and-fixes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/invalid-html-syntax-examples-and-fixes/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T16:51:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remember those treehouses that we had as children and how the wood would wear, tear, and eventually collapse because we just would not stop jumping around inside it? Well that's kind of like HTML. This markup language is like the wood to your coding project. If it’s invalid, your solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CHRISTINE T. BELZIE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 59 With Chiara Aliotta: What Is Design Storytelling?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/smashing-podcast-episode-59/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/smashing-podcast-episode-59/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of The Smashing Podcast, we take a look at design storytelling. What is it, and how can it help us shape digital experiences? Vitaly talks to Chiara Aliotta to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Design Thinking?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/what-is-design-thinking/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/what-is-design-thinking/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered if things could have been done differently? But not sure how? Well, then, do not fall in love with the solution, but fall in love with the problem! Here’s an article to dive deep into how design thinking could do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Krithika Subramanian)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passkeys: What the Heck and Why?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377305</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/passkeys-what-the-heck-and-why/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T17:41:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These things called passkeys sure are making the rounds these days. They were a main attraction at W3C TPAC 2022, gained support in Safari 16, are finding their way into macOS and iOS, and are slated to …
Passkeys: What the Heck and Why? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Neal Fennimore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Design An Effective User Onboarding Flow]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/design-effective-user-onboarding-flow/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/design-effective-user-onboarding-flow/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to maximize conversions or collect necessary user information for other purposes, a user onboarding flow is necessary. In this article, you will learn how, with the help of Feathery, to design an effective user onboarding flow for your app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Suzanne Scacca)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Protect Your App With A Threat Model Based On JSONDiff]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/protect-app-threat-model-jsondiff/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/protect-app-threat-model-jsondiff/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a developer who wants to concentrate on delivering a killer application rather than worrying about countless security issues, threat model documents can help you do that. With small architectural changes, we can make these threats manageable and prevent them in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zack Grossbart &amp; Terry Yao)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Algorithms: Skills Of Designers That AI Can’t Replicate]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/skills-designers-ai-cant-replicate/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/skills-designers-ai-cant-replicate/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article highlights non-technical skills like curiosity, observation, empathy, advocacy, visual communication, and collaboration that designers routinely use in their process to make a difference through design. AI can be used to augment designers’ workflow instead of replacing people.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lyndon Cerejo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swing Into April (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With April just around the corner, we have a new collection of desktop and mobile wallpapers waiting for you to celebrate the beginning of the new month. Designed by creatives from all across the globe, the wallpapers come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Comprehensive Checklist For Running Design Workshops]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/organizing-design-workshops-checklist/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/organizing-design-workshops-checklist/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Workshops are all about people: they involve people, are conducted by people, and aim to close the gaps in people’s communication. Slava Shestopalov shares a checklist with everything you need to keep in mind when running a workshop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Slava Shestopalov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fine-Grained Access Handling And Data Management With Row-Level Security]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/access-handling-data-management-row-level-security/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/access-handling-data-management-row-level-security/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dealing with sensitive data is an important topic for any app. In this article, you will find out how to handle sensitive or confidential information in your apps and what Row-Level Security means.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Handoff Is No Handoff]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/best-handoff-is-no-handoff/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/best-handoff-is-no-handoff/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design handoffs are inefficient and painful. They cause frustration, friction and a lot of back and forth. Can we avoid them altogether? Of course we can! Let’s see how to do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overcoming The Challenges Of Content Creation For Informational Websites]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/overcoming-challenges-content-creation-informational-websites/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/overcoming-challenges-content-creation-informational-websites/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Content matters! Unfortunately, when it comes to informational websites, content quality is often poor. There is no magic answer to fix that. However, there are practical techniques you can use to improve the copy on your websites and ensure your users find the content they are looking for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Cross-Browser DevTools Features You Might Not Know]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377264</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/some-cross-browser-devtools-features-you-might-not-know/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T20:22:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I spend a lot of time in DevTools, and I’m sure you do too. Sometimes I even bounce between them, especially when I’m debugging cross-browser issues. DevTools is a lot like browsers themselves — not all of the features in …
Some Cross-Browser DevTools Features You Might Not Know originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pankaj Parashar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>