<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-12-07T00:51:14.623Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-12-07T00:51:14.623Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Launch Your Coding Career and Land Your First Software Engineering Internship]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/launch-your-coding-career-and-get-an-internship/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/launch-your-coding-career-and-get-an-internship/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T18:21:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the fiercely competitive world of software engineering, the question isn’t whether internships matter, but how much. According to a survey by the National Association of Colleges and Employers, 89% of large tech firms emphasize internship experience when hiring. So, if you’re an aspiring software engineer, listen closely. This carefully]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vahe Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five-Second Testing: Taking A Closer Look At First Impressions (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/five-second-testing-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/five-second-testing-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Five-second testing is a popular method of usability research used in the industry, yet in essence, its core belief boils down to virtually a superstition. Eduard Kuric looks under the hood at how first impressions are affected by various factors and how UX researchers and product owners can ensure that the user’s first steps can get off on the right foot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eduard Kuric)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the SWR Library for Better Data Fetching in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/swr-library-for-data-fetching-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/swr-library-for-data-fetching-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T21:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React is un-opinionated about how you fetch and manage the remote data in your application. You may think of using the useEffect hook for simple fetching operations, but it will not help you with caching, request deduplication, always serving real-time data, and so on. Things will get more complicated when]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Furkan Emin Can</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Use Cases – What is Python Best For?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-python-best-for/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-python-best-for/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T21:22:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers are often very passionate about their tech stack, and they'll likely recommend it for anything.  It is very common to see devs on social media sharing how you can build anything with JavaScript or how Python is great for data scientists. As a Python fanatic myself, I actually]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Cruz Martinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up GitHub OAuth in a Django App for User Authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/set-up-github-oauth-on-django-for-user-authentication/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/set-up-github-oauth-on-django-for-user-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T21:19:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maintaining safe and frictionless user authentication is paramount in today's fast-changing web application landscape.  Among the many authentication methods available, GitHub OAuth has emerged as a useful tool for improving user login experience while strengthening security measures.  Django [https://docs.djangoproject.com/en/4.2/], a Python web framework, has recently gained popularity in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Iroegbu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Contribute to Open Source as a Community Manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/contributing-to-open-source-as-a-community-manager/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/contributing-to-open-source-as-a-community-manager/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T21:14:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The proverb "it takes a village" applies to more than child-rearing. It also takes a village to maintain an open source project.  Community is a large part of open source. After all, Open Source projects can't thrive without a strong network of people (community) who contribute towards it, either]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amarachi Johnson-Ubah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Study Course – Pass the Exam With This Free 14-Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-study-course-pass-the-exam-with-this-free-13-hour-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-study-course-pass-the-exam-with-this-free-13-hour-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T19:51:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Passing the AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Exam is one of the first steps to a career in cloud development. And freeCodeCamp just published a free 14-hour course that will help you prepare for the exam.  This exam mostly deals with cloud computing concepts. Even if you are new to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping Time in C++: How to use the std::chrono API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cpp-std-chrono-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cpp-std-chrono-api/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T23:38:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping track of time is a very important aspect of computer programs. Some common use cases are:  * Measure/profile the performance of certain parts of code.  * Do work at certain periods of time, from within a program.   * Detect whether threads are in a deadlock]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jayant Chowdhary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React Hooks – useEffect, useState, and useContext Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-hooks-useeffect-usestate-and-usecontext/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-hooks-useeffect-usestate-and-usecontext/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T18:38:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React is a powerful JavaScript library for building user interfaces. And it has undergone significant changes over the years.  One of the most noteworthy additions is the introduction of hooks, which revolutionized the way developers manage state and side effects in functional components.  In this guide, we'll explore]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MLOps Course – Learn to Build Machine Learning Production Grade Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mlops-course-learn-to-build-machine-learning-production-grade-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mlops-course-learn-to-build-machine-learning-production-grade-projects/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T17:50:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MLOps, short for Machine Learning Operations, refers to the practice of applying DevOps principles to machine learning. Understanding MLOps can help you build production grade machine learning projects. We just posted an MLOps course the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. MLOps is a cutting-edge field at the intersection of machine learning, data]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Marketing Changed OOP In JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/marketing-changed-oop-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/marketing-changed-oop-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussing the decisions surrounding JavaScript prototypes, the article by Juan Diego Rodriguez scrutinizes their origin, examines missteps in the design, and explores how these factors have affected the way we write JavaScript today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SVG Tutorial – How to Code Images with 12 Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/svg-tutorial-learn-to-code-images/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/svg-tutorial-learn-to-code-images/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T12:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever needed an icon for your website, but you couldn't quite find the right one? Or perhaps you wanted to have a simple diagram, but didn't want to learn a whole new library just for that? Well, good news – you can do all that and more without]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hunor Márton Borbély</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recovering Deleted Files From Your Git Working Tree]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/recovering-deleted-files-git-working-tree/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/recovering-deleted-files-git-working-tree/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is designed to assure us that we can track a project’s files at different points in time. But it doesn’t assure us that those files are always safe along the way. For those of you who have dealt with the sinking feeling that you’ve irrevocably deleted and lost files, Sanmi has a couple of approaches that, in the right situations, may help bring them back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Oluwasanmi Akande)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cold Days, Shining Lights (December 2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-december-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-december-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Could there be a better way to welcome the new month than with a collection of desktop wallpapers? We’ve got some eye-catching designs to sweeten up the last few weeks of the year and, if you’re celebrating, to get you in the holiday mood.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crafting A Killer Brand Identity For A Digital Product]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/crafting-killer-brand-identity-digital-product/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/crafting-killer-brand-identity-digital-product/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Sasha guides you through crucial processes and factors to achieve a consistent brand presence across platforms. She offers an overview of the entire brand identity process, explores collaboration with UI teams, and provides essential details on the assets required for the successful implementation of a digital brand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sasha Denisova)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Few Ways CSS Is Easier To Write In 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/few-ways-css-easier-write-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/few-ways-css-easier-write-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re living in somewhat of a CSS renaissance with new features, techniques, experiments, and ideas coming at us to an extent we haven’t seen since “CSS3”. It’s easy to feel overwhelmed when your profession seems to be advancing at breakneck speed, but Geoff Graham considers the ways “modern” CSS in 2023 has actually made CSS “easier” to write.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction To Full Stack Composability]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/introduction-full-stack-composability/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/introduction-full-stack-composability/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A well-designed composable system should not only consider the technical aspects but also take into account the nature of the content it handles. To help us with that, we can use a Headless Content Management system such as Storyblok.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Responsive Multi-Line Ribbon Shapes (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/css-responsive-multi-line-ribbon-shapes-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/css-responsive-multi-line-ribbon-shapes-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Part 1 of the series, Temani Afif demonstrated how creating ribbon patterns in CSS has evolved with the availability of new CSS features. In this second installment of this brief two-part series, we look at two additional ribbon variations that introduce techniques for masking a repeated background gradient in CSS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating And Maintaining A Voice Of Customer Program]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/creating-maintaining-voice-customer-program/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/creating-maintaining-voice-customer-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Product teams benefit from knowing their users’ needs and how they respond to product updates as they build out the roadmap of a product. This article covers Voice of Customer programs and is aimed at those who work on a product team as well as executives who are looking for how to better inform your products using insight from users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Victor Yocco &amp; Dana Daniels)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Efficient Design-to-Code Handoff Process Using Uno Platform For Figma]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/design-to-code-handoff-process-uno-platform-figma/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/design-to-code-handoff-process-uno-platform-figma/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Effective collaboration between designers and developers is vital to creating good user experiences. However, bridging the handoff between design and development with the many tools and workflows available today has its pitfalls. Matthew Mattei introduces you to the Uno Platform, which offers a robust set of productivity boosters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matthew Mattei)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Responsive Multi-Line Ribbon Shapes (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/css-responsive-multi-line-ribbon-shapes-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/css-responsive-multi-line-ribbon-shapes-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ribbons have been used to accent designs for many years now. But, the way we approach them in CSS has evolved with the introduction of newer features. In this article, Temani Afif combines background and gradient tricks to create ribbon shapes in CSS that are not only responsive but support multi-line text and are easily adjustable with a few CSS variables.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Web Design Documentation]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/designing-web-design-documentation/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/designing-web-design-documentation/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Words alone aren’t enough to safeguard best practices in the world of web design and development. Web design documentation must be like its medium — interactive and constantly evolving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Accessible UI Animations]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/creating-accessible-ui-animations/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/creating-accessible-ui-animations/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animation and accessibility are often seen as two separate powers at odds with one another. How is it possible to strike a balance between elements that move and the possible negative effects they expose to users who are sensitive to motion? Oriana García explains how her team at Mercado Libre tackled the challenge by creating guiding principles for applying animation to user interfaces and incorporating them into the team’s design system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Oriana García)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Playground: From 5-Minute Install To Instant Spin-Up]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/wordpress-playground-5-minute-install-instant-spin-up/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/wordpress-playground-5-minute-install-instant-spin-up/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Playground began as an experiment to see what a self-hosted WordPress experience might look like without the requirement of having to actually install WordPress. A year later, the experiment has evolved into a full-fledged project. Ganesh Dahal demonstrates how WordPress Playground works and gets deep into how it might be used.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ganesh Dahal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Addressing Accessibility Concerns With Using Fluid Type]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/addressing-accessibility-concerns-fluid-type/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/addressing-accessibility-concerns-fluid-type/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS `clamp()` function is often paired with viewport units for “fluid” font sizing that scales the text up and down at different viewport sizes. As common as this technique is, several voices warn that it opens up situations where text can fail WCAG Success Criterion 1.4.4, which specifies that text should scale up to at least 200% when the user’s browser reaches its 500% maximum zoom level. Max Barvian takes a deep look at the issue and offers ideas to help address it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Maxwell Barvian)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>