<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-12-27T00:10:05.712Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-12-27T00:10:05.712Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#100DaysOfCode Challenge for 2024 – Discord Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/100daysofcode-challenge-2024-discord/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/100daysofcode-challenge-2024-discord/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-24T21:37:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp always gets a huge rush of ambitious learners on New Year's Day. And each year, I try to create challenge that will help people stick with their learning. In the past, we've had cloud certification challenges, gamedev challenges, and back end development challenges. This year, we're going back to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Innovate as a Developer – a Roadmap to a Successful Tech Career [Full Book]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/creators-guide-to-innovation-book/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/creators-guide-to-innovation-book/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T22:18:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to this book that teaches you how to innovate as a developer. It isn’t just another step-by-step manual on creating specific products. It’s much more.  I’ve crafted this guide with a focus on equipping you with the mindset, skills, and habits necessary for innovation at any scale –]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vahe Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Idempotence in HTTP Methods – Explained with CRUD Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/idempotency-in-http-methods/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/idempotency-in-http-methods/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T21:19:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Idempotence refers to a program's ability to maintain a particular result even after repeated actions.  For example, let's say you have a button that only opens a door when pressed. This button does not have the ability to close the door, so it stays open even when it's pressed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yemi Ojedapo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API And Delightful UI Animations (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/view-transitions-api-ui-animations-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/view-transitions-api-ui-animations-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API is a new — but game-changing — feature that allows us to do the types of reactive state-based UI and page transitions that have traditionally been exclusive to JavaScript frameworks. In the first part of this mini two-part series, Adrian Bece thoroughly explains why we need the API and demonstrates its basic usage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering Behavioral Interviews for Software Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mastering-behavioral-interviews-for-software-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mastering-behavioral-interviews-for-software-developers/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T16:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the competitive world of software development, acing technical interviews is often considered the key to landing a dream job. However, there's another crucial aspect that aspiring developers frequently overlook – behavioral interviews. We just posted a new course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that provides a guide to mastering]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full Stack JavaScript Course: Build a Hotel Management Site with Next.js, Sanity.io, and Tailwind CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-and-deploy-a-hotel-management-site/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-and-deploy-a-hotel-management-site/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T23:54:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a complex website is a great way to learn how a bunch of technologies work together. We just posted a 10-hour course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build a hotel management website using Next.js, React, Sanity.io, Tailwind CSS, and Stripe's payment API. Lari]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn English for Developers – freeCodeCamp A2 English Curriculum]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-english-for-developers-a2/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-english-for-developers-a2/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T17:26:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm thrilled to announce that the freeCodeCamp community has been developing a comprehensive English for Developers curriculum. Together, we're going to help millions of non-native English speakers prepare for careers in tech. The trailer for freeCodeCamp's new English for Developers curriculumWhy teach English? For the first 9 years of freeCodeCamp's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use an API with Postman – A Step-by-Step Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-an-api-with-postman/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-an-api-with-postman/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T16:57:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the field of software development, effective communication between different software systems is made possible through the essential function of Application Programming Interfaces (APIs).  APIs allow developers to access and use the functionalities of a particular application, service, or platform. Postman is a powerful and user-friendly tool that simplifies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Curriculum 2024 Upgrade – Interactive Python Learning in your Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-curriculum-upgrade/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-curriculum-upgrade/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T16:51:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp just published a major upgrade to our Scientific Computing with Python certification. You can now learn Python coding fundamentals by building 15 projects – right in your browser. A 1 minute trailer for our newly-upgraded Scientific Computing with Python certificationHere's a full list of the 15 projects you'll build:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn JavaScript by Building 21 Projects – a Major freeCodeCamp Curriculum Upgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-javascript-with-new-data-structures-and-algorithms-certification-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-javascript-with-new-data-structures-and-algorithms-certification-projects/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T15:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp just launched a major upgrade to our JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures Certification [https://www.freecodecamp.dev/learn/javascript-algorithms-and-data-structures-v8/] . You can now learn JavaScript by building 21 projects! A trailer video for freeCodeCamp's upgraded JavaScript Data Structures and Algorithms CertificationInstead of coding through a series of challenges, you will learn the fundamentals of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Very freeCodeCamp Christmas  – Python & JavaScript Upgrades, English Curriculum, The Odin Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-very-freecodecamp-christmas/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-very-freecodecamp-christmas/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T13:09:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm thrilled to announce freeCodeCamp's Christmas gifts to the global developer community: #1: A new JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures certification, featuring 21 projects you can code step-by-step right in your browser. It's fully project-based, containing more than a thousand new coding challenges. A 1-minute trailer video for freeCodeCamp's upgraded]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New CSS Viewport Units Do Not Solve The Classic Scrollbar Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/new-css-viewport-units-not-solve-classic-scrollbar-problem/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/new-css-viewport-units-not-solve-classic-scrollbar-problem/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the introduction of CSS viewport units in 2012, many of us have been using `width: 100vw` as a way to set an element’s width to the full width of the viewport. But, as Šime Vidas explains in this deep dive, `100vw` does not always represent the full width of the viewport due to differences in how browsers handle scrollbars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Šime Vidas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Components For Consumption, Not Complexity (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/building-components-consumption-not-complexity-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/building-components-consumption-not-complexity-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part 2 concentrates on the key points from Luis’ framework and practical tips about managing a design system that should be both robust and easy to adopt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Luis Ouriach)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Scroll Snapping Aligned With Global Page Layout: A Full-Width Slider Case Study]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/css-scroll-snapping-aligned-global-page-layout-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/css-scroll-snapping-aligned-global-page-layout-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you run into a situation where you need the padding of one element to align with the padding of another element? In this article, Brecht De Ruyte demonstrates the issue with a full-width slider component that breaks out of the main page container and shares a couple of techniques to keep it visually aligned with other elements on the page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Brecht De Ruyte)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Components For Consumption, Not Complexity (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/building-components-consumption-not-complexity-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/building-components-consumption-not-complexity-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design systems can be of immense help, but failure to adopt them invalidates the hard work that goes into building the thing in the first place! In this two-part series of articles, Luis shares his experience with design systems and how you can overcome the potential pitfalls.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Luis Ouriach)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preparing For Interaction To Next Paint, A New Web Core Vital]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/preparing-interaction-next-paint-web-core-vital/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/preparing-interaction-next-paint-web-core-vital/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting in March 2024, Interaction to Next Paint will formally replace First Input Delay as a Core Web Vital metric. Learn how the two metrics differ, why we needed a new way to measure interaction responsiveness, and how you can start optimizing the performance of your site now for a seamless transition to the latest Core Web Vital metric.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five-Second Testing: Taking A Closer Look At First Impressions (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/five-second-testing-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/five-second-testing-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Five-second testing is a popular method of usability research used in the industry, yet in essence, its core belief boils down to virtually a superstition. Eduard Kuric looks under the hood at how first impressions are affected by various factors and how UX researchers and product owners can ensure that the user’s first steps can get off on the right foot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eduard Kuric)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Marketing Changed OOP In JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/marketing-changed-oop-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/marketing-changed-oop-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussing the decisions surrounding JavaScript prototypes, the article by Juan Diego Rodriguez scrutinizes their origin, examines missteps in the design, and explores how these factors have affected the way we write JavaScript today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recovering Deleted Files From Your Git Working Tree]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/recovering-deleted-files-git-working-tree/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/recovering-deleted-files-git-working-tree/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is designed to assure us that we can track a project’s files at different points in time. But it doesn’t assure us that those files are always safe along the way. For those of you who have dealt with the sinking feeling that you’ve irrevocably deleted and lost files, Sanmi has a couple of approaches that, in the right situations, may help bring them back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Oluwasanmi Akande)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cold Days, Shining Lights (December 2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-december-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-december-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Could there be a better way to welcome the new month than with a collection of desktop wallpapers? We’ve got some eye-catching designs to sweeten up the last few weeks of the year and, if you’re celebrating, to get you in the holiday mood.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crafting A Killer Brand Identity For A Digital Product]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/crafting-killer-brand-identity-digital-product/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/crafting-killer-brand-identity-digital-product/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Sasha guides you through crucial processes and factors to achieve a consistent brand presence across platforms. She offers an overview of the entire brand identity process, explores collaboration with UI teams, and provides essential details on the assets required for the successful implementation of a digital brand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sasha Denisova)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>