<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-08-01T00:12:10.860Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-08-01T00:12:10.860Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manage State in Your Applications – useState() vs Redux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/usestate-vs-redux-state-management/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/usestate-vs-redux-state-management/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T21:35:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State management is crucial for handling an application's data, how users interact with it, and how different parts of the app behave.  And it's not something you'll use only in React.js [https://react.dev/], but also in other popular tools like Angular.js, [https://angularjs.org/] Vue.js, [https://vuejs.org/] and Next.j [https://nextjs.org/]s. There are two]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijeoma Igboagu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Calculate Definite and Indefinite Integrals in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/calculate-definite-indefinite-integrals-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/calculate-definite-indefinite-integrals-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T18:02:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python is a versatile programming language that offers libraries and tools for scientific computing and mathematical calculations.  Many essential mathematical operations frequently involve definite and indefinite integrals. In this article, we will explore how to perform these calculations using Python. How to Calculate Single Variable Definite Integrals Install SciPy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roy Chng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Bridge the Gap Between Development and Production with Valid HTTPS Certificates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/development-production-parity-with-valid-https-certs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/development-production-parity-with-valid-https-certs/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T17:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the core principles of software development involves maintaining development/production parity. But this is not always the case for developers working on localhost. To review, dev/prod parity refers to keeping development, staging, and production environments as similar as possible to avoid encountering undetected bugs. A lack of dev/prod parity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Linda Ikechukwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Living In The Moment (August 2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T09:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New month, new wallpapers! In this post, you’ll find unique and inspiring wallpapers for August 2023. Created with love by the community for the community, they come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Higher-Order Components in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/higher-order-components-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/higher-order-components-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T17:40:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Higher-order components (HOCs) are a powerful feature of the React library. They allow you to reuse component logic across multiple components.  In React, a higher-order component is a function that takes a component as an argument and returns a new component that wraps the original component. HOCs allow you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Portfolio Site with Sanity and Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-portfolio-site-with-sanity-and-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-portfolio-site-with-sanity-and-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T16:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Knowing how to handle content is important when creating a personal website for yourself or a client.  This is because maintaining and updating a site can result in substantial expenses if you don't do it correctly. This is even more the case if you're building for someone with a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Eke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp is Launching a Podcast in Spanish]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-podcast-in-spanish/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-podcast-in-spanish/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T15:33:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello! My name is Rafael Hernandez and I'm excited to announce the launch of our new podcast: El Podcast de freeCodeCamp en Español [https://freecodecamp-en-espanol.transistor.fm/].  ‌‌‌‌In this podcast, we'll dive into the stories of inspiring people in the world of technology and content creation. Our goal is to bring you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rafael D. Hernandez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Define An Array Of Colors With CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/define-array-colors-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/define-array-colors-css/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join Temani Afif on experiment with modern CSS features to create an array of colors. The goal is to define a comma-separated list of colors and iterate through them using an index.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use TypeScript Generics with Functional React Components]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typescript-generics-with-functional-react-components/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typescript-generics-with-functional-react-components/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T18:53:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will explore the powerful synergy between TypeScript generics and functional React components. Generics allow you to define flexible components that can adapt to different data structures and enforce type safety throughout your codebase. By leveraging Generics in functional components, you can create highly reusable and adaptable]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olasunkanmi Balogun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use Artificial Intelligence And Machine Learning To Summarize Chat Conversations]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/artificial-intelligence-machine-learning-summarize-chat-conversations/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/artificial-intelligence-machine-learning-summarize-chat-conversations/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll explore how to build a chat summarizer using the Cohere API and deploy it as a web application using Gradio.[ Cohere](https://cohere.com/) is an AI platform that provides state-of-the-art natural language processing models for a variety of tasks, including summarization. We’ll cover the steps involved in training the summarizer using sample chat conversations, interacting with the Cohere API to generate summaries, and creating a user-friendly interface using [Gradio](https://www.gradio.app/).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joas Pambou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Augmented Reality Course – Take Your First Steps into the World of AR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/take-your-first-steps-into-the-world-of-augmented-reality/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/take-your-first-steps-into-the-world-of-augmented-reality/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T13:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine transforming your surroundings with interactive digital overlays, creating new experiences, and changing the way you interact with the world around you. Welcome to the future – the future of Augmented Reality (AR). The freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel just launched a comprehensive new course that will teach you how to implement]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Next.js by Building a Custom API with MongoDB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-stack-with-nextjs-and-appwrite-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-stack-with-nextjs-and-appwrite-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T12:28:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're excited to announce the launch of a new course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will give you an in-depth understanding of how to build a custom API using Next.js and MongoDB. This course was created by Hitesh Choudhary. He is an an expert in the field and has]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Multiple Virtual Hosts on a Single RabbitMQ Instance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-multiple-virtual-hosts-on-one-rabbitmq-instance/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-multiple-virtual-hosts-on-one-rabbitmq-instance/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T21:25:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, friends, and welcome to another tutorial. We'll be talking about RabbitMQ, a tool that is widely used as a message broker in distributed and Pub-Sub systems.  While multiple applications can share a single RabbitMQ instance, it's a great approach to configure it to have different virtual hosts for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ridwan Yusuf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern Technology And The Future Of Language Translation]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/modern-technology-future-language-translation/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/modern-technology-future-language-translation/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The field of language translation has never been more exciting. Explore the evolution of language translation platforms, how we got to where we are today, and what advancements we can look forward to in the coming years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adriano Raiano)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recreating YouTube’s Ambient Mode Glow Effect]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/recreating-youtube-ambient-mode-glow-effect/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/recreating-youtube-ambient-mode-glow-effect/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Adrian deconstructs YouTube’s “Ambient Mode” feature and how HTML `` and the `requestAnimationFrame` function are used to create the glowing effect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Art Of Looking Back: A Critical Reflection For Individual Contributors]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/critical-reflection-individual-contributors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/critical-reflection-individual-contributors/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover the importance of critical reflective practice and challenge some beliefs about reflection and its role in our work and growth. Kristian Mikhel suggests a critical reflective routine for individual contributors and gives some practical recommendations that will make reflection meaningful and actionable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kristian Mikhel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Age-Inclusive Products: Guidelines And Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/designing-age-inclusive-products-guidelines-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/designing-age-inclusive-products-guidelines-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With an estimated one in every eight individuals worldwide surpassing the age of 60, who are actively adopting online shopping, the need for user-friendly interfaces tailored to their needs becomes apparent. Explore the guidelines to help you design inclusive products for all, particularly for an older audience and your future self.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michal Halperin Ben Zvi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writing CSS In 2023: Is It Any Different Than A Few Years Ago?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/writing-css-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/writing-css-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS is evolving faster than ever. With all of the new features that are now available — and forthcoming — since we got Flexbox and Grid years ago, the way we write CSS is evolving, too. In this article, Geoff Graham shares which features have had the most influence on his current approaches to CSS, as well as those that have not (at least yet).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create A Rapid Research Program To Support Insights At Scale]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/create-rapid-research-program-support-insights-scale/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/create-rapid-research-program-support-insights-scale/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate your organization’s growth and innovation with the power of Rapid Research. From inception to implementation, here is the step-by-step roadmap on how to build the program from scratch and uncover the untapped ROI opportunities waiting to propel your initiatives to new heights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Devin Harold)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 63 With Chris Ferdinandi: What Is The Transitional Web?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/smashing-podcast-episode-63/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/smashing-podcast-episode-63/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of The Smashing Podcast, we’re talking about The Transitional Web. What is it, and how does it describe the technologies we’re using? Drew McLellan talks to Chris Ferdinandi to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Become A Better Speaker At Conferences]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/become-better-speaker-conferences/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/become-better-speaker-conferences/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Andy Budd, curator of UX London and Leading Design conferences, outlines some of the things that make a potentially amazing presentation, as well as a few big gotchas. If you’ve ever wondered what it takes to get a speaking slot at a conference, this article is for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andy Budd)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shines, Perspective, And Rotations: Fancy CSS 3D Effects For Images]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/shines-perspective-rotations-css-3d-effects-images/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/shines-perspective-rotations-css-3d-effects-images/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS has all kinds of tricks that are capable of turning images into neat, interactive elements. This article is a collection of fancy 3D effects for images that demonstrate those CSS powers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The UX Of Flight Searches: How We Challenged Industry Standards]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/reimagining-flight-search-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/reimagining-flight-search-ux/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As of today, the world’s 50 top airlines have all agreed on the same flight search pattern. Yet the path to booking the right flight remains frustrating and confusing. Is there really only one solution? Explore the thought experiment which turned the seemingly untouchable pattern on its head and offered new food for thought.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Robert Goesch)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sustainable Design Toolkits And Frameworks]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/sustainable-design-toolkits-and-resources/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/sustainable-design-toolkits-and-resources/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can we create products and experiences that don’t cause harm to the planet and to the people who use them? What do we need to consider to make more sustainable design decisions and reduce the carbon footprint of our websites? In this post, we compiled valuable resources that will get you familiar with the principles of sustainable design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke &amp; Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>