<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-11-14T00:12:12.050Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-11-14T00:12:12.050Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacktoberfest 2022 Contributors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hacktoberfest-2022-contributors/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hacktoberfest-2022-contributors/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T20:25:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp participated in Hacktoberfest (a month-long celebration of open source) again this year. We wanted to take a moment to thank all of our wonderful contributors for the effort they put in to help us continue to improve our curriculum and learning resources. Thank you for your contributions to open]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Naomi Carrigan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JS Copy an Object – How to Clone an Obj in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/clone-an-object-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/clone-an-object-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T17:13:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A JavaScript object is a collection of key-value pairs. It is a non-primitive data type that can contain various data types. For example: const userDetails = {   name: "John Doe",   age: 14,   verified: false }; When working with objects in JavaScript, you may sometimes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Your Own Mastodon Instance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-your-own-mastodon-instance/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-your-own-mastodon-instance/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T16:29:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mastodon is a decentralized, federated social media platform based on the  ActivityPub [https://www.w3.org/TR/activitypub/] protocol. It allows you to follow and interact with friends across multiple instances.  In this article, you will learn how freeCodeCamp set up our own Mastodon instance - and how you can too. What is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Naomi Carrigan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is YAML? The YML File Format]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-yaml-the-yml-file-format/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-yaml-the-yml-file-format/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T16:20:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YAML is one of the most popular languages for writing configuration files. In this article, you will learn how YAML compares to XML and JSON - two languages also used for creating configuration files. You will also learn some of the rules and features of the language, along with its]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Grid and Custom Shapes, Part 3]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374826</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-grid-and-custom-shapes-part-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T14:42:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Part 1 and Part 2, I am back with a third article to explore more fancy shapes. Like the previous articles, we are going to combine CSS Grid with clipping and masking to create fancy layouts for image …
CSS Grid and Custom Shapes, Part 3 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Search For A Developer Job Abroad]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/search-developer-job-abroad/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/search-developer-job-abroad/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working abroad is a popular prospect, yet many people — including professionals in the tech sphere — don’t know where to start. In this article, Andrew Stetsenko gives you an ultimate step-by-step guide to finding and making international opportunities happen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andrew Stetsenko)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Convert an Int to a String in C++ – Integer Cast Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-convert-an-int-to-a-string-in-cpp/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-convert-an-int-to-a-string-in-cpp/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T18:54:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Type casting or type conversion is the process of converting a variable from one data type to another.  Type casting can be done implicitly or explicitly.  Implicit type casting gets done automatically via the compiler, while explicit type casting is done by the developer. In this article, you'll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Error: error:0308010c:digital envelope routines::unsupported [Node Error Solved]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/error-error-0308010c-digital-envelope-routines-unsupported-node-error-solved/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/error-error-0308010c-digital-envelope-routines-unsupported-node-error-solved/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T18:39:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you work with Node.js and command line interface solutions like Webpack, create-react-app, or vue-cli-service, you might have encountered the error,  Error: error:0308010c:digital envelope routines::unsupported. You’re not alone, because I’m currently getting it too: The React app indeed failed to start: In this article, you’ll learn how to fix]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Jamstack? Tutorial for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/jamstack-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/jamstack-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T18:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have heard the term Jamstack and have been wondering what it means. Well, the Jamstack is nothing more than a modern way of building web applications.  Jamstack takes advantage of existing technologies – which we'll discuss in a minute. The result is better performance, improved security, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damilola Oladele</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fuzz Web Applications using FFuf – Web Security Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-security-fuzz-web-applications-using-ffuf/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-security-fuzz-web-applications-using-ffuf/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T17:21:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building strong authentication systems is crucial for web applications. Now that many businesses have a growing online presence, a malicious actor taking control of your website can be devastating. In this article, we will learn how to use Ffuf, a fast web fuzzer written in Go. You will learn how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming in TypeScript – Full Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/programming-in-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/programming-in-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T16:10:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript is a typed superset of JavaScript that compiles to plain JavaScript. TypeScript provides better error checking than JavaScript. This is because TypeScript uses a static type system, which means that the type of a variable is checked before the code is executed. We just published a 5-hour TypeScript course]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Bootstrap 5 in Spanish by Building a Portfolio Website – Bootstrap Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-bootstrap-5-in-spanish-by-building-a-portfolio-website-bootstrap-course-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-bootstrap-5-in-spanish-by-building-a-portfolio-website-bootstrap-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T05:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome! If you speak Spanish and you want to practice your HTML and CSS skills, create responsive websites with Bootstrap 5, and build your portfolio website, then this course is for you. In this article, you will find a brief introduction to responsive web development and Bootstrap 5. You will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design Systems: Useful Examples and Resources]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/design-systems-inspiration-resources-case-studies/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/design-systems-inspiration-resources-case-studies/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything design systems on accessibility, enterprise design systems, Figma kits, data visualization, motion design, multi-lingual design, naming, ROI calculator and UX writing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What CSS Do You Absolutely Have to Know in 2022?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374775</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/what-css-do-you-absolutely-have-to-know-in-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T13:51:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sacha Greif openly wondered whether CSS has gotten to be, you know, too big. With all the goodies that’ve shipped in browsers the past couple of years — container queries! relative color syntax! cascade layers! logical properties…
What CSS Do You Absolutely Have to Know in 2022? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing CSS Styles in a WordPress Block Theme]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374910</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/managing-css-styles-in-a-wordpress-block-theme/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T14:05:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The way we write CSS for WordPress themes is in the midst of sweeping changes. I recently shared a technique for adding fluid type support in WordPress by way of theme.json, a new file that WordPress has been pushing …
Managing CSS Styles in a WordPress Block Theme originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ganesh Dahal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New In Next.js 13?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/whats-new-nextjs-13/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/whats-new-nextjs-13/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s talk about Next.js, one of the most well-known React frameworks used for production. From new components to font optimization, Atila shares a quick overview and invites you to join his [Advanced Next.js Masterclass](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/workshops/advanced-nextjs-atila-fassina) taking place later this month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Couple Changes Coming in Chrome 108]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374894</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-couple-changes-coming-in-chrome-108/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T13:13:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“A change to overflow on replaced elements in CSS”:
From Chrome 108, the following replaced elements respect the overflow property: img, video and canvas. In earlier versions of Chrome, this property was ignored on these elements.
This 
…
A Couple Changes Coming in Chrome 108 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practical Steps To Build Transparency In Your Remote Business]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/practical-steps-build-transparency-remote-business/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/practical-steps-build-transparency-remote-business/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transparency is part of the fabric of many remote businesses. It doesn’t, however, come naturally to everyone, especially if you’ve only recently become remote. In this article, Siobhan takes you through some of the practical ways that you can build transparency within your organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Siobhan McKeown)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Difference Between Web Sockets, Web Workers, and Service Workers]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374731</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-difference-between-web-sockets-web-workers-and-service-workers/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T12:56:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web Sockets, Web Workers, Service Workers… these are terms you may have read or overheard. Maybe not all of them, but likely at least one of them. And even if you have a good handle on front-end development, there’s a …
The Difference Between Web Sockets, Web Workers, and Service Workers originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aisha Bukar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Smashing Front-End & UX Workshops]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/new-frontend-coding-ux-online-workshops/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/new-frontend-coding-ux-online-workshops/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s the state of HTML Email, Vue.js and Next.js? Would you like to level up with modern CSS? What are new, smart interface design patterns we could use? Let’s figure it all out together with our [brand new online workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) alongside our free community meetups.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing The Perfect Mobile Navigation UX]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/navigation-design-mobile-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/navigation-design-mobile-ux/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When designing navigation on mobile, we don’t have to rely on slide-in-menus or nested accordions. We can also use the curtain design pattern, and show multiple levels of navigation at once.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Links About CSS Gradients]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374697</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/some-links-about-css-gradients/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T12:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every once in a while, the blogging zeitgiest seems to coalesce around a certain topic and it’s like the saved articles in my bookmarks folder are having a conversation. The conversation sitting in there now is all about CSS Gradients …
Some Links About CSS Gradients originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rendering External API Data in WordPress Blocks on the Back End]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374381</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/rendering-external-api-data-in-wordpress-blocks-on-the-back-end/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T12:57:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a continuation of my last article about “Rendering External API Data in WordPress Blocks on the Front End”. In that last one, we learned how to take an external API and integrate it with a block that …
Rendering External API Data in WordPress Blocks on the Back End originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manoj Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Putting The Graph In GraphQL With The Neo4j GraphQL Library]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/graph-neo4j-graphql-library/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/graph-neo4j-graphql-library/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If building a GraphQL API backed by a native graph database sounds interesting or at all helpful for the problems you’re trying to solve as a developer, perhaps you’d like to give the open-source [Neo4j GraphQL Library](https://srv.buysellads.com/ads/long/x/TCZPLYDDTTTTTTFR6JINCTTTTTTGVUIVKKTTTTTTCT2NTYYTTTTTTI4BVH7U4JBCKQ466IDGV2IUWESGCV7WALL5QYYE) a try. Let’s take a closer look at the reasons why!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (William Lyon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New CSS Media Query Range Syntax]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374670</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-new-css-media-query-range-syntax/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T13:05:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Media Queries Level 4 specification has introduced a new syntax for targeting a range of viewport widths using common mathematical comparison operators, like , and =, that make more sense syntactically while writing less code for responsive web design.
The New CSS Media Query Range Syntax originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi Selvam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On The Edge Of November (2022 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November is just around the corner, and with it, a new collection of desktop wallpapers to celebrate the beginning of the month. Designed by creatives from all across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar. Let’s make November colorful!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create Advanced Animations With CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/advanced-animations-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/advanced-animations-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-29T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Yosra Emad explains how to create a rollercoaster path that a ball follows using cubic beziers and CSS transitions. You’ll also learn how the cubic-bezier function in CSS works in detail and how to stack multiple simple animations to create one complex one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yosra Emad)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Motion Controls In The Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/motion-controls-browser/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/motion-controls-browser/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've ever wanted to build a web app that you can control with hand gestures as if by magic, this article is for you. With a couple of APIs and some JavaScript, you can build apps that behave like sorcery.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yaphi Berhanu)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fancy Image Decorations: Outlines and Complex Animations]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374302</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/fancy-image-decorations-outlines-and-complex-animations/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T12:45:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve spent the last two articles in this three-part series playing with gradients to make really neat image decorations using nothing but the <img> element. In this third and final piece, we are going to explore more techniques using the …
Fancy Image Decorations: Outlines and Complex Animations originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Holographic Trading Card Effect]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374609</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/holographic-trading-card-effect/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T17:05:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Simon Goellner (@simeydotme)’s collection of Holographic Trading Cards have captured our attention.
Under the hood there is a suite of filter(), background-blend-mode(), mix-blend-mode(), and clip-path() combinations that have been painstakingly tweaked to reach the desired effect. I …
Holographic Trading Card Effect originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bradley Kouchi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Typographic Hierarchies]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/typographic-hierarchies/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/typographic-hierarchies/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Alma Hoffmann discusses six basic variables to establish a typographic hierarchy, explains how to look at each differently, and in turn, designs pieces by intentionally modifying each variable to create a typographic hierarchy effectively.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alma Hoffmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Animated, Clickable Cards With the :has() Relational Pseudo Class]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374690</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-animated-clickable-cards-with-the-has-relational-pseudo-class/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T14:15:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS :has() pseudo class is rolling out in many browsers with Chrome and Safari already fully supporting it. It’s often referred to it as “the parent selector” — as in, we can select style a parent element from a …
Creating Animated, Clickable Cards With the :has() Relational Pseudo Class originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brecht De Ruyte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State Of CSS Survey: Influence The Future Of CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/state-css-survey-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/state-css-survey-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The annual survey for anyone who writes CSS, [State of CSS](https://stateofcss.com/en-us/?source=smashing_magazine_css_survey), is nearing the end of its response period for 2022. The survey is available in many different languages and all questions are optional.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lea Verou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is There Too Much CSS Now?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374364</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/is-there-too-much-css-now/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T12:59:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As front-end developers, we’ve wished for a lot of things over the years — ways to center things in CSS, encapsulate styles, set an element’s aspect ratio, get finer-grained control over our colors, select an element based on its children’s …
Is There Too Much CSS Now? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sacha Greif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fancy Image Decorations: Masks and Advanced Hover Effects]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374194</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/fancy-image-decorations-masks-and-advanced-hover-effects/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T12:46:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Part 2 of this three-part series! We are still decorating images without any extra elements and pseudo-elements. I hope you already took the time to digest Part 1 because we will continue working with a lot of gradients …
Fancy Image Decorations: Masks and Advanced Hover Effects originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Futuristic CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/futuristic-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/futuristic-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Sacha Greif tries to anticipate future CSS trends and takes a look at some far-fetched and futuristic CSS features that might one day make their way to the browser.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sacha Greif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instant Articles, Proprietary Syndication, and a Web Built on User Fidelity Preferences]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374470</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/instant-articles-proprietary-syndication-user-fidelity-preferences/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T19:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love it when there’s a sense of synergy in the blogosphere. First, I caught Nick Heer’s coverage of Meta ending support for Instant Articles, its proprietary format for stripped-down performant news articles. He also compares it to the similar …
Instant Articles, Proprietary Syndication, and a Web Built on User Fidelity Preferences originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New In DevTools: Halloween Edition 🎃]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/devtools-updates-halloween-edition/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/devtools-updates-halloween-edition/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Patrick Brosset gives an update on the most impactful new features that are now available in DevTools, across Firefox, Chrome, Safari, and Edge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Patrick Brosset)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsive Animations for Every Screen Size and Device]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=374345</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/responsive-animations-for-every-screen-size-and-device/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T12:42:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before I career jumped into development, I did a bunch of motion graphics work in After Effects. But even with that background, I still found animating on the web pretty baffling.
Video graphics are designed within a specific ratio and …
Responsive Animations for Every Screen Size and Device originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cassie Evans</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Privacy: A New Smashing Book Is Here]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/understanding-privacy-book-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/understanding-privacy-book-release/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Understanding Privacy, our brand new Smashing Book to make sense of privacy, and learn how to create inclusive, safe and privacy-aware digital experiences. eBook now available, print shipping in late November.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Full-Site Editing: A Deep Dive Into The New Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/wordpress-full-site-editing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/10/wordpress-full-site-editing/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Nick Schäferhoff will take a deep dive into WordPress Full-Site Editing, examine the tools it provides for theme development, and provide a tutorial on how to use it to make changes to your site.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nick Schäferhoff)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>