<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-05-28T00:10:58.711Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-05-28T00:10:58.711Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing A Better Design Handoff File In Figma]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/designing-better-design-handoff-file-figma/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/designing-better-design-handoff-file-figma/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article provides practical tips for improving the handoff process between design and development in product development. The guidance covers effective communication, documentation, design details, version control, and plugin usage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ben Shih)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strings in C# – What's New, Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/new-ish-things-about-c-strings/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/new-ish-things-about-c-strings/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T13:49:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Much of what we work with in our code are strings. Let's look at some of the newish things about C# strings ... including raw string literals and raw string interpolation that are new in C# 11. Raw string literals make it easy to build complex, multi-line strings, including JSON,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deborah Kurata</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Golang Environment – GOPATH vs go.mod]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/golang-environment-gopath-vs-go-mod/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/golang-environment-gopath-vs-go-mod/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T00:23:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll explore the differences between the traditional GOPATH  environment and the go.mod based environment for Go programming.  This distinction has significant implications for how Go developers structure and manage their project workspaces and dependencies. We'll start by understanding the GOPATH environment, its organization and its]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Otavio Ehrenberger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Data Validation Rules in Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-data-validation-rules-excel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-data-validation-rules-excel/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T00:07:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data validation is a feature in Excel used in restricting data entry in specific cells. It can also prompt the user to enter valid data into the cells based on the rules and restrictions provided by the creator of the Excel worksheet.  When setting up a workbook, you might]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Faith Oyama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Sort Dictionary by Key – How to Sort a Dict with Keys]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-sort-dictionary-by-key/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-sort-dictionary-by-key/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T23:57:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sorting is a fundamental operation in computer programming that involves arranging elements in a specific order.  Whether you're working with numbers, strings, or complex data structures, sorting plays a crucial role in organizing and manipulating data efficiently.  From small arrays to large datasets, sorting algorithms allow programmers to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Exactly is Node.js? A Guide for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-exactly-is-node-guide-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-exactly-is-node-guide-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T23:08:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're thinking about doing back-end development using JavaScript, you will hear the term ‘Node.js’. Node is often associated with developing powerful web servers. But what exactly is Node.js? Is it a JavaScript framework just like Angular [https://angular.io/]? Is it a programming language? Is it a JavaScript Library? Is it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amazing Enyichi Agu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Success At Scale, A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/success-at-scale-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/success-at-scale-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet “Success At Scale”, our upcoming book with best-practice case studies from industry experts. Print and eBook shipping in fall 2023. Pre-order the book.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Golang Handbook – A Beginner's Guide to Learning Go]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-golang-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-golang-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T18:11:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Go programming language has been exploding in popularity. Tons of companies are using Go to build scalable, modern, backend infrastructure.  If you're looking to learn a new programming language, Go is a great choice. It's fast, lightweight, has an amazing open source community, and is actually quite easy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lane Wagner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build and Deploy a LeetCode Clone with React, Next JS, TypeScript, Tailwind CSS, Firebase]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-and-deploy-a-leetcode-clone-with-react-next-js-typescript-tailwind-css-firebase/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-and-deploy-a-leetcode-clone-with-react-next-js-typescript-tailwind-css-firebase/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T15:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solving coding challenges on the LeetCode website is a great way to improve your developer skills. But an even better way to improve your skills is to develop your own LeetCode website. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Component Lifecycle Methods – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-component-lifecycle-methods/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-component-lifecycle-methods/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T14:28:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In React, components have a lifecycle that consists of different phases. Each phase has a set of lifecycle methods that are called at specific points in the component's lifecycle. These methods allow you to control the component's behavior and perform specific actions at different stages of its lifecycle. A component's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Basics for DevOps – How to Setup a Linux Machine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/aws-basics-for-devops/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/aws-basics-for-devops/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T14:26:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To create an application like WhatsApp or Facebook, you'd need many servers (30-40), operating system licenses, routers, cables, switches, gateways, air conditioning units, and employees for maintenance.  All this can be expensive and time-consuming, and there is no guarantee that the application will be successful in the market. But]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Satyam Tripathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Socket Programming in Python?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/socket-programming-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/socket-programming-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T14:25:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn how to code a socket program in Python. But before that, let's understand what a socket is and where you might use it. We can define a socket as a quick connection which allows the transmission of data between two processes on the same]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>P S Mohammed Ali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Impact Of Agile Methodologies On Code Quality]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/impact-agile-methodologies-code-quality/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/impact-agile-methodologies-code-quality/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Say goodbye to traditional workflows and embrace Agile to unlock the power of high-quality code. Discover how Agile methodologies promote simplicity, modularization, readability, and continuous improvement, resulting in faster turnaround times, more responsive development processes, and ultimately, the creation of high-quality software that meets customer needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sarah Oke Okolo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 61 With Rachel Andrew: What Is Web Platform Baseline?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/smashing-podcast-episode-61/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/smashing-podcast-episode-61/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we’re talking about Web Platform Baseline. What is it, and how can it help determine your browser support policy? Drew McLellan talks to expert Rachel Andrew to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practical Design Tips And Guidelines For Beginner Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/practical-design-tips-guidelines-beginner-designers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/practical-design-tips-guidelines-beginner-designers/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-22T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s easy for beginner designers to get overwhelmed and lose confidence when creating presentations, landing pages, app and web design mockups, and even cards. Laurent Baumann shares a few simple guidelines and practical tips to help you in such situations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Laurent Baumann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Deal With Big Tooling Upgrades In Large Organizations]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/big-tooling-upgrades-large-organizations/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/big-tooling-upgrades-large-organizations/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The process of upgrading large third-party packages in equally large organizations is rarely, if ever, as easy as running an npm update and calling it a day in this context. Joran Quinten shares valuable lessons from his team’s experiences in upgrading third-party code that affects codebases across the entire organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joran Quinten)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design Patterns Are A Better Way To Collaborate On Your Design System]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/design-patterns-collaborate-design-system/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/design-patterns-collaborate-design-system/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every company and team has to have deep collaboration between engineering and design to get the value out of a design system (and not go nuts). Building design patterns first unblock people to work in parallel, keeps people synced up, and results in reusable modules that speed up your next project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ben Clemens)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solving Media Object Float Issues With CSS Block Formatting Contexts]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/media-object-float-issues-css-block-formatting-contexts/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/media-object-float-issues-css-block-formatting-contexts/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article covers common problems using CSS floats and how to solve them using a block formatting context (BFC). Whether you are a beginner or an experienced web developer, you will learn valuable insights and practical solutions for dealing with CSS float issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Gabriel Shoyombo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Sticky Menus: UX Guidelines]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/sticky-menus-ux-guidelines/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/sticky-menus-ux-guidelines/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-12T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are sticky headers always a good idea? Best practices for designing sticky headers, with examples, UX guidelines and usability considerations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Boost Your Design Workflow With Setapp]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/boost-design-workflow-setapp/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/boost-design-workflow-setapp/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, we’ll explore efficient tools to save time and speed up your workflow. Focus on what you do best — designing high-quality work, and let these tools handle the rest!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Rachel How)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Redux Toolkit With TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/guide-redux-toolkit-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/guide-redux-toolkit-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Redux Toolkit documentation calls the library a better way to write Redux logic for React apps and a simple and efficient toolkit for Redux development. In this article, you will learn about the Redux toolkit by building an app that tracks project issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Deepak Kumar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use AI Tools To Skyrocket Your Programming Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/ai-tools-skyrocket-programming-productivity/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/ai-tools-skyrocket-programming-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rise of Artificial Intelligence (AI) in recent times has incited fear in many over losing their jobs. However, that shouldn’t be the case. On the contrary, AI is an opportunity to take your programming to the next level when used tactfully with the right knowledge, as we’ll cover today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shane Duggan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Safest Way To Hide Your API Keys When Using React]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/safest-way-hide-api-keys-react/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/safest-way-hide-api-keys-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to make sure your API keys are safe and sound when working with React? Jessica Joseph’s got you covered! She will show you the best ways to hide your API keys, from using environment variables to building your own back-end proxy server.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jessica Joseph)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning JavaScript With Imagination]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/learning-javascript-with-imagination/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/learning-javascript-with-imagination/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the story of how one little octopus, explaining one beginner’s concept, carried such weight and power for Kylo that it drove his work and led him to research something that is really quite silly. And yet, it transformed how he learned to write — and finally understand — JavaScript.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kylo Robinson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Growing Need For Effective Password Management]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/effective-password-management/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/effective-password-management/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Highlighting the advantages of self-hosted solutions over cloud-based alternatives and exploring collaborative password management and more, P demonstrates how to organize convenient and secure password management in a company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iliya Garakh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 60 With Mei Zhang: How Do You Design A Design Process?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/smashing-podcast-episode-60/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/smashing-podcast-episode-60/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re talking about the process of design. How do you build a process to enable your best work? Vitaly Friedman talks to designer Mei Zhang to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make Your May Magnificent (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-30T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May is almost here, so what better occasion could there be for some fresh and inspiring desktop and mobile wallpapers? Created with love by artists and designers from across the globe, the wallpapers in this post come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>