<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-01-10T00:10:44.611Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-01-10T00:10:44.611Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do Zsh Configuration Files Work?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-do-zsh-configuration-files-work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-do-zsh-configuration-files-work/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T20:37:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beginners often get confused when configuring Zsh shell on a Mac. Zsh shell offers four configuration files with no discernible differences. Particularly, ~/.zshrc and ~/.zprofile appear to be identical, leaving us wondering which one to use.  In this article, you'll learn the difference and a simple guideline for your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kehoe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Work with RESTful APIs in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-work-with-restful-apis-in-react-simplified-steps-and-practical-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-work-with-restful-apis-in-react-simplified-steps-and-practical-examples/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T19:09:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RESTful APIs are a crucial component in modern web development. They allow communication between different applications over the internet.  REST (which stands for Representational State Transfer) APIs operate on a stateless client-server architecture, providing a standardized way to create, read, update, and delete resources. Integrating RESTful APIs with React]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The React Roadmap for 2024 – How to Learn React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-react-roadmap-learn-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-react-roadmap-learn-react/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T18:57:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, I'll break down a complete roadmap that will cover all the concepts, libraries, and tools to help you become a React developer in 2024. My goal is to show you the happy path in React, navigating you away from pitfalls so you can spend your time on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a GitHub Template Repository for Scaffolding with React, Vite, and TailwindCSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-github-template-repository-with-react-vite-and-tailwindcss/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-github-template-repository-with-react-vite-and-tailwindcss/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T18:04:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers love productivity. When it comes to coding, we want to do things fast and we look out for opportunities to re-use things as much as possible. Say, you are getting started with a ReactJS project and want to use TailwindCSS  for the same. The first time, it would]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TAPAS ADHIKARY</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use New CSS Features to Build a Progress Indicator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-new-css-features-to-build-a-progress-indicator/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-new-css-features-to-build-a-progress-indicator/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T15:39:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the last 7 months, I’ve had my head down building Component Odyssey [https://component-odyssey.com/]. It’s been a richly fulfilling project and I’m eager for people to take the course and learn heaps about building component libraries using web components. I’ve seen some incredible demos over the past year, and wanted]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrico Karoulla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Data Analysis with Comprehensive 19-Hour Bootcamp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-data-analysis-with-comprehensive-19-hour-bootcamp/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-data-analysis-with-comprehensive-19-hour-bootcamp/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T15:39:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world of data analysis is vast and continually evolving, and staying ahead in this field requires a solid foundation in its core technologies and methodologies. We just published a 19-hour data analysis bootcamp on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This bootcamp, developed by Alex Freberg, provides an immersive learning experience]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use pnpm – Installation and Common Commands]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-pnpm/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-pnpm/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T15:31:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[pnpm is like npm, but it's way faster and more efficient. After all, the starting p stands for performant. According to its creator, Zoltan Kochan, pnpm "allows you to save gigabytes of disk space." Many popular projects including Next.js, Vite, Svelte, and even freeCodeCamp use pnpm. So now is a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Biswas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make React Apps SEO-Friendly – A Handbook for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-seo-friendly-react-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-seo-friendly-react-apps/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T15:25:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When developing your web applications, you should always consider search engine optimization (SEO) techniques. Many things come into play when you're making sure your web application operates as intended and has an online presence. Search engines such as Google, Bing, and Yahoo serve as the primary medium for users seeking]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okosa Leonard Onyekachukwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless Architecture Patterns and Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/serverless-architecture-patterns-and-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/serverless-architecture-patterns-and-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T01:07:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless architecture has become a hot topic in the developer world, and for good reason.  It promises a paradigm shift – one where we leave behind the burdens of server management and focus solely on building and deploying code. No more provisioning VMs, patching software, or scaling infrastructure manually.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Faith Oyama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collect.js Tutorial – How to Work with JavaScript Arrays and Objects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/work-with-javascript-arrays-objects-with-collect-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/work-with-javascript-arrays-objects-with-collect-js/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T22:38:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript arrays are one of the most important data structures in the language, since everything is already an object in JavaScript. They're useful in so many applications, and many other data structures build on top of JavaScript arrays and objects. While the language provides a lot of helpful array and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zubair Idris Aweda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SolidStart: A Different Breed Of Meta-Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/solidstart-different-breed-meta-framework/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/solidstart-different-breed-meta-framework/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready for a little exercise of pulling a framework apart and putting the pieces back together? In this article, Atila Fassina explains how meta-frameworks have evolved around core libraries in their own unique ways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API And Delightful UI Animations (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/view-transitions-api-ui-animations-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/view-transitions-api-ui-animations-part2/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API is a new — but game-changing — feature that allows us to do the types of reactive state-based UI and page transitions that have traditionally been exclusive to JavaScript frameworks. In the second half of this mini two-part series, Adrian Bece expands on the demos from the first article to demonstrate how the View Transitions API can be used to transition not just elements between two states but the transition between full views and pages in single-page and multi-page applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Magic Of New Beginnings (January 2024 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2024/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s start into the new year with a little inspiration boost: wallpapers created with love by the community for the community. Happy 2024!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Sense Of “Senseless” JavaScript Features]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/making-sense-of-senseless-javascript-features/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/making-sense-of-senseless-javascript-features/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript may be the most popular client-side language in the world, but it’s far from perfect and not without its quirks. Juan Diego Rodriguez examines several “absurd” JavaScript eccentricities and explains how they made it into the language as well as how to avoid them in your own code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API And Delightful UI Animations (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/view-transitions-api-ui-animations-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/view-transitions-api-ui-animations-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API is a new — but game-changing — feature that allows us to do the types of reactive state-based UI and page transitions that have traditionally been exclusive to JavaScript frameworks. In the first part of this mini two-part series, Adrian Bece thoroughly explains why we need the API and demonstrates its basic usage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New CSS Viewport Units Do Not Solve The Classic Scrollbar Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/new-css-viewport-units-not-solve-classic-scrollbar-problem/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/new-css-viewport-units-not-solve-classic-scrollbar-problem/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the introduction of CSS viewport units in 2012, many of us have been using `width: 100vw` as a way to set an element’s width to the full width of the viewport. But, as Šime Vidas explains in this deep dive, `100vw` does not always represent the full width of the viewport due to differences in how browsers handle scrollbars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Šime Vidas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Components For Consumption, Not Complexity (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/building-components-consumption-not-complexity-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/building-components-consumption-not-complexity-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part 2 concentrates on the key points from Luis’ framework and practical tips about managing a design system that should be both robust and easy to adopt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Luis Ouriach)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Scroll Snapping Aligned With Global Page Layout: A Full-Width Slider Case Study]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/css-scroll-snapping-aligned-global-page-layout-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/css-scroll-snapping-aligned-global-page-layout-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you run into a situation where you need the padding of one element to align with the padding of another element? In this article, Brecht De Ruyte demonstrates the issue with a full-width slider component that breaks out of the main page container and shares a couple of techniques to keep it visually aligned with other elements on the page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Brecht De Ruyte)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Components For Consumption, Not Complexity (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/building-components-consumption-not-complexity-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/building-components-consumption-not-complexity-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design systems can be of immense help, but failure to adopt them invalidates the hard work that goes into building the thing in the first place! In this two-part series of articles, Luis shares his experience with design systems and how you can overcome the potential pitfalls.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Luis Ouriach)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>