<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-07-23T00:11:35.024Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-07-23T00:11:35.024Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Art Of Looking Back: A Critical Reflection For Individual Contributors]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/critical-reflection-individual-contributors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/critical-reflection-individual-contributors/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover the importance of critical reflective practice and challenge some beliefs about reflection and its role in our work and growth. Kristian Mikhel suggests a critical reflective routine for individual contributors and gives some practical recommendations that will make reflection meaningful and actionable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kristian Mikhel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Integrate ChatGPT with Google Sheets Using Google Apps Script]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-chat-gpt-formulas-in-google-sheets/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-chat-gpt-formulas-in-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:06:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to this tutorial on how to integrate ChatGPT with Google Spreadsheets using the GPT API and Google Apps Script. We will create two custom formulas, GPT_SUMMARY and GPT_SIMPLIFY. You can use GPT_SUMMARY to summarize a large passage or text into a few bullet points for easy reading. And you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nibesh Khadka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Full Stack Development with Next.js and Supabase by Building a Twitter Clone.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-full-stack-development-with-next-js-and-supabase-by-building-a-twitter-clone/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-full-stack-development-with-next-js-and-supabase-by-building-a-twitter-clone/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T15:49:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Turn this: Into this: We just launched a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you master full stack development with Next.js 13 and Supabase by building a Twitter clone. The course also uses Tailwind CSS and TypeScript. This intensive course has been expertly developed by Pranjal Soni,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Join the #100daysofOSS Challenge and Embrace the Power of Open Source]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/100-days-of-oss-challenge/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/100-days-of-oss-challenge/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T20:25:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I made my first pull request (PR) to an open-source project six years ago. Technically, it was pre-work for a bootcamp that I would eventually complete, but it started my journey into open source.  It wasn’t until a couple of years later, after completing my bootcamp, that I saw]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BekahHW</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Project – How to Convert Multiple Images into a Single PDF File]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/convert-multiple-images-into-a-single-pdf-file-with-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/convert-multiple-images-into-a-single-pdf-file-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T20:13:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating projects is the best way to learn a programming language. It is fun and it's a creative way to learn new things.  Whenever I try to learn a new language or new technology, I try to create a project, whether it's a small byte-sized or big project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manipulate HTML and CSS Using JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/manipulate-html-and-css-using-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/manipulate-html-and-css-using-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T18:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, the HTML DOM (Document Object Model) represents the structure and content of an HTML document as a tree-like structure. In it, each element, attribute, and text node in the HTML document is represented as a node in the DOM tree.  In this article you're going to learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Information Architecture? How to Create Userflows and Sitemaps for UX Design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/information-architecture-userflow-sitemap/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/information-architecture-userflow-sitemap/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T20:40:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At some point in your design career, you may hear about Information Architecture (or IA). You might even have to create a userflow or sitemap. Now, this article aims to help you go back to the basics and remind you of the meaning and importance of IA. So if you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijelekhai Faith Olohijere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Are Two Similar Objects Not Equal in JavaScript?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-are-two-similar-objects-not-equal-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-are-two-similar-objects-not-equal-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T18:53:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, two objects may not be equal even though they appear to be similar. Why is that the case? 🤔 Let's understand why. For example: const obj1 = {   name: "Dillion" } const obj2 = {   name: "Dillion" } console.log(obj1 === obj2) // false As]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern Python App Design with ttkbootstrap]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/modern-python-app-design-with-ttkbootstrap/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/modern-python-app-design-with-ttkbootstrap/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T18:39:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking to add a touch of modernity to your Python apps? Do you want to master Tkinter and ttkbootstrap for a sleek, contemporary design? freeCodeCamp.org has just launched a brand new video course on YouTube that will teach you how to easily implement modern designs in your Tkinter-based]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLI Shells – A Brief History of Human-Computer Interfaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/shells-a-history-of-human-computer-interfaces/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/shells-a-history-of-human-computer-interfaces/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T16:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A computer is basically a piece of electronic circuitry that performs tasks as instructed by its users. But for a human to interact with this hardware, they must really know and understand how it works. The person must also know the order in which to give the computer various tasks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chidiadi Anyanwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Measure Django Code Quality Using SonarQube, Pytest, and Coverage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-measure-django-code-quality-using-sonarqube-pytest-and-coverage/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-measure-django-code-quality-using-sonarqube-pytest-and-coverage/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T16:36:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greetings, fellow coding enthusiasts! We're going to dive deep into the realm of Django code quality assessment. In this comprehensive guide, I'll walk you through an in-depth approach to measuring the code quality of your Django-based application. By the end of this tutorial, you will be able to:  1.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ridwan Yusuf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Age-Inclusive Products: Guidelines And Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/designing-age-inclusive-products-guidelines-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/designing-age-inclusive-products-guidelines-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With an estimated one in every eight individuals worldwide surpassing the age of 60, who are actively adopting online shopping, the need for user-friendly interfaces tailored to their needs becomes apparent. Explore the guidelines to help you design inclusive products for all, particularly for an older audience and your future self.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michal Halperin Ben Zvi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writing CSS In 2023: Is It Any Different Than A Few Years Ago?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/writing-css-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/writing-css-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS is evolving faster than ever. With all of the new features that are now available — and forthcoming — since we got Flexbox and Grid years ago, the way we write CSS is evolving, too. In this article, Geoff Graham shares which features have had the most influence on his current approaches to CSS, as well as those that have not (at least yet).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create A Rapid Research Program To Support Insights At Scale]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/create-rapid-research-program-support-insights-scale/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/create-rapid-research-program-support-insights-scale/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate your organization’s growth and innovation with the power of Rapid Research. From inception to implementation, here is the step-by-step roadmap on how to build the program from scratch and uncover the untapped ROI opportunities waiting to propel your initiatives to new heights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Devin Harold)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 63 With Chris Ferdinandi: What Is The Transitional Web?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/smashing-podcast-episode-63/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/smashing-podcast-episode-63/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of The Smashing Podcast, we’re talking about The Transitional Web. What is it, and how does it describe the technologies we’re using? Drew McLellan talks to Chris Ferdinandi to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Become A Better Speaker At Conferences]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/become-better-speaker-conferences/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/become-better-speaker-conferences/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Andy Budd, curator of UX London and Leading Design conferences, outlines some of the things that make a potentially amazing presentation, as well as a few big gotchas. If you’ve ever wondered what it takes to get a speaking slot at a conference, this article is for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andy Budd)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shines, Perspective, And Rotations: Fancy CSS 3D Effects For Images]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/shines-perspective-rotations-css-3d-effects-images/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/shines-perspective-rotations-css-3d-effects-images/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS has all kinds of tricks that are capable of turning images into neat, interactive elements. This article is a collection of fancy 3D effects for images that demonstrate those CSS powers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The UX Of Flight Searches: How We Challenged Industry Standards]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/reimagining-flight-search-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/reimagining-flight-search-ux/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As of today, the world’s 50 top airlines have all agreed on the same flight search pattern. Yet the path to booking the right flight remains frustrating and confusing. Is there really only one solution? Explore the thought experiment which turned the seemingly untouchable pattern on its head and offered new food for thought.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Robert Goesch)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sustainable Design Toolkits And Frameworks]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/sustainable-design-toolkits-and-resources/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/sustainable-design-toolkits-and-resources/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can we create products and experiences that don’t cause harm to the planet and to the people who use them? What do we need to consider to make more sustainable design decisions and reduce the carbon footprint of our websites? In this post, we compiled valuable resources that will get you familiar with the principles of sustainable design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke &amp; Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Off To New Adventures (July 2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-july-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-july-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s welcome the new month with some fresh desktop wallpapers. Designed by artists and designers from around the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar for July 2023. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s The Perfect Design Process?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/perfect-design-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/perfect-design-process/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The design process is messy. You might be following a structured approach, but too often, it takes a life of its own. And before you know it, you are designing in chaos, with last-minute changes and missed deadlines. So, what’s the “perfect” design process?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful DevTools Tips and Tricks]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/popular-devtools-tips/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/popular-devtools-tips/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s discover the most popular DevTools tips that can boost your productivity and revolutionize your debugging workflow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Patrick Brosset)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind The Curtains Of Wikipedia Redesign]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/behind-curtains-wikipedia-redesign/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/behind-curtains-wikipedia-redesign/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Wikipedia team shipped a redesign of the ubiquitous and one of the [most visited websites](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_most_visited_websites) on the web. Alex Hollender and Jon Robson led the work and generously discussed the effort with us in a thorough, wide-ranging interview that covers the design, development, and processes that went into the project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Penpot’s Flex Layout: Building CSS Layouts In A Design Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/penpot-flex-layout-building-css-layouts-design-tool/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/penpot-flex-layout-building-css-layouts-design-tool/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s article, let’s explore how we can use Flex Layout and see how it empowers designers with greater control over their work while saving everyone’s time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>