<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-03-21T00:11:03.570Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-03-21T00:11:03.570Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now Shipping: Success At Scale, A New Smashing Book by Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/success-at-scale-book-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/success-at-scale-book-release/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s here, and it’s shipping! Meet our newest Smashing book, ”Success at Scale”. It’s filled with practical insights and real-world case studies of how big changes can be made on projects of any size. Addy Osmani has curated finest examples, case studies and interviews to help you get successful at scale. Jump to the details and get the book right away.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Abstraction in Coding? A Guide for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-abstraction-in-coding/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-abstraction-in-coding/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T22:29:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've met and talked to multiple new coders recently, and I see a common mistake they all seem to make. They don't embrace and understand abstractions in their code, or in their learning. But what are abstractions? And why are they important? Let's dive in! What is an Abstraction? In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kealan Parr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intro to Stacks – Data Structure and Algorithm Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/intro-to-stacks-data-structure-and-algorithm-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/intro-to-stacks-data-structure-and-algorithm-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T15:08:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding the stack data structure is important for anyone interested in computer science. It is a key data structure used in many programs and also coding challenges. Understanding stacks can help you in technical interviews. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you master]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn App Development with Spring Boot 3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-app-development-with-spring-boot-3/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-app-development-with-spring-boot-3/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T14:57:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3 is an advanced framework that simplifies the development of new Spring applications through convention over configuration, providing a range of out-of-the-box functionalities for building enterprise-grade applications efficiently. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to develop apps with Spring]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Always Have A BuildContext in Flutter Outside of UI Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-always-have-a-buildcontext-in-flutter-outside-ui-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-always-have-a-buildcontext-in-flutter-outside-ui-code/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T14:42:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The BuildContext provides important app-wide configuration information to all widgets in the widget tree. It is always naturally available in build methods and within State classes.  In this article, we will explore how we can obtain a valid BuildContext outside the scope of its natural availability. Table Of Contents]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Obumuneme Nwabude</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Protect Data in Transit using HMAC and Diffie-Hellman in Node.js [Full Handbook]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hmac-diffie-hellman-in-node/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hmac-diffie-hellman-in-node/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T23:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data integrity refers to the assurance that data remains accurate, unaltered, and consistent throughout its lifecycle. In communication, it is crucial to ensure data integrity to safeguard against unintended alterations and malicious interventions during transmission. The integrity of Digital Data is accomplished using Hashing Algorithms. The  crypto module in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamdaan Ali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Control the Brightness of an LED with a Potentiometer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/control-led-with-potentiometer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/control-led-with-potentiometer/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T19:48:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Potentiometers are used in various electronic circuits and systems. You can use them in electronic devices to control volume, brightness, motor speed, voltage regulation, and so on. You've most likely used a potentiometer before with appliances like radios, microwaves, blenders, electric fans, game controllers, and others. They are generally used]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sketchnotes And Key Takeaways From SmashingConf Antwerp 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/sketchnotes-key-takeaways-smashingconf-antwerp-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/sketchnotes-key-takeaways-smashingconf-antwerp-2023/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How was the first SmashingConf in Antwerp, you ask? One of our online attendees, Krisztina Szerovay, shares her sketchnotes and takeaways of the talks that were held on both days of the conference — with photos and recordings saved as best for last. [See you live in Antwerp this year, maybe?](https://smashingconf.com/antwerp-2024)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Krisztina Szerovay)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Linked list? Types of Linked List with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-linked-list-types-and-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-linked-list-types-and-examples/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T15:25:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A linked list is a linear data structure consisting of a sequence of nodes. Unlike arrays, linked lists do not require contiguous memory allocation. Instead, each node is dynamically allocated its own memory space.  Nodes are connected through references, forming the linked structure. One advantage of linked lists is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sule-Balogun Olanrewaju Ganiu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Migrate Your Local Data to MongoDB Atlas]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mongodb-data-migration/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mongodb-data-migration/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T14:40:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data forms the bedrock of our daily lives, as a lot of day-to-day decision-making is hinged on its existence. Just like energy, data can be transformed from one medium to another. So far, web development has become much more advanced, and data migration and backup is an essential skill every]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>oluwatobi Joshua</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use Prettier in Visual Studio Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-prettier-in-visual-studio-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-prettier-in-visual-studio-code/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T12:35:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nowadays, every tech company strives to build quality software fast. That's why every developer must learn how to write clean and readable code.  But when a project is managed by multiple developers, the focus shifts into consistency especially in terms of written code.  Keeping a consistent code style]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matéush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Reactive Programming? Beginner's Guide to Writing Reactive Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/reactive-programming-beginner-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/reactive-programming-beginner-guide/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T09:02:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to our journey through the dynamic world of reactive programming! This fascinating paradigm is all about building responsive, resilient, and adaptable applications that effortlessly manage vast amounts of data almost instantly. Imagine writing a program that needs to react instantly to changes—be it user inputs, messages from other systems,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pacifique LINJANJA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Event Calendars For Web Made Easy With These Commercial Options]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/event-calendars-web-commercial-options/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/event-calendars-web-commercial-options/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Collection of top-notch calendar components for seamless event scheduling. Whether you prefer ready-to-use setups or enjoy tweaking code for a tailored experience, these calendars have you covered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Preethi Sam)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Success At Scale: Last Chance For Pre-Sale Price]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/success-at-scale-book-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/success-at-scale-book-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our next book, “Success at Scale” is finally at the printer, which means we’ll be shipping books soon. It’s also your last chance to get the book at the presale price. Get your copy and save now!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern CSS Tooltips And Speech Bubbles (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/modern-css-tooltips-speech-bubbles-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/modern-css-tooltips-speech-bubbles-part2/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Part 1 of this series, Temani Afif explored different CSS techniques to create tooltip shapes. The main challenge was to rely on a single element and create optimized code that could easily be controlled using CSS variables to update the size, shape, and position of the tail. In this second part, you are going explore more shapes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The End Of My Gatsby Journey]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/end-of-gatsby-journey/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/end-of-gatsby-journey/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[“Gatsby headaches”](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/gatsby-headaches-i18n-part-1/) are over. Juan Diego Rodríguez reflects on his decision to stop using Gatsby as his go-to framework. Through a detailed examination of its strengths and weaknesses, he provides valuable insights and alternative options for developers navigating their tooling choices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern CSS Tooltips And Speech Bubbles (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/modern-css-tooltips-speech-bubbles-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/03/modern-css-tooltips-speech-bubbles-part1/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tooltips are a very common pattern used in CSS for years. There are a lot of ways to approach tooltips in CSS, though some evoke headaches with all the magic numbers they require. In this article, Temani Afif presents modern techniques to create tooltips with the smallest amount of markup and the greatest amount of flexibility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Waiting For Spring (March 2024 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-march-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-march-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new batch of desktop wallpapers is for you. Designed by artists and designers from across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar for March 2024. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reporting Core Web Vitals With The Performance API]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/reporting-core-web-vitals-performance-api/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/reporting-core-web-vitals-performance-api/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Performance API is a set of standards for measuring and evaluating performance metrics with JavaScript. This article demonstrates how to use the Performance API to generate performance metrics directly in the DOM to create your own reporting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Web Designer’s Accessibility Advocacy Toolkit]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/web-designer-accessibility-advocacy-toolkit/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/web-designer-accessibility-advocacy-toolkit/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital designer Yichan Wang has put together this collection of strategies and selling points to help you encourage and advocate for accessibility in your place of work, including useful scripts you can use as starting points.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yichan Wang)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vanilla JavaScript, Libraries, And The Quest For Stateful DOM Rendering]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/vanilla-javascript-libraries-quest-stateful-dom-rendering/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/vanilla-javascript-libraries-quest-stateful-dom-rendering/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s well-established that the web faces wide-ranging usability and performance issues, from user-hostile UI patterns and twisted search results to sluggish performance and battery-draining bloat. In this article, Frederik examines one small-but-significant aspect where developers take the reins: Painting pixels on the screen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederik Dohr)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>