<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-02-16T00:09:52.669Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-02-16T00:09:52.669Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript in the Browser – How the Document Object Model (DOM) and Events Work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-in-the-browser-dom-and-events/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-in-the-browser-dom-and-events/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T20:07:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this in-depth tutorial, you'll learn all about the Document Object Model, or DOM for short. As a web developer, understanding the DOM is fundamental for interacting with web browsers and creating dynamic web applications.  Throughout this guide, we will explore the DOM's hierarchical tree structure, essential properties, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samyak Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn SvelteKit in 2 hours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-sveltekit-full-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-sveltekit-full-course/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T18:47:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SvelteKit is the next evolution of Svelte, a modern JavaScript framework that compiles your code to highly efficient, vanilla JavaScript at build time. It's a great framework to learn for developers seeking to hone their skills or dive into modern web frameworks. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to Make Art with Code – p5.js Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/art-of-coding-with-p5js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/art-of-coding-with-p5js/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T18:39:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[p5.js is a JavaScript library that's transforming the way artists and designers approach make art with code. If you're intrigued by the intersection of art and programming, freeCodeCamp's YouTube course on p5.js is an ideal starting point.  Patt Vira created this course. She loves making art with code and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Draw with JavaScript on an HTML Canvas Element – Gorilla Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-draw-a-gorilla-with-javascript-on-html-canvas/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-draw-a-gorilla-with-javascript-on-html-canvas/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T16:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drawing from code can be fun for many reasons. You can generate art that follows a certain logic. You can create animations by moving only parts of an image. And you can even build up a whole game as I covered in this tutorial [/news/gorillas-game-in-javascript/]. In my last article, we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hunor Márton Borbély</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Chrome DevTools – Simple Strategies for Smarter Web Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/chrome-devtools/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/chrome-devtools/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T16:12:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a web developer, there are many tools out there – in addition to your code editor – that can make you more efficient.  It doesn't matter if you're just starting out or have been coding for years. Knowing how to effectively use Developer Tools (DevTools for short) can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ophy Boamah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the App Directory in Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/app-directory-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/app-directory-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T00:52:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're building a project using the latest version of Next.js, you'll be prompted to select between using the app/ directory or the pages/ directory. The  app/ directory is now the recommended way of building apps in Next.js. In this article, you'll learn how to maximize the potential of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Oghenetejiri Ukumakube</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Map Method – Syntax and Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-map-method/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-map-method/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T00:50:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript's map method, introduced in ECMAScript 5, is a fundamental tool for array manipulation and transformation. This method is versatile and simple, and has become a staple in modern JavaScript programming.  In this article, we'll explore the map method's syntax and its wide array of applications, ranging from basic]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahil Mahapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Custom React Hook – a Hands-on Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-custom-react-hooks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-custom-react-hooks/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T17:39:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have been working with React, I bet you've had the opportunity to use hooks. But have you ever tried to create your own hook?  Today I will help you create your first custom hook and explain how they can improve your codebase. Why Create Custom Hooks? You]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matéush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Backend Development by Building a CRUD API with Node and MongoDB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/crud-api-with-node-js-express-mongodb/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/crud-api-with-node-js-express-mongodb/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T15:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A key part of most backend development projects is CRUD. Simply put, CRUD stands for Create, Read, Update, Delete. These fundamental operations form the basis of how data is handled in many applications, making understanding them crucial for backend development. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Accessibility Standards Can Empower Better Chart Visual Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/accessibility-standards-empower-better-chart-visual-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/accessibility-standards-empower-better-chart-visual-design/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility for data visualization extends well beyond web standards, at least if you’re trying to create an experience that’s actually useful. This article focuses on techniques for creating useful and accessible visualizations that extend well beyond compliance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kent Eisenhuth)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started with Golang – a Developer Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/golang-developer-roadmap/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/golang-developer-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T14:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Go programming language – also known as Golang – is now almost 15 years old. And it's become a popular choice for web development and microservices thanks to its performance and efficient resource utilisation.  Go jobs are also quite well-paid. As per the Glassdoor report [https://www.glassdoor.com/Salaries/golang-developer-salary-SRCH_KO0,16.htm?countryPickerRedirect=true] , the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shubham Chadokar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Practical Guide To Designing For Children]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/practical-guide-design-children/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/practical-guide-design-children/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to design for children aged 3–12, with insights into user behavior, considerations for parents, and practical UX guidelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Draw Radar Charts In Web]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/draw-radar-charts-web/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/draw-radar-charts-web/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A radar chart — also commonly called a spider chart — is yet another way to visualize data and make connections. Radar charts are inherently geometric, making them both a perfect fit and fun to make with CSS, thanks to the `polygon()` function. Read along as Preethi Sam demonstrates the process and sprinkles it with a pinch of JavaScript to make a handy, reusable component.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Preethi Sam)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frequently Heard In My Beginning Front-End Web Development Class]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/frequently-heard-beginning-front-end-web-development-class/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/frequently-heard-beginning-front-end-web-development-class/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What could we learn from entry-level students in front-end web development? As seasoned professionals, you might think you’ve seen it all, but the truth is that the newcomers are asking the most intriguing questions and making connections that those of us who have spent years on the front end may have never considered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Development Is Getting Too Complex, And It May Be Our Fault]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/web-development-getting-too-complex/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/web-development-getting-too-complex/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An overwhelming number of frameworks and tooling available today gives the impression that web development has gotten perhaps too complex. Juan Diego Rodríguez explores if web development really is that complex and, most importantly, how we can prevent it from getting even more difficult than we already perceive it to be.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Designing For Older Adults]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/guide-designing-older-adults/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/guide-designing-older-adults/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With one billion people aged 60 or older worldwide, inclusivity is more important than ever. Learn how to create digital experiences that empower independence and competence for older adults while enhancing usability for all. An upcoming part of Smart Interface Design Patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Words Cannot Describe: Designing For AI Beyond Conversational Interfaces]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/designing-ai-beyond-conversational-interfaces/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/02/designing-ai-beyond-conversational-interfaces/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Artificial Intelligence evolves the computing paradigm, designers have an opportunity to craft more intuitive user interfaces. Maximillian Piras examines how the latest AI capabilities can reshape the future of human-computer interaction beyond conversation alone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Maximillian Piras)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[29 Days Of Inspiration (February 2024 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-february-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-february-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With February just around the corner, how about a little inspiration boost? We might have one for you: desktop wallpapers created with love by the community for the community. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Feature Trap: Why Feature Centricity Is Harming Your Product]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/feature-centricity-harming-product/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/feature-centricity-harming-product/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most product teams commonly adopt a feature-centric mindset, finding them convenient for brainstorming, drafting requirement documents, and integrating into backlogs and ticketing systems. In this article, Andy Budd shows how fixation with features might be holding you back and how making a few small tweaks to your process could make an entire world of difference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andy Budd)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Simple Guide To Retrieval Augmented Generation Language Models]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/guide-retrieval-augmented-generation-language-models/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/guide-retrieval-augmented-generation-language-models/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Language models have shown impressive capabilities. But that doesn’t mean they’re without faults, as anyone who has witnessed a ChatGPT “hallucination” can attest. In this article, Joas Pambou diagnoses the symptoms that cause hallucinations and explains not only what RAG is but also different approaches for using it to solve language model limitations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joas Pambou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Blurry Shimmer Effect]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/css-blurry-shimmer-effect/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/css-blurry-shimmer-effect/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taking inspiration from shadows, author Yair Even Or creates the same sort of thing, only with a blurring effect in place of the shadow. Read along for a step-by-step explanation of how it comes together using a combination of masks, gradients, and the good ol’ `backdrop-filter` property.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yair Even Or)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Dilemma In Graphic Design: Steering Towards Excellence In Typography And Beyond]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/ai-dilemma-graphic-design-typography/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/01/ai-dilemma-graphic-design-typography/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI promises a major upheaval in typography, with designers finding themselves navigating both opportunities and challenges. How will it impact quality, design roles, and our use of type in the future? As we explore this new frontier, we realise that we are at a juncture as significant as Gutenberg’s press, set to redefine how we interact with text and visual communication.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Filip Paldia &amp; Jamie Clarke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>