<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-06-27T00:11:53.048Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-06-27T00:11:53.048Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind The Curtains Of Wikipedia Redesign]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/behind-curtains-wikipedia-redesign/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/behind-curtains-wikipedia-redesign/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Wikipedia team shipped a redesign of the ubiquitous and one of the [most visited websites](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_most_visited_websites) on the web. Alex Hollender and Jon Robson led the work and generously discussed the effort with us in a thorough, wide-ranging interview that covers the design, development, and processes that went into the project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Exception Filters to Catch Bugs in Nest.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/exception-filters-in-nestjs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/exception-filters-in-nestjs/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T21:38:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's common to find errors and bugs in your code if you're a software developer. They might occur because of incorrect input, from passing the wrong data types, or because of delays or response timeouts.  And even though errors and bugs are a part of life, they can stress]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okoye Victor Chukwuebuka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Shopping Cart with React and TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-shopping-cart-with-react-and-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-shopping-cart-with-react-and-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T17:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial we are going to build a real-life shopping cart 🛒 application.  We'll talk about the technology stack and the features it will have in a minute. I'll also walk you through the process step-by-step. But first, let me show you what it's going to look like.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mihail Gaberov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Penpot’s Flex Layout: Building CSS Layouts In A Design Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/penpot-flex-layout-building-css-layouts-design-tool/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/penpot-flex-layout-building-css-layouts-design-tool/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s article, let’s explore how we can use Flex Layout and see how it empowers designers with greater control over their work while saving everyone’s time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a ChatGPT Plugin – Case Study using PodcastAPI.com and Serverless Cloudflare Pages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-chatgpt-plugin-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-chatgpt-plugin-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T23:01:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT [https://chat.openai.com/] is a highly intelligent auto-completion tool. It takes instructions or questions in natural language and provides good enough text-based outputs.  But there’s a catch — ChatGPT’s knowledge only goes up until September 2021. So, as of writing this blog post (June 2023), the model itself is not aware of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wenbin Fang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make a Database Read-Only in MySQL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-a-database-read-only-in-mysql/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-a-database-read-only-in-mysql/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T22:49:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are learning MySQL, then you are likely enjoying executing different commands and checking the results afterward.  But you may be working on a project where you have modified your database to an acceptable state and you're worried about altering it by mistake. This could happen when you're]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intro to Generative AI – 10 Free Courses by Google]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/intro-to-generative-ai-10-free-courses-by-google/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/intro-to-generative-ai-10-free-courses-by-google/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T22:22:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you tired of all the AI talk yet? I am too, but I'm also intrigued by the technology behind it. If you'd like to dive into some of the details behind how AI actually works and take a break from the many creepy AI examples on the internet, check]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key Computer Science Concepts Every Software Engineer Should Know – and How to Learn Them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-every-software-engineer-should-know/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-every-software-engineer-should-know/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T22:06:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a software engineer, you may feel like you are in a bit of a rat race.  The rat race to learn the new technologies. A new frontend framework, a new database or even a new language which is a variation of another language. It's never ending and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tamerlan Gudabayev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Gnome Extensions For Developer Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-best-gnome-extensions-for-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-best-gnome-extensions-for-developers/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T22:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a beginner who's using a Gnome-based distro like Ubuntu, Fedora, Arch Linux, and so on, there are tons of extensions available from the Gnome community. Gnome is an open-source Linux-based distro desktop environment (operating system) maintained by a large number of developers. Choosing the right Gnome extension(s) can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create an AI Tweet Generator Using LangChain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-an-ai-tweet-generator-openai-langchain/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-an-ai-tweet-generator-openai-langchain/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T20:20:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've got a fun tutorial for you today. If you've read my previous article on building custom-knowledge chatbots using LangChain [/news/langchain-how-to-create-custom-knowledge-chatbots/], then you must be bursting with ideas of great projects you can create. Well, I want to encourage your creativity and give a concrete example of what you can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shane Duggan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Pandas & Python for Data Analysis [Full Course]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-pandas-for-data-science/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-pandas-for-data-science/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T12:50:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pandas is an open source data analysis and manipulation tool. It is important to learn if you are interested in data science. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Pandas through interactive projects. You will develop 7 projects ranging from]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Supabase, an Open-Source Firebase Alternative]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-supabase-open-source-firebase-alternative/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-supabase-open-source-firebase-alternative/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T12:20:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Supabase is an open-source Firebase alternative that is rapidly gaining popularity in the developer community. If you are looking to sharpen their backend skills, consider learning how to use Supabase. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org channel that is designed to help you master Supabase. This course was]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using AI To Detect Sentiment In Audio Files]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/ai-detect-sentiment-audio-files/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/ai-detect-sentiment-audio-files/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dive into an article where you will build an app that evaluates audio files for positive and negative sentiments. The idea is that you will create an interface for uploading an audio file, then transcribe the contents into text before analyzing the text and assigning it a positive or negative score for how the tone is perceived.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joas Pambou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Editing Comes To The Headless CMS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/visual-editing-headless-cms/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/visual-editing-headless-cms/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visual editing is beginning to make its way into headless architecture and the early results look promising. We’ll look at a few headless CMSs that currently support visual editing in this article.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Scott Gallant)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Headaches And How To Cure Them: i18n (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/gatsby-headaches-i18n-part-2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/gatsby-headaches-i18n-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part 2 of the series concentrates on implementing internationalization (i18n) on a Gatsby website, an essential feature on any multilingual website that can be quite a bit of trouble if incorrectly implemented, creating more problems than it solves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Was SmashingConf In San Franciso Like?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/smashingconf-sanfrancisco2023-recap/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/smashingconf-sanfrancisco2023-recap/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One way of getting a more behind-the-scenes experience of any Smashing event is to apply as a volunteer, and Ren did just that! The SmashingConf team organized a conference in good ol’ San Francisco this year, and here’s pretty much how it went down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ren Chen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Codux: The React Visual Editor That Improves Developer Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/codux-react-visual-editor-improves-developer-experience/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/codux-react-visual-editor-improves-developer-experience/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[Codux](https://codux.hopp.to/smashing) is a new visual IDE brought to you by the fine folks over at[ Wix](https://www.wix.com/). It’s got a lot of low-code features that level the playing field for app development but is really designed for React developers. How so, you ask? That’s what we’re going to explore in this article.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build Server-Side Rendered (SSR) Svelte Apps With SvelteKit]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/build-server-side-rendered-svelte-apps-sveltekit/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/build-server-side-rendered-svelte-apps-sveltekit/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SvelteKit is a framework for building apps using Svelte. In this article, Sriram shows you how to build a server-side rendered (SSR) SvelteKit application and deploy it to Netlify by following this step-by-step guide.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sriram Thiagarajan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 62 With Slava Shestopalov: What Is Design Management?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/smashing-podcast-episode-62/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/smashing-podcast-episode-62/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of The Smashing Podcast, we ask what is a design manager? What does it take and how does it relate to the role of Designer? Vitaly talks to Slava Shestopalov to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Headaches And How To Cure Them: i18n (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/gatsby-headaches-i18n-part-1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/gatsby-headaches-i18n-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this first part of a two-part hands-on guide, Juan Rodriguez explains how to use several i18n plugins for Gatsby and reviews some others.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design Under Constraints: Challenges, Opportunities, And Practical Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/design-constraints-challenges-opportunities-practical-strategies/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/design-constraints-challenges-opportunities-practical-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unleash the power of creative limitation! Learn how constraints aren’t barriers but instead stepping stones to innovative design. Find out how to challenge unproductive restrictions and leverage the rest to your advantage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing Sites And Apps With Blind Users: A Cheat Sheet]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/testing-sites-apps-blind-users-cheat-sheet/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/testing-sites-apps-blind-users-cheat-sheet/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While compliance with accessibility checklists is essential, it doesn’t necessarily mean a pleasant experience. That’s why live sessions can give you lots of priceless insights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Slava Shestopalov &amp; Eugene Shykiriavyi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Universal And Cognitive-Friendly UX Design Through Pivot Tables And Grids]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/universal-cognitive-friendly-ux-design-tables-grids/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/universal-cognitive-friendly-ux-design-tables-grids/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article covers the best tips and recommendations on the elements to pay attention to, the rules to follow, and life hacks to get around certain difficulties in table design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yuliia Nikitina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Primitive Objects In JavaScript: When To Use Them (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/primitive-objects-javascript-part-2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/primitive-objects-javascript-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the second part of the series, Kirill looks at the usefulness of primitive objects, exploring how reducing capabilities could be a benefit for your project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kirill Myshkin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Enable Collaboration In A Multiparty Setting]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/enable-collaboration-multiparty-setting/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/enable-collaboration-multiparty-setting/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Artificial Intelligence becomes more widespread, so too does the adoption of digital agents and voice interactions. Explore the power of mixed reality systems and multimodal communication to enhance collaboration between consultants and clients, transforming advisory services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Hannah Kühne &amp; Madlaina Kalunder)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iA Presenter: A Case Study On Product Pricing Considerations]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/ia-presenter-case-study-product-pricing-considerations/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/ia-presenter-case-study-product-pricing-considerations/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pricing a product or service is one of the more challenging aspects of product development. Pricing is an inexact science, and chances are you will not get it right the first time. But where do you even begin? Let’s explore the important considerations that go into product pricing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced Form Control Styling With Selectmenu And Anchoring API]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/advanced-form-control-styling-selectmenu-anchoring-api/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/advanced-form-control-styling-selectmenu-anchoring-api/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to the Open UI working community group, there’s a new element on the horizon, <selectmenu>, that will make styling this type of form control a whole lot better. You’re going to walk through an early implementation of this new experimental element by creating a pattern that you would never have thought possible with CSS alone — a radial selection menu.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Brecht De Ruyte)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create Your Own Path In June (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new batch of desktop wallpapers might be for you. Designed by artists and designers from across the globe, the wallpapers in this post come in versions with and without a calendar for June 2023. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>