<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-04-16T00:10:33.327Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-04-16T00:10:33.327Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conda Channel - What Is a Channel in Conda?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-channel-in-conda/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-channel-in-conda/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T16:36:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you install a package in Conda, it is downloaded and extracted from a remote directory using the directory's URL. The directory where these packages are stored is known as a channel. In this article, you'll learn what a channel is, how to use default channels, and how add new]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Pretty Print JSON in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-pretty-print-json-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-pretty-print-json-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T15:38:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JSON (JavaScript Object Notation) is a popular data interchange format that is widely used in web applications, APIs, and databases. It is a lightweight and human-readable format that is easy to parse and generate.  But when dealing with large and complex JSON data, it can be difficult to read]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does $ Mean in JavaScript? Dollar Sign Operator in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-the-dollar-sign-mean-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-the-dollar-sign-mean-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T15:10:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As you dive into JavaScript code, you may come across the use of a dollar sign ($) in various contexts. In this article, we will explore what the dollar sign means in JavaScript, commonly known as the "dollar sign operator," and how it is used in JavaScript programming. Understanding the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JSONObject.toString() – How to Convert JSON to a String in Java]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/jsonobject-tostring-how-to-convert-json-to-a-string-in-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/jsonobject-tostring-how-to-convert-json-to-a-string-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T15:05:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of web applications and services, JSON (JavaScript Object Notation) has become a widely used data format for data exchange between different systems.  In Java, it's common to work with JSON data, and an operation you'll frequently perform is converting a JSON object to a string representation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Refresh Page – How to Reload a Page in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-refresh-page-how-to-reload-a-page-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-refresh-page-how-to-reload-a-page-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T15:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is a versatile programming language that allows developers to create dynamic and interactive web applications. One common task in web development is to refresh or reload a web page, either to update its content or to trigger certain actions. In this article, we will explore different ways to refresh]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is An ACL? Access Control Lists Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-deep-dive-into-access-control-lists/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-deep-dive-into-access-control-lists/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T14:43:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In computing, access control is the concept of limiting or regulating a person or machine's access to certain information or resources.  One of the major mechanisms you use to do that is an access control list (ACL). An ACL is a set of rules for allowing or denying access]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chidiadi Anyanwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Initialize a Java List – List of String Initialization in Java]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-initialize-a-java-list/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-initialize-a-java-list/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T14:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Java is a popular programming language widely used for developing robust and scalable applications. One of the essential data structures in Java is a list, which allows developers to store and manipulate a collection of elements. Initializing a list in Java is a crucial step in the development process as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Blog with the Ghost API and Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-blog-website-with-ghost-api-and-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-blog-website-with-ghost-api-and-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T21:14:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ghost CMS is a popular content management system that many devs and companies use to host their blogs.  It has many features and an editor that's highly optimized for writing. You can even build different themes using handlebars.js [https://handlebarsjs.com/]. But if you don't know Handlebars, learning it can be]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The difference between Arrow functions and Normal functions in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-difference-between-arrow-functions-and-normal-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-difference-between-arrow-functions-and-normal-functions/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T21:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, there are two types of functions. You have normal functions and arrow functions. Let's explore the difference between them in this article. Arrow functions was introduced in ES6. And it introduced a simple and shorter way to create functions. Here's how to create a normal function, with arguments,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Live Football Scoreboard in React with Vite and Vitest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-project-with-vite-and-vitest/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-project-with-vite-and-vitest/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T20:41:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to yet another tutorial [https://www.mihailgaberov.com/] where you will learn how to build a ⚽ scoreboard app in React. This time we will use Vite as our next generation frontend tooling [https://vitejs.dev/] and Vitest [https://vitest.dev/] as a Vite-native unit testing framework.  You will also learn how to leverage React]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mihail Gaberov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passkeys: What the Heck and Why?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377305</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/passkeys-what-the-heck-and-why/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T17:41:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These things called passkeys sure are making the rounds these days. They were a main attraction at W3C TPAC 2022, gained support in Safari 16, are finding their way into macOS and iOS, and are slated to …
Passkeys: What the Heck and Why? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Neal Fennimore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Design An Effective User Onboarding Flow]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/design-effective-user-onboarding-flow/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/design-effective-user-onboarding-flow/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to maximize conversions or collect necessary user information for other purposes, a user onboarding flow is necessary. In this article, you will learn how, with the help of Feathery, to design an effective user onboarding flow for your app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Suzanne Scacca)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Protect Your App With A Threat Model Based On JSONDiff]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/protect-app-threat-model-jsondiff/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/protect-app-threat-model-jsondiff/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a developer who wants to concentrate on delivering a killer application rather than worrying about countless security issues, threat model documents can help you do that. With small architectural changes, we can make these threats manageable and prevent them in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zack Grossbart &amp; Terry Yao)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Algorithms: Skills Of Designers That AI Can’t Replicate]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/skills-designers-ai-cant-replicate/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/skills-designers-ai-cant-replicate/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article highlights non-technical skills like curiosity, observation, empathy, advocacy, visual communication, and collaboration that designers routinely use in their process to make a difference through design. AI can be used to augment designers’ workflow instead of replacing people.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lyndon Cerejo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swing Into April (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With April just around the corner, we have a new collection of desktop and mobile wallpapers waiting for you to celebrate the beginning of the new month. Designed by creatives from all across the globe, the wallpapers come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Comprehensive Checklist For Running Design Workshops]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/organizing-design-workshops-checklist/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/organizing-design-workshops-checklist/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Workshops are all about people: they involve people, are conducted by people, and aim to close the gaps in people’s communication. Slava Shestopalov shares a checklist with everything you need to keep in mind when running a workshop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Slava Shestopalov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fine-Grained Access Handling And Data Management With Row-Level Security]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/access-handling-data-management-row-level-security/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/access-handling-data-management-row-level-security/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dealing with sensitive data is an important topic for any app. In this article, you will find out how to handle sensitive or confidential information in your apps and what Row-Level Security means.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Handoff Is No Handoff]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/best-handoff-is-no-handoff/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/best-handoff-is-no-handoff/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design handoffs are inefficient and painful. They cause frustration, friction and a lot of back and forth. Can we avoid them altogether? Of course we can! Let’s see how to do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overcoming The Challenges Of Content Creation For Informational Websites]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/overcoming-challenges-content-creation-informational-websites/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/overcoming-challenges-content-creation-informational-websites/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Content matters! Unfortunately, when it comes to informational websites, content quality is often poor. There is no magic answer to fix that. However, there are practical techniques you can use to improve the copy on your websites and ensure your users find the content they are looking for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Cross-Browser DevTools Features You Might Not Know]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377264</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/some-cross-browser-devtools-features-you-might-not-know/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T20:22:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I spend a lot of time in DevTools, and I’m sure you do too. Sometimes I even bounce between them, especially when I’m debugging cross-browser issues. DevTools is a lot like browsers themselves — not all of the features in …
Some Cross-Browser DevTools Features You Might Not Know originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pankaj Parashar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 58 With Debbie Levitt: What Is CX Design?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/smashing-podcast-episode-58/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/smashing-podcast-episode-58/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we ask what is Customer Experience design, and how does it differ from User Experience design? Vitaly Friedman talks to expert Debbie Levitt to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Fonts For Interface Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/free-fonts-interface-designers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/free-fonts-interface-designers/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just a few beautiful, well-crafted fonts for headings and body text that you probably haven’t spotted before. Free for personal and commercial use. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>