<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-08-23T00:09:15.579Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-08-23T00:09:15.579Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Bundle a Simple React Application Using esbuild]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/bundle-a-basic-react-application-using-esbuild/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/bundle-a-basic-react-application-using-esbuild/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T20:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bundling is an important phase in the web development process, particularly when dealing with JavaScript frameworks like React. It entails combining all the various JavaScript files and dependencies into a single file for faster browser loading and execution.  esbuild is a lightweight and efficient bundler for React apps. Here's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JS Date Validations – How To Validate a Date in JavaScript (With Examples)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-validate-a-date-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-validate-a-date-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T19:08:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are times when you need to validate a date input in your JavaScript applications. This article will show you how to perform the following date validations:  1. Check if a string is a valid date  2. Validate a string in the DD/MM/YYYY format  3. Check if]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy an Application to a Kubernetes Cluster]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploy-docker-image-to-kubernetes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploy-docker-image-to-kubernetes/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T16:34:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's ever-changing technology landscape, companies are looking for reliable and scalable ways to run and manage software. And containers have transformed the way we deliver software. Container orchestration platforms have made it possible to deploy and manage containerised applications. Kubernetes is one such platform that has been a game-changer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Protect Your Website Against SEO Poisoning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ensuring-website-security-collaborative-measures-for-cybersecurity-and-seo-experts-to-prevent-seo-poisoning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ensuring-website-security-collaborative-measures-for-cybersecurity-and-seo-experts-to-prevent-seo-poisoning/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T16:20:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's digital landscape, search engine optimization (SEO) is important for increasing online visibility and driving organic traffic to websites.  But cybersecurity threats, including SEO poisoning, pose a great risks to both website owners and SEO efforts.  To fight these risks and safeguard websites, cybersecurity experts and SEO]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isah Jacob</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Calculator App with Svelte]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-calculator-app-with-svelte/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-calculator-app-with-svelte/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T15:48:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Svelte is an open-source front-end JavaScript framework used for building web applications, designed to make developing interactive user interfaces more efficient and performant.  Compared to other front-end frameworks like React, Vue, or Angular, it focuses on a different approach by compiling components. In most traditional frameworks, you build components]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adejumo Ridwan Suleiman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stateful vs Stateless Architecture – Explained for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/stateful-vs-stateless-architectures-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/stateful-vs-stateless-architectures-explained/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T21:08:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In programming, "state" refers to the condition of a system, component, or application at a particular point in time.  As a simple example, if you are shopping on amazon.com, whether you are currently logged into the site or if you have anything stored in your cart are some examples]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adetunji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing ScrapePark.org – Practice Web Scraping Without Hurting Anyone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/practice-web-scraping-safely/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/practice-web-scraping-safely/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T19:50:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I grew up in the 1990s, we skateboarded everywhere. If a parking lot had a ledge or a handrail, you'd better believe we waxed it and grinded our boards across it. Fast forward to the 2020s – many cities have built public skate parks. These are safe, legal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Development with Large Language Models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/development-with-large-language-models/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/development-with-large-language-models/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T16:13:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) open up a wide range of capabilities for developers. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will equip you with the skills to use LLMs effectively for your projects. Developed by Akshath from Luup.ai, this course will help you unlock the potential]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Google Drive Clone with Laravel, PHP, and Vue.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-google-drive-clone-with-laravel-php-vuejs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-google-drive-clone-with-laravel-php-vuejs/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T14:48:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building file manager application is a great way to learn many important programming concepts. We just posted a 14-hour course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build and deploy a feature-rich file manager application using Laravel (the PHP framework), Inertia, and Vue.js. This comprehensive course]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the JavaScript at() Array Method]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-at-method/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-at-method/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T14:41:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of JavaScript's most exciting new features is the at() method. The at()  method is a new addition to the Array prototype in JavaScript. You can use this method to access elements in an array using a numeric index. The at() method takes an integer value and returns the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Natalie Pina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better Context Menus With Safe Triangles]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/better-context-menus-safe-triangles/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/better-context-menus-safe-triangles/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how to improve the user experience of nested menus and tackle a minor yet common issue with them when the user’s pointer leaves the menu item for a moment, and the nested menu goes away, requiring the user to re-hover and try again. A well-known concept called the “safe triangle” solves this problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Costa Alexoglou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern Methods For Improving Drupal’s Largest Contentful Paint Core Web Vital]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/methods-improving-drupal-largest-contentful-paint-core-web-vital/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/methods-improving-drupal-largest-contentful-paint-core-web-vital/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The background image used in the hero component, which is slow to load, is a very common problem with any component that uses a large image file as a background image. In this article, Mike Herchel walks you through how to tackle this common performance issue using modern techniques.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mike Herchel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Knip: An Automated Tool For Finding Unused Files, Exports, And Dependencies]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/knip-automated-tool-find-unused-files-exports-dependencies/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/knip-automated-tool-find-unused-files-exports-dependencies/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of the projects have at least a few unused files, exports, and dependencies lying around, often because it’s difficult knowing when one thing relies on another and scary removing something you’re not sure is in use. Lars Kappert shares a tool he’s been working on that offers a solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lars Kappert)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Accessible Text Over Images: Best Practices, Techniques And Resources (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/designing-accessible-text-over-images-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/designing-accessible-text-over-images-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In part 2 of the series, Hannah Milan reviews various accessible text over images techniques for designing your content, including framing the image, soft-colored gradients technique, text styles and text position, solid color shapes, and use of colored backgrounds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Hannah Milan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running A Page Speed Test: Monitoring vs. Measuring]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/running-page-speed-test-monitoring-versus-measuring/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/running-page-speed-test-monitoring-versus-measuring/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What does your performance “stack” look like? There are all kinds of tools available for measuring page speed, but what data and assumptions do they use to measure performance? And speaking of *measuring* performance, there’s quite a difference between that and *monitoring* performance. Let’s dig in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Friction As A Feature In Machine Learning Algorithms]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/friction-feature-machine-learning-algorithms/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/friction-feature-machine-learning-algorithms/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Friction often has a negative connotation in user experience design, but it actually has many benefits. Its best-known use case is mitigating unintended consequences in high-risk scenarios, yet it has a new place in the age of artificial intelligence. Adding strategic friction to interfaces can lead to profound efficiency gains in machine learning algorithms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Maximillian Piras)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Accessible Text Over Images: Best Practices, Techniques, And Resources (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/designing-accessible-text-over-images-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/designing-accessible-text-over-images-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this two-part series of articles, Hannah Milan covers the best practices when using various accessible text over images techniques for designing your web and mobile app content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Hannah Milan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Optimized Performance To Serve A Global Audience]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/optimize-performance-serve-global-audience/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/optimize-performance-serve-global-audience/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liran Cohen and the team at Bookaway, a travel booking service, dramatically improved their site’s performance by auditing Core Web Vitals. In this article, Liran shares his team’s process for auditing and monitoring Web Vitals and the effort it took to dramatically improve Bookaway’s performance — and the benefits that came with it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Liran Cohen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 64 With Alvin Bryan: What Is A Headless CMS?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/smashing-podcast-episode-64/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/smashing-podcast-episode-64/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re talking about headless content management systems. What are they, and how do they differ from more traditional systems? Drew McLellan talks to Alvin Bryan to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS And Accessibility: Inclusion Through User Choice]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/css-accessibility-inclusion-user-choice/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/08/css-accessibility-inclusion-user-choice/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Carie Fisher outlines which CSS media features are available for detecting user preferences and how they are used to design and build more inclusive user experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carie Fisher)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Living In The Moment (August 2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-august-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T09:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New month, new wallpapers! In this post, you’ll find unique and inspiring wallpapers for August 2023. Created with love by the community for the community, they come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Define An Array Of Colors With CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/define-array-colors-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/define-array-colors-css/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join Temani Afif on experiment with modern CSS features to create an array of colors. The goal is to define a comma-separated list of colors and iterate through them using an index.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use Artificial Intelligence And Machine Learning To Summarize Chat Conversations]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/artificial-intelligence-machine-learning-summarize-chat-conversations/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/artificial-intelligence-machine-learning-summarize-chat-conversations/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll explore how to build a chat summarizer using the Cohere API and deploy it as a web application using Gradio.[ Cohere](https://cohere.com/) is an AI platform that provides state-of-the-art natural language processing models for a variety of tasks, including summarization. We’ll cover the steps involved in training the summarizer using sample chat conversations, interacting with the Cohere API to generate summaries, and creating a user-friendly interface using [Gradio](https://www.gradio.app/).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joas Pambou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern Technology And The Future Of Language Translation]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/modern-technology-future-language-translation/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/07/modern-technology-future-language-translation/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The field of language translation has never been more exciting. Explore the evolution of language translation platforms, how we got to where we are today, and what advancements we can look forward to in the coming years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adriano Raiano)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>