<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-06-14T00:09:57.532Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-06-14T00:09:57.532Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Page Elements – Explained for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-page-elements/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-page-elements/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T21:01:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML, which stands for Hypertext Markup Language, is the standard markup language used for creating web pages and structuring their content on the World Wide Web.  HTML serves as the backbone of web development and acts as a fundamental building block for creating web-based documents. Let's take a quick]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Promises Work in JavaScript – A Comprehensive Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/guide-to-javascript-promises/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/guide-to-javascript-promises/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T16:35:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript has the ability to carry out asynchronous (or async) instructions. These instructions run in the background until they have finished processing.  Asynchronous instructions do not stop the JavaScript engine from actively accepting and processing more instructions. This is why JavaScript is non-blocking in nature. There are a few]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amazing Enyichi Agu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Power Platform Fundamentals Certification (PL-900) – Pass the Exam With This Free 4-Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/microsoft-power-platform-fundamentals-certification-pl-900/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/microsoft-power-platform-fundamentals-certification-pl-900/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T14:28:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Certifications like the Microsoft Power Platform Fundamentals can help you advance in your career. You can learn everything you need to know to earn the Microsoft Power Platform Fundamentals Certification by completing this free 4-hour course that we just posted on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Andrew Brown created this course.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 62 With Slava Shestopalov: What Is Design Management?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/smashing-podcast-episode-62/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/smashing-podcast-episode-62/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of The Smashing Podcast, we ask what is a design manager? What does it take and how does it relate to the role of Designer? Vitaly talks to Slava Shestopalov to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI in Google Sheets – How to Use GPT Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-in-google-sheets/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-in-google-sheets/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T22:10:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seems to be the year of AI. And my favorite tool, Google Sheets, is not to be left out of the fun. 🎉 Coefficient [https://coefficient.io/gpt-google-sheets] produced a Google sheets extension with the ability to use OpenAI's GPT models from within a spreadsheet. It’s called GPT Copilot and it’s available]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use MySQL Stored Procedures to Simplify Database Operations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-simplify-database-operations-using-mysql-stored-procedures/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-simplify-database-operations-using-mysql-stored-procedures/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T22:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the realm of database management, MySQL has emerged as one of the most popular and reliable choices.  MySQL not only offers robust data storage capabilities but also provides a powerful feature called "procedures" that allows developers to streamline complex database operations.  In this tutorial, we will delve]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Upgrade Your React Skills with Three Helpful Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/upgrade-your-react-skills/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/upgrade-your-react-skills/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T21:12:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since its announcement in 2013, React.js continues to be one of the most widely used JavaScript tools, thanks to its unmatched versatility and efficiency.  Backed by its component-based architecture and virtual DOM implementation, React.js excels in building modern and dynamic web applications. It enables developers to create reusable UI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moyosore J Olaojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Streamline Your File Upload Process in Express.js with Multer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/simplify-your-file-upload-process-in-express-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/simplify-your-file-upload-process-in-express-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T21:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[File uploading is a common requirement in web development projects. But handling file uploads in Node.js can be complex and time-consuming. That's where Multer comes in.  Multer is a powerful middleware for Node.js that simplifies the file upload process by handling multipart/form-data requests. In this tutorial, you will learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelvin Moses</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Improve Your Technical Writing Skills by Contributing to Open Source Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-tech-writing-skills-by-contributing-to-open-source/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-tech-writing-skills-by-contributing-to-open-source/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T18:15:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you been writing your tech blog posts on Hashnode [https://hashnode.com/about] or Dev.to [http://dev.to/], but you're itching to try something new? If so, there is something that can quench your thirst: contributing to open source.  I know, I know, you’ve probably heard “Contribute to open source!” countless times in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CHRISTINE T. BELZIE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Headaches And How To Cure Them: i18n (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/gatsby-headaches-i18n-part-1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/gatsby-headaches-i18n-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this first part of a two-part hands-on guide, Juan Rodriguez explains how to use several i18n plugins for Gatsby and reviews some others.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Change Commit Message – How to Edit Commit Messages with Git Amend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-edit-git-commit-messages-with-git-amend/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-edit-git-commit-messages-with-git-amend/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T17:58:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Commit messages play a crucial role in Git version control. They provide a historical record of changes made to a repository.  Clear and descriptive commit messages help you collaborate better with team members, more easily maintain your code, and understand how the project works.  But there are times]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How CSS Spacing Works – A Guide for Web Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-spacing-guide-for-web-devs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-spacing-guide-for-web-devs/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T16:26:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we're going to talk about spacing in CSS spacing – sounds so basic, right? Well, it's not as basic as you might think.  Take, for instance, when you visit your favorite e-commerce site to scout for products. The first thing that welcomes you to the platform]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clinton Joy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design Under Constraints: Challenges, Opportunities, And Practical Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/design-constraints-challenges-opportunities-practical-strategies/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/design-constraints-challenges-opportunities-practical-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unleash the power of creative limitation! Learn how constraints aren’t barriers but instead stepping stones to innovative design. Find out how to challenge unproductive restrictions and leverage the rest to your advantage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing Sites And Apps With Blind Users: A Cheat Sheet]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/testing-sites-apps-blind-users-cheat-sheet/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/testing-sites-apps-blind-users-cheat-sheet/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While compliance with accessibility checklists is essential, it doesn’t necessarily mean a pleasant experience. That’s why live sessions can give you lots of priceless insights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Slava Shestopalov &amp; Eugene Shykiriavyi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Universal And Cognitive-Friendly UX Design Through Pivot Tables And Grids]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/universal-cognitive-friendly-ux-design-tables-grids/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/universal-cognitive-friendly-ux-design-tables-grids/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article covers the best tips and recommendations on the elements to pay attention to, the rules to follow, and life hacks to get around certain difficulties in table design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yuliia Nikitina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Primitive Objects In JavaScript: When To Use Them (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/primitive-objects-javascript-part-2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/primitive-objects-javascript-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the second part of the series, Kirill looks at the usefulness of primitive objects, exploring how reducing capabilities could be a benefit for your project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kirill Myshkin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Enable Collaboration In A Multiparty Setting]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/enable-collaboration-multiparty-setting/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/enable-collaboration-multiparty-setting/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Artificial Intelligence becomes more widespread, so too does the adoption of digital agents and voice interactions. Explore the power of mixed reality systems and multimodal communication to enhance collaboration between consultants and clients, transforming advisory services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Hannah Kühne &amp; Madlaina Kalunder)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iA Presenter: A Case Study On Product Pricing Considerations]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/ia-presenter-case-study-product-pricing-considerations/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/ia-presenter-case-study-product-pricing-considerations/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pricing a product or service is one of the more challenging aspects of product development. Pricing is an inexact science, and chances are you will not get it right the first time. But where do you even begin? Let’s explore the important considerations that go into product pricing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced Form Control Styling With Selectmenu And Anchoring API]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/advanced-form-control-styling-selectmenu-anchoring-api/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/06/advanced-form-control-styling-selectmenu-anchoring-api/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to the Open UI working community group, there’s a new element on the horizon, <selectmenu>, that will make styling this type of form control a whole lot better. You’re going to walk through an early implementation of this new experimental element by creating a pattern that you would never have thought possible with CSS alone — a radial selection menu.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Brecht De Ruyte)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create Your Own Path In June (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new batch of desktop wallpapers might be for you. Designed by artists and designers from across the globe, the wallpapers in this post come in versions with and without a calendar for June 2023. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing A Better Design Handoff File In Figma]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/designing-better-design-handoff-file-figma/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/designing-better-design-handoff-file-figma/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article provides practical tips for improving the handoff process between design and development in product development. The guidance covers effective communication, documentation, design details, version control, and plugin usage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ben Shih)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Success At Scale, A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/success-at-scale-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/success-at-scale-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet “Success At Scale”, our upcoming book with best-practice case studies from industry experts. Print and eBook shipping in fall 2023. Pre-order the book.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Impact Of Agile Methodologies On Code Quality]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/impact-agile-methodologies-code-quality/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/impact-agile-methodologies-code-quality/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-25T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Say goodbye to traditional workflows and embrace Agile to unlock the power of high-quality code. Discover how Agile methodologies promote simplicity, modularization, readability, and continuous improvement, resulting in faster turnaround times, more responsive development processes, and ultimately, the creation of high-quality software that meets customer needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sarah Oke Okolo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 61 With Rachel Andrew: What Is Web Platform Baseline?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/smashing-podcast-episode-61/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/smashing-podcast-episode-61/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we’re talking about Web Platform Baseline. What is it, and how can it help determine your browser support policy? Drew McLellan talks to expert Rachel Andrew to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practical Design Tips And Guidelines For Beginner Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/practical-design-tips-guidelines-beginner-designers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/practical-design-tips-guidelines-beginner-designers/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-22T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s easy for beginner designers to get overwhelmed and lose confidence when creating presentations, landing pages, app and web design mockups, and even cards. Laurent Baumann shares a few simple guidelines and practical tips to help you in such situations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Laurent Baumann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Deal With Big Tooling Upgrades In Large Organizations]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/big-tooling-upgrades-large-organizations/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/big-tooling-upgrades-large-organizations/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The process of upgrading large third-party packages in equally large organizations is rarely, if ever, as easy as running an npm update and calling it a day in this context. Joran Quinten shares valuable lessons from his team’s experiences in upgrading third-party code that affects codebases across the entire organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joran Quinten)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design Patterns Are A Better Way To Collaborate On Your Design System]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/design-patterns-collaborate-design-system/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/design-patterns-collaborate-design-system/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every company and team has to have deep collaboration between engineering and design to get the value out of a design system (and not go nuts). Building design patterns first unblock people to work in parallel, keeps people synced up, and results in reusable modules that speed up your next project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ben Clemens)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solving Media Object Float Issues With CSS Block Formatting Contexts]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/media-object-float-issues-css-block-formatting-contexts/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/05/media-object-float-issues-css-block-formatting-contexts/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article covers common problems using CSS floats and how to solve them using a block formatting context (BFC). Whether you are a beginner or an experienced web developer, you will learn valuable insights and practical solutions for dealing with CSS float issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Gabriel Shoyombo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>