<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-03-12T00:11:00.128Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-03-12T00:11:00.128Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Remove Duplicate Data 
in SQL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-duplicate-data-in-sql/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-duplicate-data-in-sql/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T21:22:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Duplicates can be a big problem in SQL databases as they can slow down query performance and waste valuable storage space.  Fortunately, there are several ways to remove duplicate data in SQL.  In this article, we will explore some of the most effective methods for removing duplicate data]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluseye Jeremiah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript One-Liners to Use in Every Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-one-liners-to-use-in-every-project/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-one-liners-to-use-in-every-project/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T21:18:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is a powerful language that can do a lot with very little code. In some cases, the amount of code you need to write doesn't exceed more than a single line, which is why they are known as one-liners. Let's go through 10 essential one liners worth using in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Iterate Over Dictionary – How to Loop Through a Dict]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-iterate-over-dictionary-how-to-loop-through-a-dict/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-iterate-over-dictionary-how-to-loop-through-a-dict/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T21:10:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will talk about dictionaries, and also learn how to loop through a dictionary in python. Python Dictionaries In Python, a dictionary is a built-in data structure used to store and organize data in key-value pairs.  A dictionary has two parts for each entry: a key]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript String Tutorial – String Methods in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-string-tutorial-string-methods-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-string-tutorial-string-methods-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T19:14:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A string is a sequence of characters intended to represent text. Strings can contain any kind of character, like letters, numbers, or special characters.  They are a very useful data type and you will be probably working with them frequently. So it's important to know how to manipulate them]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dario Di Cillo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Simpler JavaScript Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/simplify-javascript-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/simplify-javascript-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T18:57:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As developers, writing clean and maintainable code is the goal. But sometimes, this is hard to achieve when we have a large and bulky codebase that can become complex and difficult to manage. One way to avoid this is to simplify your code. This can help improve its readability, efficiency,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oyedele Temitope</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Forms in React]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-forms-in-react/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-forms-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T17:43:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forms play an essential role in modern web applications. They enable users to share information, complete tasks and provide feedback.  Without forms, many of the tasks that we take for granted on the web, such as logging in, signing up, or making purchases, would not be possible. As such,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dickson Boateng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Mistakes I Made When Starting My First React Project]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377098</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/5-mistakes-starting-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T16:41:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You know what it’s like to pick up a new language or framework. Sometimes there’s great documentation to help you find your way through it. But even the best documentation doesn’t cover absolutely everything. And when you work with something …
5 Mistakes I Made When Starting My First React Project originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Oliver Bray</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Pragmatist’s Guide To Lean User Research]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/pragmatists-guide-lean-user-research/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/pragmatists-guide-lean-user-research/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-10T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Instead of telling you once again what the best practice is and adding to your imposter syndrome, let’s concentrate on some practical approaches to user research that we might be able to fit into our existing projects without being left disillusioned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make a Clickable SVG Map With HTML and CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-clickable-svg-map-html-css/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-clickable-svg-map-html-css/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T19:43:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tour Afrique]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rufai Mustapha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Perform Machine Learning Tasks with Python and SQL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/machine-learning-with-python-and-sql/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/machine-learning-with-python-and-sql/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T17:57:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Machine learning has become a popular field in recent years, with various applications in data analysis, computer vision, natural language processing, and more.  Python is one of the most widely used programming languages for machine learning, thanks to its rich ecosystem of libraries, frameworks, and tools.  But to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluseye Jeremiah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting CORS – How to Pentest Cross-Origin Resource Sharing Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/exploiting-cors-guide-to-pentesting/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/exploiting-cors-guide-to-pentesting/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T16:25:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All web browsers implement a security model known as the Same-Origin Policy (SOP). It restricts domains from accessing and retrieving data from other domains’ resources.  The SOP policy helps protect users from malicious scripts that could access their sensitive data or perform unauthorized actions on their behalf. For example,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nairuz Abulhul</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Web Development from Harvard University (CS50 Web)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-web-development-from-harvard-university-cs50/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-web-development-from-harvard-university-cs50/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T12:37:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking to expand your knowledge and skills in web programming? Look no further than CS50's Web Programming with Python and JavaScript course from Harvard University. This full course is designed to provide a comprehensive understanding of web programming, from the basics of HTML and CSS to more advanced]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Complex Forms In Vue]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/building-complex-forms-vue/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/building-complex-forms-vue/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that creating a complex form can be progressively enhanced using some Vue features like the v-for and the v-model? In this article, Olufunke shares some basic Vue core features that are super useful when building out the complex form in your day-to-day Vue usage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Olufunke Moronfolu)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a Clock with the New CSS sin() and cos() Trigonometry Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377074</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-a-clock-with-the-new-css-sin-and-cos-trigonometry-functions/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-08T14:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS trigonometry functions are here! Well, they are if you’re using the latest versions of Firefox and Safari, that is. Having this sort of mathematical power in CSS opens up a whole bunch of possibilities. In this tutorial, I thought …
Creating a Clock with the New CSS sin() and cos() Trigonometry Functions originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mads Stoumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create Dynamic Donut Charts With TailwindCSS And React]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/dynamic-donut-charts-tailwind-css-react/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/dynamic-donut-charts-tailwind-css-react/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Paul Scanlon shares a super lightweight approach to creating a Donut chart using conic-gradient(). There are no additional libraries to install or maintain, and there’s no heavy JavaScript that needs to be downloaded by the browser in order for them to work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why You Should Consider Graphs For Your Next GraphQL Project]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/consider-graphs-graphql-project/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/consider-graphs-graphql-project/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Adam Cowley examines the Graph behind GraphQL and demonstrates why Neo4j could be the best fit for your next project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adam Cowley)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inspiring Web Design And UX Showcases]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/inspiring-web-design-ux-showcases/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/inspiring-web-design-ux-showcases/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you sometimes feel that all websites look the same? In this post, we compiled web design showcases that prove differently. They highlight some of the finest web designs, well-crafted experiences, and delightful interactions from across the web. Inspiration is guaranteed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Fonts in WordPress Block Themes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377123</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/managing-fonts-in-wordpress-block-themes/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-06T15:26:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fonts are a defining characteristic of the design of any site. That includes WordPress themes, where it’s common for theme developers to integrate a service like Google Fonts into the WordPress Customizer settings for a “classic” PHP-based theme. That hasn’t …
Managing Fonts in WordPress Block Themes originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ganesh Dahal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How AI Technology Will Transform Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/ai-technology-transform-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/ai-technology-transform-design/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Nick and Gleb cover the current state of design, answer common questions designers have about AI tools, and share practical tips on how designers can make the most of using AI tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nick Babich &amp; Gleb Kuznetsov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything You Need to Know About the Gap After the List Marker]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376748</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/everything-you-need-to-know-about-the-gap-after-the-list-marker/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-02T18:20:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was reading “Creative List Styling” on Google’s web.dev blog and noticed something odd in one of the code examples in the ::marker section of the article. The built-in list markers are bullets, ordinal numbers, and letters. The ::marker pseudo-element …
Everything You Need to Know About the Gap After the List Marker originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Šime Vidas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moving From Vue 1 To Vue 2 To Vue 3: A Case Study Of Migrating A Headless CMS System]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/vue-case-study-migrating-headless-cms-system/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/vue-case-study-migrating-headless-cms-system/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-02T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Elisabeth Wieser-Linhart explores its potential benefits and drawbacks and shares what considerations and steps were involved in the process of migrating the front-end interface of Storyblok’s headless content management system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lisi Linhart)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daydreaming In March (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-march-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-march-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-28T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s get ready for March with some fresh wallpapers! Designed with love by the community for the community, the wallpaper designs in this collection are available in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Penpot, An Open-Source Design Platform Made For Designers And Developers Alike]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/meet-penpot-open-source-design-platform-designers-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/meet-penpot-open-source-design-platform-designers-developers/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-28T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-evolving design tools landscape, it can be difficult to keep up with the latest and greatest. In this article, we’ll take a closer look at Penpot, the first design and prototyping tool that’s fully open-source and based on open web standards, making it an ideal choice for both designers and developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Accessible Form Validation]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/guide-accessible-form-validation/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/guide-accessible-form-validation/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Each time we build a field validation from scratch, accessibility doesn’t come out of the box. In this guide, Sandrina breaks down what we need to take into consideration, so that nobody gets stuck on an inaccessible invalid field.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sandrina Pereira)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chocolate, Waffles And Fries: Meet SmashingConf Antwerp 2023 🇧🇪]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/meet-smashingconf-antwerp/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/meet-smashingconf-antwerp/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-22T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brand new conference on design & UX, for designers and UI engineers who love the web. On design systems, usability, product design and complex UIs. That’s SmashingConf Antwerp, taking place in magical Bourla on October 9–11, 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Future-Proof High-Performance Websites With Astro Islands And Headless CMS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/building-future-proof-high-performance-websites-astro-islands-headless-cms-storyblok/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/building-future-proof-high-performance-websites-astro-islands-headless-cms-storyblok/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-22T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s see how to achieve phenomenal web performance and great developer experience with Astro and a headless CMS, resulting in the best possible experience for users, developers and content creators alike.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Manuel Schröder)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Internationalization (i18n) Right With Remix And Headless CMS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/internationalization-i18n-right-remix-headless-cms-storyblok/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/internationalization-i18n-right-remix-headless-cms-storyblok/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-21T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article will show you the impact of internationalization, its fundamental logic, how to approach it with Remix, and optionally, how to manage it more conveniently using a headless CMS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani &amp; Arisa Fukuzaki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 57 With Marcin Wichary: What’s The Key To A Great Keyboard?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/smashing-podcast-episode-57/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/smashing-podcast-episode-57/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we ask what’s the key to a great keyboard? Is this essential part of our daily toolkit easily overlooked? Vitaly Friedman talks to expert Marcin Wichary to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keys To An Accessibility Mindset]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/keys-accessibility-mindset/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/keys-accessibility-mindset/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-20T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An accessible product can be daunting to build as there’s so much nuance and technical depth to consider. In this article, Daniel Yuschick demonstrates three keys for approaching and developing accessible content without leaving you lost in the weeds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Daniel Yuschick)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Step-By-Step Guide To Building Accessible Carousels]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/guide-building-accessible-carousels/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/guide-building-accessible-carousels/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-17T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most carousels come along with usability and accessibility issues. To avoid these issues, this article addresses step-by-step design considerations as well as semantic requirements for carousels to be accessible. It is intended to create an in-depth understanding of the implementation and its impact on users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sonja Weckenmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Putting Gears In Motion: Animating Cars With HTML And SVG]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/putting-gears-motion-animating-cars-with-html-svg/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/putting-gears-motion-animating-cars-with-html-svg/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SVG `` provides a way to define how an element moves along a motion path. In this article, Paul Scanlon shares an idea of how to use it by animating race cars in an infinite loop as easy as one-two-three!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five Steps To Design Your Product With Powerful Storytelling]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/sell-product-powerful-storytelling/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/02/sell-product-powerful-storytelling/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-15T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to apply powerful storytelling to design a compelling and memorable digital experience on a landing page. A case study of the [Smart Interface Design Patterns landing page](https://smart-interface-design-patterns.com/).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Chiara Aliotta)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Approach to Lazy Loading Custom Elements]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376991</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/an-approach-to-lazy-loading-custom-elements/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-13T15:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re fans of Custom Elements around here. Their design makes them particularly amenable to lazy loading, which can be a boon for performance.
Inspired by a colleague’s experiments, I recently set about writing a simple auto-loader: Whenever a custom …
An Approach to Lazy Loading Custom Elements originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frederik Dohr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Different Ways to Get CSS Gradient Shadows]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376764</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/different-ways-to-get-css-gradient-shadows/"/>
        <updated>2023-02-10T15:13:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s a question I hear asked quite often: Is it possible to create shadows from gradients instead of solid colors? There is no specific CSS property that does this (believe me, I’ve looked) and any blog post you find about …
Different Ways to Get CSS Gradient Shadows originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>