<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-12-04T00:51:44.395Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-12-04T00:51:44.395Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add a Table of Contents to Your Article on Ghost]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-a-table-of-contents-to-your-article-on-ghost/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-a-table-of-contents-to-your-article-on-ghost/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T19:47:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A table of contents (or TOC) is a list of chapters or section titles in an article. You'll usually find it at the beginning of an article, right after the introduction. When you write a long blog post or an article with independent sections, consider adding a table of contents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ayu Adiati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SVG Tutorial – How to Code Images with 7 Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/svg-tutorial-learn-to-code-images/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/svg-tutorial-learn-to-code-images/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T19:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever needed an icon for your website, but you couldn't quite find the right one? Or perhaps you wanted to have a simple diagram, but didn't want to learn a whole new library just for that? Well, good news – you can do all that and more without]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hunor Márton Borbély</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recovering Deleted Files From Your Git Working Tree]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/recovering-deleted-files-git-working-tree/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/recovering-deleted-files-git-working-tree/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is designed to assure us that we can track a project’s files at different points in time. But it doesn’t assure us that those files are always safe along the way. For those of you who have dealt with the sinking feeling that you’ve irrevocably deleted and lost files, Sanmi has a couple of approaches that, in the right situations, may help bring them back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Oluwasanmi Akande)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use JavaScript Arrow Functions – Explained in Detail]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-arrow-functions-in-depth/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-arrow-functions-in-depth/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T19:26:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone! In this article, I’m going to explain one of the most useful features in JavaScript: the arrow function. I’ll compare the arrow function with the regular function syntax, I'll show you how to convert a regular function into an arrow function easily, and I'll discuss why the arrow]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Sebhastian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create HTML Accordion Elements With and Without JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-html-accordions-with-and-without-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-html-accordions-with-and-without-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T19:10:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accordion elements are very handy for displaying topic titles and expandable details below them when you click the title. In this article, I'll walk you through creating an FAQ section with some expandable accordion elements. I'll show you how to do this without any JavaScript, and then we'll add a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Clang AST-Based C++ Static Analysis Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/clang-ast-based-static-analysis-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/clang-ast-based-static-analysis-tools/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T19:01:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Clang is a set of tools and projects that provides infrastructure for languages in the C family like C, C++, OpenCL, and CUDA. It is a part of the LLVM [https://www.llvm.org/] project. This article will show you how to use Clang's front end libraries to build a simple static analysis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jayant Chowdhary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code and Deploy an Instagram Clone with React and Firebase]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-and-deploy-an-instagram-clone-with-react-and-firebase/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-and-deploy-an-instagram-clone-with-react-and-firebase/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T16:25:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating an Instagram clone is a fun project that can help you master important front end development skills. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that teaches you how to create an Instagram clone using React and Firebase. Burak Orkmez developed this course. This course is perfect]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[API Documentation Best Practices Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/api-documentation-best-practices-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/api-documentation-best-practices-course/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T16:17:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since APIs are the backbone of software development, effective API documentation is critical.  We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to write good documentation for APIs. You will learn how to craft, automate, and publish API documentation that is not only]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cold Days, Shining Lights (December 2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-december-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-december-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Could there be a better way to welcome the new month than with a collection of desktop wallpapers? We’ve got some eye-catching designs to sweeten up the last few weeks of the year and, if you’re celebrating, to get you in the holiday mood.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Logic in JavaScript – Operators, Conditions, Truthy/Falsy, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/logic-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/logic-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T21:50:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is a versatile programming language that empowers developers to create dynamic and interactive web pages.  One of the foundational elements of JavaScript programming is the application of logical operations to make decisions and control program flow.  In this guide, we'll delve into the basics of logical operations]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced Music Production with FL Studio – Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/advanced-music-production-fl-studio/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/advanced-music-production-fl-studio/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T21:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the right tools and training, anyone can become a music producer. We just release a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you advanced music production skills using FL Studio. Tristan Willcox developed this course. Tristan is a professional music producer with over 10,000 hours in music]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why You Might Want to Move Your Workloads Out of the Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-you-might-want-to-move-your-workloads-out-of-the-cloud/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-you-might-want-to-move-your-workloads-out-of-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T21:24:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is a public cloud like AWS or Microsoft's Azure the right place to host every  deployment workload at every stage of its life? To be honest, I once thought that that was true – at least 95% of the time. But things have changed. Even though new services are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crafting A Killer Brand Identity For A Digital Product]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/crafting-killer-brand-identity-digital-product/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/crafting-killer-brand-identity-digital-product/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Sasha guides you through crucial processes and factors to achieve a consistent brand presence across platforms. She offers an overview of the entire brand identity process, explores collaboration with UI teams, and provides essential details on the assets required for the successful implementation of a digital brand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sasha Denisova)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Few Ways CSS Is Easier To Write In 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/few-ways-css-easier-write-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/few-ways-css-easier-write-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re living in somewhat of a CSS renaissance with new features, techniques, experiments, and ideas coming at us to an extent we haven’t seen since “CSS3”. It’s easy to feel overwhelmed when your profession seems to be advancing at breakneck speed, but Geoff Graham considers the ways “modern” CSS in 2023 has actually made CSS “easier” to write.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction To Full Stack Composability]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/introduction-full-stack-composability/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/introduction-full-stack-composability/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A well-designed composable system should not only consider the technical aspects but also take into account the nature of the content it handles. To help us with that, we can use a Headless Content Management system such as Storyblok.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Responsive Multi-Line Ribbon Shapes (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/css-responsive-multi-line-ribbon-shapes-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/css-responsive-multi-line-ribbon-shapes-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Part 1 of the series, Temani Afif demonstrated how creating ribbon patterns in CSS has evolved with the availability of new CSS features. In this second installment of this brief two-part series, we look at two additional ribbon variations that introduce techniques for masking a repeated background gradient in CSS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating And Maintaining A Voice Of Customer Program]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/creating-maintaining-voice-customer-program/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/creating-maintaining-voice-customer-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Product teams benefit from knowing their users’ needs and how they respond to product updates as they build out the roadmap of a product. This article covers Voice of Customer programs and is aimed at those who work on a product team as well as executives who are looking for how to better inform your products using insight from users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Victor Yocco &amp; Dana Daniels)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Efficient Design-to-Code Handoff Process Using Uno Platform For Figma]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/design-to-code-handoff-process-uno-platform-figma/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/design-to-code-handoff-process-uno-platform-figma/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Effective collaboration between designers and developers is vital to creating good user experiences. However, bridging the handoff between design and development with the many tools and workflows available today has its pitfalls. Matthew Mattei introduces you to the Uno Platform, which offers a robust set of productivity boosters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matthew Mattei)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Responsive Multi-Line Ribbon Shapes (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/css-responsive-multi-line-ribbon-shapes-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/css-responsive-multi-line-ribbon-shapes-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ribbons have been used to accent designs for many years now. But, the way we approach them in CSS has evolved with the introduction of newer features. In this article, Temani Afif combines background and gradient tricks to create ribbon shapes in CSS that are not only responsive but support multi-line text and are easily adjustable with a few CSS variables.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Web Design Documentation]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/designing-web-design-documentation/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/designing-web-design-documentation/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Words alone aren’t enough to safeguard best practices in the world of web design and development. Web design documentation must be like its medium — interactive and constantly evolving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Accessible UI Animations]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/creating-accessible-ui-animations/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/creating-accessible-ui-animations/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animation and accessibility are often seen as two separate powers at odds with one another. How is it possible to strike a balance between elements that move and the possible negative effects they expose to users who are sensitive to motion? Oriana García explains how her team at Mercado Libre tackled the challenge by creating guiding principles for applying animation to user interfaces and incorporating them into the team’s design system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Oriana García)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Playground: From 5-Minute Install To Instant Spin-Up]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/wordpress-playground-5-minute-install-instant-spin-up/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/wordpress-playground-5-minute-install-instant-spin-up/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Playground began as an experiment to see what a self-hosted WordPress experience might look like without the requirement of having to actually install WordPress. A year later, the experiment has evolved into a full-fledged project. Ganesh Dahal demonstrates how WordPress Playground works and gets deep into how it might be used.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ganesh Dahal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Addressing Accessibility Concerns With Using Fluid Type]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/addressing-accessibility-concerns-fluid-type/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/addressing-accessibility-concerns-fluid-type/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-07T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS `clamp()` function is often paired with viewport units for “fluid” font sizing that scales the text up and down at different viewport sizes. As common as this technique is, several voices warn that it opens up situations where text can fail WCAG Success Criterion 1.4.4, which specifies that text should scale up to at least 200% when the user’s browser reaches its 500% maximum zoom level. Max Barvian takes a deep look at the issue and offers ideas to help address it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Maxwell Barvian)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>