<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-12-13T00:11:01.973Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-12-13T00:11:01.973Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting up a screen reader testing environment on your computer]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375722</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/setting-up-a-screen-reader-testing-environment-on-your-computer/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-12T20:56:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sara Soueidan with everything you need, from what screen reading options are out there all the way to setting up virtual machines for them, installing them, and confguring keyboard options. It’s truly a one-stop reference that pulls together disparate …
Setting up a screen reader testing environment on your computer originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Programming? A Handbook for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-programming-tutorial-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-programming-tutorial-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-12T17:10:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the amazing world of programming. This is one of the most useful and powerful skills that you can learn and use to make your visions come true.  In this handbook, we will dive into why programming is important, its applications, its basic concepts, and the skills you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saving Settings for a Custom WordPress Block in the Block Editor]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375577</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/saving-settings-for-a-custom-wordpress-block-in-the-block-editor/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-12T14:06:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve accomplished a bunch of stuff in this series! We created a custom WordPress block that fetches data from an external API and renders it on the front end. Then we took that work and extended it so the data …
Saving Settings for a Custom WordPress Block in the Block Editor originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manoj Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Future Of Design: Human-Powered Or AI-Driven?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/future-design-human-powered-ai-driven/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/future-design-human-powered-ai-driven/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Keima Kai provides a brief history of AI in web design, explores its current implications for creativity, and offers suggestions for how web designers can stay ahead of the curve.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Keima Kai)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Type Checking – How to Check Type in JS with typeof()]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-type-checking-how-to-check-type-in-js-with-typeof/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-type-checking-how-to-check-type-in-js-with-typeof/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-09T22:16:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is a dynamically typed (or loosely typed) programming language. It allows you to declare variables without specifying or defining the variable type. You can create a variable in JavaScript without defining the type of value you can store in the variable. This can affect your program and cause bugs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Networking Commands You Should Know as a Beginner]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linux-networking-commands-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/linux-networking-commands-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-09T18:54:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can you imagine what it would be like to have a laptop but not to be able to access the internet? If you're a developer (or an aspiring one), you'll likely use the internet every day. So you should learn a few useful networking commands.  To learn networking in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Improve Your Data Privacy – A Personal Guide to Protecting Your Online Information]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-personal-guide-to-data-privacy/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-personal-guide-to-data-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-09T18:51:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What's the difference between data privacy and data security? Data security is about protecting your data from unauthorized access (basically ensuring that hackers can't access your data). Data privacy, on the other hand, is about giving you more granular control over how (and by whom) your data is accessed, used,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Kaczanowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Dropdown Menu with JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-dropdown-menu-with-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-dropdown-menu-with-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-09T18:27:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you use the internet, you've likely used a dropdown menu before. They primarily serve two purposes: collecting user input in web forms, and implementing action/navigation menus in web applications. Dropdowns are one of the best ways to offer numerous options for a similar collection of elements without needing to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Eke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Infinite Slider Flipping Through Polaroid Images]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375537</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-infinite-slider-flipping-through-polaroid-images/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-09T14:26:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last article, we made a pretty cool little slider (or “carousel” if that’s what you prefer) that rotates in a circular direction. This time we are going to make one that flips through a stack of Polaroid …
CSS Infinite Slider Flipping Through Polaroid Images originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Statement vs Expression – What's the Difference in Programming?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/statement-vs-expression-whats-the-difference-in-programming/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/statement-vs-expression-whats-the-difference-in-programming/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T23:44:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning the syntax of a programming language is key if you want to use that language effectively. This is true for both new and experienced developers. And one of the most important things to pay attention to while learning a programming language is whether the code you're dealing with is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ogundiran Ayobami</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Slicing – How to Slice an Array and What Does [::-1] Mean?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-slicing-how-to-slice-an-array/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-slicing-how-to-slice-an-array/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T19:13:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Slicing an array is the concept of cutting out – or slicing out – a part of the array. How do you do this in Python? I'll show you how in this article. If you like watching video content to supplement your reading, here's a video version [https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sgXInOpc4Iw] of this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Crack Hashes with Hashcat — a Practical Pentesting Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hacking-with-hashcat-a-practical-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/hacking-with-hashcat-a-practical-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T15:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hashing is one of the pillars of cybersecurity. From securing passwords to sensitive data, there are a variety of use cases for hashing. Hashing is often confused with encryption. A simple difference is that hashed data is not reversible. Encrypted data can be reversed using a key. This is why]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animated Background Stripes That Transition on Hover]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375697</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/animated-background-stripes-transition-hover/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T15:36:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How often to do you reach for the CSS background-size property? If you’re like me — and probably lots of other front-end folks — then it’s usually when you background-size: cover an image to fill the space of an entire …
Animated Background Stripes That Transition on Hover originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Here! “Understanding Privacy,” A New Smashing Book Is Shipping Now]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/understanding-privacy-new-smashing-book/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/understanding-privacy-new-smashing-book/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Understanding Privacy,” the new Smashing Book by Heather Burns, will help you create inclusive, safe and privacy-aware digital experiences. Print books are now shipping! [Jump to details](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/understanding-privacy-new-smashing-book/#about-the-book) and [get the book right away](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/printed-books/understanding-privacy/).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Lambda Interview Questions and Answers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/aws-lambda-interview-questions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/aws-lambda-interview-questions/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T20:54:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'll go over some of the most commonly asked questions that come up in interviews about AWS Lambda.  Note that this is not an exhaustive list – but you can use this guide as a reference to refresh your knowledge and get pointers for further study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mugilan Ragupathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Remove a Specific Character from a String in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-a-specific-character-from-a-string-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-a-specific-character-from-a-string-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T18:43:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When coding in Python, there may be times when you need to remove a character from a string. Removing characters from strings is handy if you are working with user-generated inputs and need to clean your data and remove unwanted characters. Specifically, you may need to remove only one instance]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding Box Shadows to WordPress Blocks and Elements]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375412</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/adding-box-shadows-to-wordpress-blocks-and-elements/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T13:59:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS box-shadow and outline properties gained theme.json support in WordPress 6.1. Let's look at a few examples of how it works in real themes, and what options we have to apply these styles to WordPress blocks and elements.
Adding Box Shadows to WordPress Blocks and Elements originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ganesh Dahal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advent Calendars For Web Designers And Developers (2022 Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/tech-advent-calendars-web-developers-web-designers-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/tech-advent-calendars-web-developers-web-designers-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready for the countdown to Christmas? This year, the web community was once again busy creating tech advent calendars jam-packed with fantastic content to sweeten your days. But which ones to follow? We help you find the right one, whether you’re a front-end dev, UX designer, or content strategist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS is OK, I guess.]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375747</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-is-ok-i-guess/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-06T15:37:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing but ear-to-ear smiles as I was watching this video from @quayjn on YouTube. (No actual name in the byline, though I think it’s Brian Katz if my paper trail is correct).
The best is this Pen you can …
CSS is OK, I guess. originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible Front-End Patterns For Responsive Tables (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/accessible-front-end-patterns-responsive-tables-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/accessible-front-end-patterns-responsive-tables-part1/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-06T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no universal solution for making every kind of table responsive and usable on smaller screens, so we have to rely on various patterns, which Adrian explains in this two-part series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does WWW still belong in URLs?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375184</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/does-www-still-belong-in-urls/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T15:20:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For years, a small pedantry war has been raging in our address bars. In one corner are brands like Google, Instagram, and Facebook. This group has chosen to redirect example.com to www.example.com. In the opposite corner: …
Does WWW still belong in URLs? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pieter De Decker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Infinite and Circular Rotating Image Slider]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375308</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-only-infinite-and-circular-image-slider/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T14:12:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image sliders (also called carousels) are everywhere. There are a lot of CSS tricks to create the common slider where the images slide from left to right (or the opposite). It’s the same deal with the many JavaScript libraries out …
CSS Infinite and Circular Rotating Image Slider originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Anatomy Of Themed Design System Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/anatomy-themed-design-system-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/anatomy-themed-design-system-components/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world of design systems can be overwhelming sometimes. There’s a lot to take in when you get into that space! In this article, Dan Donald dives into a simple component and explores some issues, complexity, and power we can encounter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Dan Donald)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digging Deeper Into Container Style Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375607</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/digging-deeper-into-container-style-queries/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T13:59:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wrote up some early thoughts on container style queries a little while back. It’s still early days. They’re already defined in the CSS Containment Module Level 1 specification (currently in Editor’s Draft status) but there’s still a couple of …
Digging Deeper Into Container Style Queries originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FabUnit: A Smart Way To Control And Synchronize Typo And Space]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/fabunit-smart-way-control-synchronize-typo-space/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/fabunit-smart-way-control-synchronize-typo-space/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’ll take a look at the Sass function that does all the work for you — with no media queries, no breakpoints, and no design jumps. In this article, Fabienne Bielmann explains what FabUnit stands for and why she decided to create her very own responsive magic formula.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Fabienne Bielmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using The New Constrained Layout In WordPress Block Themes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375278</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-the-new-constrained-layout-in-wordpress-block-themes/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T14:11:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the main goals of the WordPress Site Editor (and, yes, that is now the “official” name) is to move basic block styling from CSS to structured JSON. JSON files are machine-readable, which makes it consumable by …
Using The New Constrained Layout In WordPress Block Themes originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ganesh Dahal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Endings And New Beginnings (December 2022 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-december-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-december-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December is almost here, so why not spread some holiday love across your devices? We’ve got some beautiful wallpapers to sweeten up the last days of the year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Than “Slapping Paint on a Website”]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375190</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/more-than-slapping-paint-on-a-website/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-29T15:03:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m a sucker for anything about front-end job titles.
Anselm Hannemann:
CSS evolved and we’re beyond the point where everyone can just do it as a side interest. We all can learn it and build amazing stuff with it, 
…
More Than “Slapping Paint on a Website” originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newer Things to Know About Good Ol’ HTML Lists]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375273</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/newer-things-to-know-about-good-ol-html-lists/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-28T14:05:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML lists are boring. They don’t do much, so we don’t really think about them despite how widely used they are. And we’re still able to do the same things we’ve always done to customize them, like removing markers, reversing …
Newer Things to Know About Good Ol’ HTML Lists originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Schwarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Document Object Model (DOM) Geometry: A Beginner’s Introduction And Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/document-object-model-geometry-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/document-object-model-geometry-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, Pearl Akpan analyzes the methods and properties that make user interface solutions such as infinite scrolling, animating elements on scroll, or even the popular drag and drop achievable, and afterward, dives into some practical use cases for them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Pearl Akpan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Messages & Color Contrast]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375343</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/apple-messages-color-contrast/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T14:25:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, color me this! I was griping to myself last night about just how gosh dang hard it is to read text messages in Apple Messages. You know, not the blue bubbles that you get when messaging other iPhone users. …
Apple Messages & Color Contrast originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Developer Blog]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375599</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/wordpress-developer-blog/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T18:36:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, hey check this out. Looks like there is a brand spankin’ new blog over at WordPress.org all about WordPress development. In the original proposal for the blog, Birgit Pauli-Haak writes:
The Make Core blog has a heavy 
…
WordPress Developer Blog originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing A Vue App]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/optimizing-vue-app/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/optimizing-vue-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prioritizing performance when building our web apps improves the user experience and helps ensure they can be used by as many people as possible. In this article, Michelle Barker will walk you through some of the front-end optimization tips to keep our Vue apps as efficient as possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taming the Cascade With BEM and Modern CSS Selectors]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375144</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/taming-the-cascade-with-bem-and-modern-css-selectors/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T13:59:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BEM. Like seemingly all techniques in the world of front-end development, writing CSS in a BEM format can be polarizing. But it is – at least in my Twitter bubble – one of the better-liked CSS methodologies.
Personally, I think …
Taming the Cascade With BEM and Modern CSS Selectors originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Keyboard Accessibility: JavaScript (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/guide-keyboard-accessibility-javascript-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/guide-keyboard-accessibility-javascript-part2/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is the second of two parts about a guide to making websites accessible to keyboard users. Here Cristian Diaz covers a toolset on JavaScript that you can mix into different components to create a great experience for keyboard users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cristian Díaz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 54 With Stéphanie Walter: What Is User Journey Mapping?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/smashing-podcast-episode-54/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/smashing-podcast-episode-54/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode we’re talking about User Journey Mapping. What is it, and how does it help us build better digital products? Vitaly talks to expert Stéphanie Walter to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Image Optimization On Jamstack Sites]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/guide-image-optimization-jamstack-sites/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/guide-image-optimization-jamstack-sites/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Alba Silvente shows us the theoretical and practical solutions to the most common problems when working with images and how to automate them by using a headless CMS and an image CDN.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alba Silvente)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Automated Test Results To Improve Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/automated-test-results-improve-accessibility/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/automated-test-results-improve-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Noah Mashni and Mark Steadman share their approach to how to leverage the automated test results from the accessibility checks to drive change and reach sustainable digital accessibility transformation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Noah Mashni and Mark Steadman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Keyboard Accessibility: HTML And CSS (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/guide-keyboard-accessibility-html-css-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/guide-keyboard-accessibility-html-css-part1/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Cristian Diaz covers how to use HTML and CSS to create an accessible experience for keyboard users while mentioning what WCAG criteria we should keep into consideration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cristian Díaz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>