<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-12-14T00:10:12.874Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-12-14T00:10:12.874Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Virtual Host Enumeration – How to Uncover Hidden Web Assets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/virtual-host-enumeration-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/virtual-host-enumeration-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T18:48:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When performing external penetration testing or bug bounty hunting, security experts explore the targeted system from various angles to collect as much information as possible and identify potential attack vectors. This involves identifying all the available assets, domains, and subdomains. During the testing reconnaissance phase, testers spend time on virtual]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nairuz Abulhul</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Go Tools to Use for Your Frontend Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/go-tools-for-your-frontend-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/go-tools-for-your-frontend-projects/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T18:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Go programming language [https://go.dev/] is renowned for its efficiency in  backend development [https://blog.boot.dev/golang/become-golang-backend-dev/]. But it's pretty easy to extend its capabilities to frontend projects as well. This article explores essential Go tools that empower frontend developers to enhance their workflows, emphasizing simplicity and productivity. Prequisites Before diving into]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ekemini Samuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced Google Sheets Concepts – How to Build a Vigenère Cipher]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/advanced-google-sheets-concepts-build-a-vigenere-cipher/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/advanced-google-sheets-concepts-build-a-vigenere-cipher/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T18:13:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Vigenère Cipher encrypts and decrypts text using a different alphabet for each letter. It consists of text to encrypt and a key with a different letter corresponding to each letter in the text.  Creating a grid of alphabets helps illustrate this practice. If the first letter in your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Scroll Snapping Aligned With Global Page Layout: A Full-Width Slider Case Study]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/css-scroll-snapping-aligned-global-page-layout-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/css-scroll-snapping-aligned-global-page-layout-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you run into a situation where you need the padding of one element to align with the padding of another element? In this article, Brecht De Ruyte demonstrates the issue with a full-width slider component that breaks out of the main page container and shares a couple of techniques to keep it visually aligned with other elements on the page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Brecht De Ruyte)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up a Django Development Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-a-django-development-environment/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-a-django-development-environment/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T15:52:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Django is a high-level web framework written in Python that encourages a rapid and realistic functional design. The Django web framework is free and open-source and is widely used to create both small and large web applications. In this tutorial, you will learn the following:  * What a development]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Poromon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[innerHTML vs innerText vs textContent – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/innerhtml-vs-innertext-vs-textcontent/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/innerhtml-vs-innertext-vs-textcontent/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In HTML, innerHTML, innerText, and textContent are properties of the DOM (Document Object Model). They allow you to read and update the content of HTML elements. But they have different behaviours in terms of the content they include and how they handle HTML markup. By the end of this article,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Semah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Comment Your JavaScript Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/comment-your-javascript-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/comment-your-javascript-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing comments in JavaScript is crucial for code readability, maintainability, and developer collaboration. Comments serve as notes within the codebase, explaining its functionality and logic, or providing context.  In this article, I will explain the significance of commenting your code, best practices to follow, and examples showcasing effective commenting]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asynchronous JavaScript – How to Use Promises in Your JS Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-promises-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-promises-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:52:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is a versatile programming language that powers the dynamic behavior of websites.  As web applications become more sophisticated, the need to handle asynchronous operations efficiently becomes crucial. Asynchronous JavaScript allows you to execute code without blocking the main thread, ensuring a smoother user experience.  Promises are a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is an API Gateway and Why is it Useful?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-api-gateways/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-api-gateways/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:40:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[APIs are often referred to as the front-door for applications to access data and business logic from backend services. As explained here [https://lightcloud.substack.com/p/api-integration-patterns], an API is essentially the interface that a piece of software presents to other humans or programs, allowing them to interact with that software. When creating an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adetunji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Components For Consumption, Not Complexity (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/building-components-consumption-not-complexity-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/building-components-consumption-not-complexity-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design systems can be of immense help, but failure to adopt them invalidates the hard work that goes into building the thing in the first place! In this two-part series of articles, Luis shares his experience with design systems and how you can overcome the potential pitfalls.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Luis Ouriach)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install MongoDB with OpenSSL 3 Support on Fedora 39]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-mongodb-with-openssl-3-support-on-fedora-39/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-mongodb-with-openssl-3-support-on-fedora-39/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T18:52:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you will learn how to install MongoDB with support for the latest version of OpenSSL on the Fedora Linux operating system.  If you already have it installed, this tutorial will help you fix the mongosh OpenSSL configuration error. To follow along, you will need a terminal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matheus A. S. Freitas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++ Tutorial – What Are the constexpr and constinit Specifiers?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cpp-constexpr-and-constinit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cpp-constexpr-and-constinit/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T18:50:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we write programs, many operations which are performed at runtime can actually be done at compile time – that is, baked into code.  This improves program performance since operations are no longer being computed on the fly, during runtime.  While these techniques of offloading operations to compile]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jayant Chowdhary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preparing For Interaction To Next Paint, A New Web Core Vital]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/preparing-interaction-next-paint-web-core-vital/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/preparing-interaction-next-paint-web-core-vital/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting in March 2024, Interaction to Next Paint will formally replace First Input Delay as a Core Web Vital metric. Learn how the two metrics differ, why we needed a new way to measure interaction responsiveness, and how you can start optimizing the performance of your site now for a seamless transition to the latest Core Web Vital metric.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five-Second Testing: Taking A Closer Look At First Impressions (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/five-second-testing-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/five-second-testing-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Five-second testing is a popular method of usability research used in the industry, yet in essence, its core belief boils down to virtually a superstition. Eduard Kuric looks under the hood at how first impressions are affected by various factors and how UX researchers and product owners can ensure that the user’s first steps can get off on the right foot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eduard Kuric)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Marketing Changed OOP In JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/marketing-changed-oop-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/marketing-changed-oop-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussing the decisions surrounding JavaScript prototypes, the article by Juan Diego Rodriguez scrutinizes their origin, examines missteps in the design, and explores how these factors have affected the way we write JavaScript today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Juan Diego Rodríguez)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recovering Deleted Files From Your Git Working Tree]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/recovering-deleted-files-git-working-tree/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/12/recovering-deleted-files-git-working-tree/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is designed to assure us that we can track a project’s files at different points in time. But it doesn’t assure us that those files are always safe along the way. For those of you who have dealt with the sinking feeling that you’ve irrevocably deleted and lost files, Sanmi has a couple of approaches that, in the right situations, may help bring them back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Oluwasanmi Akande)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cold Days, Shining Lights (December 2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-december-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-december-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Could there be a better way to welcome the new month than with a collection of desktop wallpapers? We’ve got some eye-catching designs to sweeten up the last few weeks of the year and, if you’re celebrating, to get you in the holiday mood.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crafting A Killer Brand Identity For A Digital Product]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/crafting-killer-brand-identity-digital-product/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/crafting-killer-brand-identity-digital-product/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Sasha guides you through crucial processes and factors to achieve a consistent brand presence across platforms. She offers an overview of the entire brand identity process, explores collaboration with UI teams, and provides essential details on the assets required for the successful implementation of a digital brand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sasha Denisova)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Few Ways CSS Is Easier To Write In 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/few-ways-css-easier-write-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/few-ways-css-easier-write-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re living in somewhat of a CSS renaissance with new features, techniques, experiments, and ideas coming at us to an extent we haven’t seen since “CSS3”. It’s easy to feel overwhelmed when your profession seems to be advancing at breakneck speed, but Geoff Graham considers the ways “modern” CSS in 2023 has actually made CSS “easier” to write.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction To Full Stack Composability]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/introduction-full-stack-composability/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/introduction-full-stack-composability/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A well-designed composable system should not only consider the technical aspects but also take into account the nature of the content it handles. To help us with that, we can use a Headless Content Management system such as Storyblok.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Responsive Multi-Line Ribbon Shapes (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/css-responsive-multi-line-ribbon-shapes-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/css-responsive-multi-line-ribbon-shapes-part2/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Part 1 of the series, Temani Afif demonstrated how creating ribbon patterns in CSS has evolved with the availability of new CSS features. In this second installment of this brief two-part series, we look at two additional ribbon variations that introduce techniques for masking a repeated background gradient in CSS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating And Maintaining A Voice Of Customer Program]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/creating-maintaining-voice-customer-program/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/creating-maintaining-voice-customer-program/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Product teams benefit from knowing their users’ needs and how they respond to product updates as they build out the roadmap of a product. This article covers Voice of Customer programs and is aimed at those who work on a product team as well as executives who are looking for how to better inform your products using insight from users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Victor Yocco &amp; Dana Daniels)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Efficient Design-to-Code Handoff Process Using Uno Platform For Figma]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/design-to-code-handoff-process-uno-platform-figma/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/design-to-code-handoff-process-uno-platform-figma/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Effective collaboration between designers and developers is vital to creating good user experiences. However, bridging the handoff between design and development with the many tools and workflows available today has its pitfalls. Matthew Mattei introduces you to the Uno Platform, which offers a robust set of productivity boosters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matthew Mattei)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Responsive Multi-Line Ribbon Shapes (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/css-responsive-multi-line-ribbon-shapes-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/11/css-responsive-multi-line-ribbon-shapes-part1/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ribbons have been used to accent designs for many years now. But, the way we approach them in CSS has evolved with the introduction of newer features. In this article, Temani Afif combines background and gradient tricks to create ribbon shapes in CSS that are not only responsive but support multi-line text and are easily adjustable with a few CSS variables.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Temani Afif)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>