<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-04-19T00:10:20.149Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-04-19T00:10:20.149Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy a NodeJS App with AWS CloudFormation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploy-nodejs-app-with-cloudformation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploy-nodejs-app-with-cloudformation/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T18:03:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine you have built a great product and its user base is growing rapidly. You want to scale your product to be available to people around the world. To do this, you'll need good cloud infrastructure. But managing your cloud infrastructure manually can be exhausting. You might start wondering, "how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Common Causes of Invalid HTML Syntax – and How to Fix Them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/invalid-html-syntax-examples-and-fixes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/invalid-html-syntax-examples-and-fixes/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T16:51:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remember those treehouses that we had as children and how the wood would wear, tear, and eventually collapse because we just would not stop jumping around inside it? Well that's kind of like HTML. This markup language is like the wood to your coding project. If it’s invalid, your solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CHRISTINE T. BELZIE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does $ Mean in Python? Operator Meaning + String Formatting Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-the-dollar-sign-mean-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-the-dollar-sign-mean-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T16:39:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Operators are special symbols you can use to perform different operations on variables (operands) in programming.  Python has different operators like arithmetic operators, assignment operators, logical operators, boolean operators, comparison operators, bitwise operators, and so on.  Although you'll not come across the dollar sign ($) operator when learning]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Primitive Values vs Reference Values – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-assigning-values-vs-assigning-references/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-assigning-values-vs-assigning-references/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T16:31:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In JavaScript, variables can hold two types of data: primitive values and reference values. Understanding the difference between these two types of data is crucial for writing efficient and bug-free code.  In this short article, we will explore the difference between values and references in JavaScript. Table]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 59 With Chiara Aliotta: What Is Design Storytelling?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/smashing-podcast-episode-59/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/smashing-podcast-episode-59/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of The Smashing Podcast, we take a look at design storytelling. What is it, and how can it help us shape digital experiences? Vitaly talks to Chiara Aliotta to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ModuleNotFoundError: no module named 'requests' [Solved in Python Django]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-module-not-found-error-solved/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-module-not-found-error-solved/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T23:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Errors are an inevitable part of programming, and every programmer will encounter them at some point in their career.  Errors in programming can take various forms, including syntax errors, logic errors, and runtime errors, and they can have a significant impact on the functioning of a program. Understanding the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is DevOps? How Development + Operations Helps Teams Work More Efficiently]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-devops-works/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-devops-works/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T23:37:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When developers and operations teams work together, they can identify and solve problems more quickly. This helps them deliver software to users faster and with fewer errors.  This general practice is called DevOps. It involves using tools and techniques to automate tasks and make software development and deployment more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Satyam Tripathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Git Rebase – Tutorial for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-git-rebase/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-git-rebase/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T22:17:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The software engineering landscape is constantly changing. Staying up to date on new technologies is absolutely critical. But as developers, sometimes we forget how important it is to dig a bit deeper into the tried and true technologies that are the backbone of software development – such as version control]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Abbene</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Protect Your PWA – Web App Security Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-protect-your-pwa/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-protect-your-pwa/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T21:28:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, everybody! I'm Rahul [https://fueler.io/rahoool]. In today's world, web apps have become more prevalent because they work seamlessly on multiple devices. But as with any application, PWAs can be vulnerable to security threats, which can compromise user data and damage the reputation. It's natural to get excited about launching something]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rahul</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Machine Leaning without Libraries or Frameworks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-machine-leaning-without-libraries-or-frameworks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-machine-leaning-without-libraries-or-frameworks/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T16:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready to unravel the mysteries of machine learning algorithms and elevate your software development skills? Look no further!  We just published a machine learning course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This "No Black Box" Machine Learning Course in JavaScript offers a unique, hands-on approach to understanding machine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Design Thinking?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/what-is-design-thinking/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/what-is-design-thinking/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered if things could have been done differently? But not sure how? Well, then, do not fall in love with the solution, but fall in love with the problem! Here’s an article to dive deep into how design thinking could do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Krithika Subramanian)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conda Channel - What Is a Channel in Conda?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-channel-in-conda/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-channel-in-conda/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-14T16:36:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you install a package in Conda, it is downloaded and extracted from a remote directory using the directory's URL. The directory where these packages are stored is known as a channel. In this article, you'll learn what a channel is, how to use default channels, and how add new]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passkeys: What the Heck and Why?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377305</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/passkeys-what-the-heck-and-why/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T17:41:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These things called passkeys sure are making the rounds these days. They were a main attraction at W3C TPAC 2022, gained support in Safari 16, are finding their way into macOS and iOS, and are slated to …
Passkeys: What the Heck and Why? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Neal Fennimore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Design An Effective User Onboarding Flow]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/design-effective-user-onboarding-flow/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/design-effective-user-onboarding-flow/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to maximize conversions or collect necessary user information for other purposes, a user onboarding flow is necessary. In this article, you will learn how, with the help of Feathery, to design an effective user onboarding flow for your app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Suzanne Scacca)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Protect Your App With A Threat Model Based On JSONDiff]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/protect-app-threat-model-jsondiff/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/protect-app-threat-model-jsondiff/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a developer who wants to concentrate on delivering a killer application rather than worrying about countless security issues, threat model documents can help you do that. With small architectural changes, we can make these threats manageable and prevent them in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zack Grossbart &amp; Terry Yao)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Algorithms: Skills Of Designers That AI Can’t Replicate]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/skills-designers-ai-cant-replicate/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/skills-designers-ai-cant-replicate/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article highlights non-technical skills like curiosity, observation, empathy, advocacy, visual communication, and collaboration that designers routinely use in their process to make a difference through design. AI can be used to augment designers’ workflow instead of replacing people.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lyndon Cerejo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swing Into April (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With April just around the corner, we have a new collection of desktop and mobile wallpapers waiting for you to celebrate the beginning of the new month. Designed by creatives from all across the globe, the wallpapers come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Comprehensive Checklist For Running Design Workshops]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/organizing-design-workshops-checklist/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/organizing-design-workshops-checklist/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Workshops are all about people: they involve people, are conducted by people, and aim to close the gaps in people’s communication. Slava Shestopalov shares a checklist with everything you need to keep in mind when running a workshop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Slava Shestopalov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fine-Grained Access Handling And Data Management With Row-Level Security]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/access-handling-data-management-row-level-security/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/access-handling-data-management-row-level-security/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dealing with sensitive data is an important topic for any app. In this article, you will find out how to handle sensitive or confidential information in your apps and what Row-Level Security means.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Handoff Is No Handoff]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/best-handoff-is-no-handoff/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/best-handoff-is-no-handoff/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design handoffs are inefficient and painful. They cause frustration, friction and a lot of back and forth. Can we avoid them altogether? Of course we can! Let’s see how to do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overcoming The Challenges Of Content Creation For Informational Websites]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/overcoming-challenges-content-creation-informational-websites/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/overcoming-challenges-content-creation-informational-websites/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Content matters! Unfortunately, when it comes to informational websites, content quality is often poor. There is no magic answer to fix that. However, there are practical techniques you can use to improve the copy on your websites and ensure your users find the content they are looking for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Cross-Browser DevTools Features You Might Not Know]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377264</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/some-cross-browser-devtools-features-you-might-not-know/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-22T20:22:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I spend a lot of time in DevTools, and I’m sure you do too. Sometimes I even bounce between them, especially when I’m debugging cross-browser issues. DevTools is a lot like browsers themselves — not all of the features in …
Some Cross-Browser DevTools Features You Might Not Know originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pankaj Parashar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 58 With Debbie Levitt: What Is CX Design?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/smashing-podcast-episode-58/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/smashing-podcast-episode-58/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we ask what is Customer Experience design, and how does it differ from User Experience design? Vitaly Friedman talks to expert Debbie Levitt to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>