<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-12-20T00:09:50.944Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-12-20T00:09:50.944Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Have Fun Building React Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/have-fun-building-react-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/have-fun-building-react-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T21:41:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building React apps can either be a very fun experience or a very difficult and tedious one, based off of the tools you choose. React is a JavaScript library that, unlike frameworks like Angular, leave us to making a lot of decisions on our own. You have to choose which]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Your Own Wireguard VPN in Five Minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-your-own-wireguard-vpn-in-five-minutes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-your-own-wireguard-vpn-in-five-minutes/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T20:46:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may already understand how important a good VPN can be for maintaining the security and privacy of your mobile communications.  Whether you need to use your phone for banking over a public airport or coffee shop WiFi connection, or you're worried about the wrong people listening in on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Speed up Your Software Development Pipeline]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-speed-up-your-software-development-pipeline/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-speed-up-your-software-development-pipeline/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T17:51:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've ever managed a software development pipeline—or have plans to do so—there's one thing you'll need to prioritize above almost all else: speed.  No matter the type of software you're working on, you'll always be under pressure to speed up your team's deliverables. Some of that pressure might]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrej Kovacevic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Playground: Running WordPress in the Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376297</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/wordpress-playground-run-in-browser/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T16:52:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being able to quickly spin up a WordPress instance has been the strength of WordPress ever since its famous “five-minute install”. Upload a few files, configure a few settings, and you’re off.
The friction of uploading files has gotten …
WordPress Playground: Running WordPress in the Browser originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taking The Stress Out Of Design System Management]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/taking-stress-out-design-system-management/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/taking-stress-out-design-system-management/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Masha goes over five tips that make it easier to manage a design system while increasing its effectiveness. This short guide is aimed at smaller teams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Masha Shaposhnikova)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[API Testing Best Practices – How to Test APIs for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rules-of-api-testing-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rules-of-api-testing-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T21:25:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this digital age, APIs have become the cornerstone of how data is shared and processed. But many users are often unaware of the fact that they are putting their trust in an API and not a person. This is why it's important to leverage API testing techniques to ensure]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hillary Nyakundi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility Best Practices – What to Remember When Building Accessible Web Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/accessibility-best-practices-to-make-web-apps-accessible/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/accessibility-best-practices-to-make-web-apps-accessible/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T21:01:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone should be able to use your websites and apps - both people with disabilities and those without. This will make your website accessible. Think about the last site you built, or your favorite site. Are you confident that anyone can use your site and perform the critical actions it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shruti Kapoor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pair Programming with the ChatGPT AI – Does GPT-3.5 Understand Bash?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pair-programming-with-the-chatgpt-ai-how-well-does-gpt-3-5-understand-bash/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pair-programming-with-the-chatgpt-ai-how-well-does-gpt-3-5-understand-bash/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T17:51:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We've been hearing a lot about artificial intelligence and natural language processing – and in particular about the latest version of OpenAI's GPT – for weeks.  The recent release of GPT 3.5, and specifically the very new ChatGPT tool, is definitely a huge leap forward. You may have read]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Telegram Bot using Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-telegram-bot-using-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-telegram-bot-using-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T17:42:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automated chatbots are quite useful for stimulating interactions. We can create chatbots for Slack, Discord, and other platforms.  In this article, I'll teach you how to build a Telegram chatbot that will tell you your horoscope. So, let’s get started! How to Get Your Bot Token To set up]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a ROM? ROM Price and Cost Estimate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-rom-price-and-cost-estimate-2/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-rom-price-and-cost-estimate-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T17:27:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROM stands for Rough Order of Magnitude. It is a project management guideline to determine the estimated range of costs for a project. This article will explain:  1. Who should use a ROM  2. When to use a ROM  3. How to calculate a ROM  4.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Infinite 3D Sliders]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375621</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-infinite-3d-sliders/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T14:58:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this series, we’ve been making image sliders with nothing but HTML and CSS. The idea is that we can use the same markup but different CSS to get wildly different results, no matter how many images we toss …
CSS Infinite 3D Sliders originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boosting Productivity For Designers With Efficient Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/optimizing-design-workflow-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/optimizing-design-workflow-tools/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Ashish Bogawat shares some of his favorite ways how to boost productivity and do things faster, better, and probably more fun by using efficient tools and workflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ashish Bogawat)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS display:none and visibility:hidden – What's the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-display-none-and-visibility-hidden-the-difference/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-display-none-and-visibility-hidden-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T23:13:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[display:none and visibility:hidden are two style declarations you can use to hide elements on the screen with CSS. But what are the differences between them? When building applications, there are times that you want to hide elements visually (not deleting them from the DOM, just the screen). You can do]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Select the Right EC2 Instance – A Guide to EC2 Instances and Their Capabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-select-the-right-ec2-instance/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-select-the-right-ec2-instance/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T19:08:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EC2 (Elastic Compute Cloud) is the most widely-used compute service from AWS. It's also one of the oldest services launched by AWS, as it was started in 2006.  In this article, I will go through some things you should consider when selecting an EC2 instance.  You can think]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adetunji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So, you’d like to animate the display property]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375714</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/so-youd-like-to-animate-the-display-property/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T15:41:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS Working Group gave that a thumbs-up a couple weeks ago. The super-duper conceptual proposal being that we can animate or transition from, say, display: block to display: none.
It’s a bit of a brain-twister to reason …
So, you’d like to animate the display property originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Prioritize User Security When Collecting Offline Data]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/prioritize-user-security-collecting-offline-data/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/prioritize-user-security-collecting-offline-data/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Concerns over online privacy and security are nothing new. In this article, Suzanne Scacca explores how the right CSV importer can help businesses better prioritize user security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Suzanne Scacca)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Links on AI-Related Stuff]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376201</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/some-links-on-ai-related-stuff/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-14T21:34:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every so often, I find that the links I save to read later fall into natural groups or patterns that reveal common threads of interest. The past couple of weeks have produced a lot of thoughts about ChatGPT, an …
Some Links on AI-Related Stuff originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unchain My Inaccessibly-Labelled Heart]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375952</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/unchain-my-inaccessibly-labelled-heart/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-14T14:08:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Suzy Naschansky from the HTMHell Advent Calendar:
<h2 id="article1-heading"All About Dragons</h2<pI like dragons. Blah blah blah blah blah.</p<p<a id="article1-read-more" aria-labelledby="article1-read-more article1-heading"Read more</a</p
See that aria-labelledby attribute? It chains two IDs from the …
Unchain My Inaccessibly-Labelled Heart originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Holiday Snowtacular 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376229</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/holiday-snowtacular-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T23:03:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve got ourselves a real holiday treat! Join host Alex Trost from the Frontend Horse community for the Holiday Snowtacular 2022 this Friday, December 16.
There’s a lineup of 12 awesome speakers — including Chris Coyier, Cassidy Williams, Kevin …
Holiday Snowtacular 2022 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Privacy: Protect Your Users, Protect Yourself]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/understanding-privacy-protect-your-users-protect-yourself/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/understanding-privacy-protect-your-users-protect-yourself/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All of us want to create inclusive, safe, and privacy-aware digital experiences, but where to begin? Our brand new Smashing Book, “Understanding Privacy,” written by Heather Burns, can help you lay the ground for future developers, designers, and project managers to build a better web for tomorrow. [Jump to the details](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/understanding-privacy-new-smashing-book/#about-the-book) or [get the book right away](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/printed-books/understanding-privacy/).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Heather Burns)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible Front-End Patterns For Responsive Tables (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/accessible-front-end-patterns-responsive-tables-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/accessible-front-end-patterns-responsive-tables-part2/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no universal solution for making every kind of table responsive and usable on smaller screens, so we have to rely on various patterns, which Adrian explains in this two-part series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Few Times Container Size Queries Would Have Helped Me Out]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375728</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-few-times-container-size-queries-would-have-helped-me-out/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T13:53:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Container Queries are still gaining traction and many of us are getting our hands wet with them, even if it’s for little experiments or whatnot. They’ve got great, but not quite full, browser support — enough to justify using …
A Few Times Container Size Queries Would Have Helped Me Out originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Christofi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting up a screen reader testing environment on your computer]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375722</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/setting-up-a-screen-reader-testing-environment-on-your-computer/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-12T20:56:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sara Soueidan with everything you need, from what screen reading options are out there all the way to setting up virtual machines for them, installing them, and confguring keyboard options. It’s truly a one-stop reference that pulls together disparate …
Setting up a screen reader testing environment on your computer originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saving Settings for a Custom WordPress Block in the Block Editor]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375577</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/saving-settings-for-a-custom-wordpress-block-in-the-block-editor/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-12T14:06:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve accomplished a bunch of stuff in this series! We created a custom WordPress block that fetches data from an external API and renders it on the front end. Then we took that work and extended it so the data …
Saving Settings for a Custom WordPress Block in the Block Editor originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manoj Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Future Of Design: Human-Powered Or AI-Driven?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/future-design-human-powered-ai-driven/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/future-design-human-powered-ai-driven/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Keima Kai provides a brief history of AI in web design, explores its current implications for creativity, and offers suggestions for how web designers can stay ahead of the curve.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Keima Kai)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Infinite Slider Flipping Through Polaroid Images]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375537</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-infinite-slider-flipping-through-polaroid-images/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-09T14:26:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last article, we made a pretty cool little slider (or “carousel” if that’s what you prefer) that rotates in a circular direction. This time we are going to make one that flips through a stack of Polaroid …
CSS Infinite Slider Flipping Through Polaroid Images originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animated Background Stripes That Transition on Hover]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375697</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/animated-background-stripes-transition-hover/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T15:36:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How often to do you reach for the CSS background-size property? If you’re like me — and probably lots of other front-end folks — then it’s usually when you background-size: cover an image to fill the space of an entire …
Animated Background Stripes That Transition on Hover originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Here! “Understanding Privacy,” A New Smashing Book Is Shipping Now]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/understanding-privacy-new-smashing-book/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/understanding-privacy-new-smashing-book/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Understanding Privacy,” the new Smashing Book by Heather Burns, will help you create inclusive, safe and privacy-aware digital experiences. Print books are now shipping! [Jump to details](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/understanding-privacy-new-smashing-book/#about-the-book) and [get the book right away](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/printed-books/understanding-privacy/).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding Box Shadows to WordPress Blocks and Elements]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375412</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/adding-box-shadows-to-wordpress-blocks-and-elements/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T13:59:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS box-shadow and outline properties gained theme.json support in WordPress 6.1. Let's look at a few examples of how it works in real themes, and what options we have to apply these styles to WordPress blocks and elements.
Adding Box Shadows to WordPress Blocks and Elements originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ganesh Dahal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advent Calendars For Web Designers And Developers (2022 Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/tech-advent-calendars-web-developers-web-designers-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/tech-advent-calendars-web-developers-web-designers-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready for the countdown to Christmas? This year, the web community was once again busy creating tech advent calendars jam-packed with fantastic content to sweeten your days. But which ones to follow? We help you find the right one, whether you’re a front-end dev, UX designer, or content strategist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS is OK, I guess.]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375747</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-is-ok-i-guess/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-06T15:37:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing but ear-to-ear smiles as I was watching this video from @quayjn on YouTube. (No actual name in the byline, though I think it’s Brian Katz if my paper trail is correct).
The best is this Pen you can …
CSS is OK, I guess. originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible Front-End Patterns For Responsive Tables (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/accessible-front-end-patterns-responsive-tables-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/accessible-front-end-patterns-responsive-tables-part1/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-06T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no universal solution for making every kind of table responsive and usable on smaller screens, so we have to rely on various patterns, which Adrian explains in this two-part series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does WWW still belong in URLs?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375184</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/does-www-still-belong-in-urls/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T15:20:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For years, a small pedantry war has been raging in our address bars. In one corner are brands like Google, Instagram, and Facebook. This group has chosen to redirect example.com to www.example.com. In the opposite corner: …
Does WWW still belong in URLs? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pieter De Decker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Infinite and Circular Rotating Image Slider]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375308</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-only-infinite-and-circular-image-slider/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T14:12:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image sliders (also called carousels) are everywhere. There are a lot of CSS tricks to create the common slider where the images slide from left to right (or the opposite). It’s the same deal with the many JavaScript libraries out …
CSS Infinite and Circular Rotating Image Slider originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Anatomy Of Themed Design System Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/anatomy-themed-design-system-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/anatomy-themed-design-system-components/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world of design systems can be overwhelming sometimes. There’s a lot to take in when you get into that space! In this article, Dan Donald dives into a simple component and explores some issues, complexity, and power we can encounter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Dan Donald)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FabUnit: A Smart Way To Control And Synchronize Typo And Space]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/fabunit-smart-way-control-synchronize-typo-space/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/fabunit-smart-way-control-synchronize-typo-space/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’ll take a look at the Sass function that does all the work for you — with no media queries, no breakpoints, and no design jumps. In this article, Fabienne Bielmann explains what FabUnit stands for and why she decided to create her very own responsive magic formula.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Fabienne Bielmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Endings And New Beginnings (December 2022 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-december-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-december-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December is almost here, so why not spread some holiday love across your devices? We’ve got some beautiful wallpapers to sweeten up the last days of the year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Document Object Model (DOM) Geometry: A Beginner’s Introduction And Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/document-object-model-geometry-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/document-object-model-geometry-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, Pearl Akpan analyzes the methods and properties that make user interface solutions such as infinite scrolling, animating elements on scroll, or even the popular drag and drop achievable, and afterward, dives into some practical use cases for them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Pearl Akpan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing A Vue App]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/optimizing-vue-app/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/optimizing-vue-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prioritizing performance when building our web apps improves the user experience and helps ensure they can be used by as many people as possible. In this article, Michelle Barker will walk you through some of the front-end optimization tips to keep our Vue apps as efficient as possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Keyboard Accessibility: JavaScript (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/guide-keyboard-accessibility-javascript-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/11/guide-keyboard-accessibility-javascript-part2/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is the second of two parts about a guide to making websites accessible to keyboard users. Here Cristian Diaz covers a toolset on JavaScript that you can mix into different components to create a great experience for keyboard users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cristian Díaz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>