<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-01-12T00:10:06.261Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-01-12T00:10:06.261Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Accessibility – Common ARIA Mistakes to Avoid]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-accessibility-common-aria-mistakes-to-avoid/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-accessibility-common-aria-mistakes-to-avoid/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T21:58:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible Rich Internet Applications – or ARIA – is a set of attributes and roles defined by the Web Accessibility Initiative [https://www.w3.org/WAI/]. These make the web more accessible to people with disabilities.  ARIA is extremely important for building accessible web applications. But it's very easy to misuse ARIA and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilknur Eren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS by Building the Google Logo in Pure CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-google-logo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-google-logo/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T19:15:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the best ways to learn CSS is by creating something useful while you learn. I will show you how to use the following CSS items by creating the Google logo:  * position relative and absolute  * pseudo classes ::before and ::after  * positioning an element]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Bland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React Dev Tools – With Example Code and Videos]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-dev-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-dev-tools/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T18:18:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working on a React project, one of the easiest ways to debug your code is using the React Dev Tools. React Dev Tools is an extension created by the React team. It enables developers to debug their code inside their Developer Tools. Once you add the extension, you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aman Kalra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accounting Number Format in Excel – How to Apply it to Selected Cells]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/accounting-number-format-in-excel-how-to-apply-it-to-selected-cells/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/accounting-number-format-in-excel-how-to-apply-it-to-selected-cells/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T18:11:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article I will show you how to format cells in Microsoft Excel. We'll be looking particularly at the Accounting format for cells with numbers.  At the end of the article I'll give you two bonuses: a short video walkthrough of the methods we go over, as well]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developing Games Using Unreal Engine 5]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/developing-games-using-unreal-engine-5/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/developing-games-using-unreal-engine-5/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T15:27:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unreal Engine 5 is a powerful game engine that has been used to create some of the most popular and critically acclaimed games in recent years.  We just published an 11-hour Unreal Engine course for beginners on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Sourav created this coruse. He has 7 years]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[:has is an unforgiving selector]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376342</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/has-is-an-unforgiving-selector/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T14:18:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A little thing happened on the way to publishing the CSS :has() selector to the ol’ Almanac. I had originally described :has() as a “forgiving” selector, the idea being that anything in its argument is evaluated, even if one or …
:has is an unforgiving selector originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Closed Captions And Subtitles UX]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/closed-captions-subtitles-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/closed-captions-subtitles-ux/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-11T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Captioning can be much more than text. Design patterns for better UX of subtitles, captions, video players, transcripts and on-screen text.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS by Building the Git Logo in Pure CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-git-logo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-css-create-the-git-logo/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T18:54:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the best ways to learn CSS is by creating something useful while you learn. I will show you how to use the following CSS items by creating the Git logo:  * Transform to rotate an image  * position relative and absolute  * pseudo classes ::before]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Bland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL CONVERT – The DATE to String or DATETIME Function]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-convert-the-date-to-string-or-datetime-function-2/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-convert-the-date-to-string-or-datetime-function-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T18:30:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working with SQL, you'll need to learn how to format dates properly. This is because dates are an important aspect of any SQL and other software-related activities. You need to be able to work with dates to add timestamps to entries and keep track of when things happen,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Joins – LEFT Join, RIGHT Join, and INNER Join Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-sql-joins/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-sql-joins/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T18:23:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SQL is a programming language we use to interact with relational databases. SQL databases contain tables, which contain rows of data. These tables usually contain similar or related data. In an office management web application database, you would have tables for  employees, their departments, their managers, the projects they]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zubair Idris Aweda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Performance – How to Improve Page Speed with async and defer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-performance-async-defer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-performance-async-defer/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T18:18:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In web programming, JavaScript brings interactiveness and dynamic behaviour to your web pages. While HTML and CSS take care of the structure and aesthetics of the pages, they will be merely usable without JavaScript doing its job in the background. You can include JavaScript code in the HTML file in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TAPAS ADHIKARY</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Projects for Beginners in 2023 – Fun Ideas with Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-projects-for-beginners-easy-ideas-with-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-projects-for-beginners-easy-ideas-with-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T17:53:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You're ready to start making simple projects with React, but you don't know what to make. Where should you start? I have created seven unique and fun React projects for you to make, all of which will teach you essential React concepts that you need to know in 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Faking Min Width on a Table Column]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376307</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/faking-min-width-on-a-table-column/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T15:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The good ol’ <table> tag is the most semantic HTML for showing tabular data. But I find it very hard to control how the table is presented, particularly column widths in a dynamic environment where you might not know how …
Faking Min Width on a Table Column originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anders Pedersen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Your Collaboration Problems Go Away By Sharing Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/sharing-components-designers-developers-collaboration-problems/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/sharing-components-designers-developers-collaboration-problems/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-10T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently UXPin has extended its powerful Merge technology by adding npm integration, allowing designers to sync React component libraries without requiring any developer input. This new step aims to improve collaboration between designers and developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shane Hudson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Styling Buttons in WordPress Block Themes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376237</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/styling-buttons-in-wordpress-block-themes/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T13:56:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A little while back, Ganesh Dahal penned a post here on CSS-Tricks responding to a tweet that asked about adding CSS box shadows on WordPress blocks and elements. There’s a lot of great stuff in there that leverages new features …
Styling Buttons in WordPress Block Themes originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fränk Klein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Authentication In Websites: A Banking Analogy]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/authentication-websites-banking-analogy/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/authentication-websites-banking-analogy/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-09T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is Eric Burel’s attempt at making the implementation of authentication less obscure. You’ll learn about tokens, authorization, CORS, credentials, HTTP headers, and such.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Burel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Getting Data Visualization Right]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/guide-getting-data-visualization-right/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/guide-getting-data-visualization-right/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-05T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Sara Dholakia presents a guide on how to choose just the right type of data visualization, with guidelines and things to keep in mind.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sara Dholakia)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The State Of Usability In 2023 🎊]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/usability-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/01/usability-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-01-02T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That’s how people behave on the web in 2023. Some observations from real usability testing on what people do and what they don’t do on the web. From disabled copy-paste to magic link sign-in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opening The Doors To 2023 (January Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2023/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-31T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s start into the new year with a little inspiration boost: wallpapers created with love by the community for the community. Happy 2023!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fluid Typography: Predicting A Problem With Your User’s Zoom-In]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/fluid-typography-predict-problem-users-zoom-in/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/fluid-typography-predict-problem-users-zoom-in/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-30T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Ruslan Yevych will show you an easy way how to predict the appearance of a problem known as WCAG Failure Under 1.4.4 Resize Text (AA) while zooming the page. You will have a clear understanding of the possible risks of using responsive typography at the stage of development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ruslan Yevych)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thank You (2022 Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375486</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/thank-you-2022-edition/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-28T15:46:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You know, this is the time of year where Chris normally publishes a big ol’ reflection of the past year. The first one was published in 2007, the same year CSS-Tricks began, and it continued all the way through 2021…
Thank You (2022 Edition) originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Command-Line Data Manipulation]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/guide-command-line-data-manipulation-cli-miller/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/guide-command-line-data-manipulation-cli-miller/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-27T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No more random scripts in Python and JavaScript to transform CSV or JSON data. In this article, Alvin Bryan shows you how to use Miller, a small and powerful CLI tool, to do all your data processing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alvin Bryan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying CSS Logical Properties On Web Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/deploying-css-logical-properties-on-web-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/deploying-css-logical-properties-on-web-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have already heard of CSS logical properties or RTL adaptations but are still deciding whether to deploy them widely. To help raise your awareness of their possibilities, Nicolas Hoffmann shares his experience of how he and his team at Proton carried out a massive move from CSS logical props to production and how you can consider them from a different perspective in your very own projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nicolas Hoffmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022 Roundup of Web Research]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375869</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/2022-roundup-of-web-research/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-21T15:03:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve started making a tradition of rounding up the latest front-end research at the end of each year. We did it in 2020 and again in 2021. Reports are released throughout the year by a bunch of different companies …
2022 Roundup of Web Research originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Help choose the syntax for CSS Nesting]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376319</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/help-choose-the-syntax-for-css-nesting/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T16:04:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Nesting is making the rounds yet again. Remember earlier this year when Adam and Miriam put three syntax options up for a vote? Those results were tallied and it wasn’t even even close.
Now there’s another chance …
Help choose the syntax for CSS Nesting originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful Accessibility And Usability Examples To Help Improve Your Designs]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/useful-accessibility-usability-examples-help-improve-your-designs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/useful-accessibility-usability-examples-help-improve-your-designs/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-20T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Thomas Bohm shares strategies and methods to tackle some common graphic communication problems and gives you insights into how to improve accessibility and usability and make your designs much better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Thomas Bohm)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Playground: Running WordPress in the Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376297</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/wordpress-playground-run-in-browser/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T16:52:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being able to quickly spin up a WordPress instance has been the strength of WordPress ever since its famous “five-minute install”. Upload a few files, configure a few settings, and you’re off.
The friction of uploading files has gotten …
WordPress Playground: Running WordPress in the Browser originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taking The Stress Out Of Design System Management]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/taking-stress-out-design-system-management/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/taking-stress-out-design-system-management/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Masha goes over five tips that make it easier to manage a design system while increasing its effectiveness. This short guide is aimed at smaller teams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Masha Shaposhnikova)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Infinite 3D Sliders]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375621</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-infinite-3d-sliders/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T14:58:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this series, we’ve been making image sliders with nothing but HTML and CSS. The idea is that we can use the same markup but different CSS to get wildly different results, no matter how many images we toss …
CSS Infinite 3D Sliders originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boosting Productivity For Designers With Efficient Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/optimizing-design-workflow-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/optimizing-design-workflow-tools/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-16T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Ashish Bogawat shares some of his favorite ways how to boost productivity and do things faster, better, and probably more fun by using efficient tools and workflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ashish Bogawat)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So, you’d like to animate the display property]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375714</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/so-youd-like-to-animate-the-display-property/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T15:41:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS Working Group gave that a thumbs-up a couple weeks ago. The super-duper conceptual proposal being that we can animate or transition from, say, display: block to display: none.
It’s a bit of a brain-twister to reason …
So, you’d like to animate the display property originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Prioritize User Security When Collecting Offline Data]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/prioritize-user-security-collecting-offline-data/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/prioritize-user-security-collecting-offline-data/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Concerns over online privacy and security are nothing new. In this article, Suzanne Scacca explores how the right CSV importer can help businesses better prioritize user security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Suzanne Scacca)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Links on AI-Related Stuff]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376201</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/some-links-on-ai-related-stuff/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-14T21:34:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every so often, I find that the links I save to read later fall into natural groups or patterns that reveal common threads of interest. The past couple of weeks have produced a lot of thoughts about ChatGPT, an …
Some Links on AI-Related Stuff originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unchain My Inaccessibly-Labelled Heart]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375952</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/unchain-my-inaccessibly-labelled-heart/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-14T14:08:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Suzy Naschansky from the HTMHell Advent Calendar:
<h2 id="article1-heading"All About Dragons</h2<pI like dragons. Blah blah blah blah blah.</p<p<a id="article1-read-more" aria-labelledby="article1-read-more article1-heading"Read more</a</p
See that aria-labelledby attribute? It chains two IDs from the …
Unchain My Inaccessibly-Labelled Heart originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Holiday Snowtacular 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=376229</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/holiday-snowtacular-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T23:03:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve got ourselves a real holiday treat! Join host Alex Trost from the Frontend Horse community for the Holiday Snowtacular 2022 this Friday, December 16.
There’s a lineup of 12 awesome speakers — including Chris Coyier, Cassidy Williams, Kevin …
Holiday Snowtacular 2022 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Privacy: Protect Your Users, Protect Yourself]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/understanding-privacy-protect-your-users-protect-yourself/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/understanding-privacy-protect-your-users-protect-yourself/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All of us want to create inclusive, safe, and privacy-aware digital experiences, but where to begin? Our brand new Smashing Book, “Understanding Privacy,” written by Heather Burns, can help you lay the ground for future developers, designers, and project managers to build a better web for tomorrow. [Jump to the details](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/understanding-privacy-new-smashing-book/#about-the-book) or [get the book right away](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/printed-books/understanding-privacy/).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Heather Burns)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible Front-End Patterns For Responsive Tables (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/accessible-front-end-patterns-responsive-tables-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/12/accessible-front-end-patterns-responsive-tables-part2/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no universal solution for making every kind of table responsive and usable on smaller screens, so we have to rely on various patterns, which Adrian explains in this two-part series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Few Times Container Size Queries Would Have Helped Me Out]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=375728</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-few-times-container-size-queries-would-have-helped-me-out/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T13:53:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Container Queries are still gaining traction and many of us are getting our hands wet with them, even if it’s for little experiments or whatnot. They’ve got great, but not quite full, browser support — enough to justify using …
A Few Times Container Size Queries Would Have Helped Me Out originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Christofi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>