<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-05-01T00:11:32.010Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-05-01T00:11:32.010Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make Your May Magnificent (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-30T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May is almost here, so what better occasion could there be for some fresh and inspiring desktop and mobile wallpapers? Created with love by artists and designers from across the globe, the wallpapers in this post come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Hoisting in JavaScript | Hoisting Functions, Variables and Classes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-hoisting-in-javascript-3/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-hoisting-in-javascript-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T14:54:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hoisting is a concept or behavior in JavaScript where the declaration of a function, variable, or class goes to the top of the scope they were defined in. What does this mean? Hoisting is a concept you may find in some programming languages (such as JavaScript) and not in others.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pub/Sub in Redis – How to Use the Publish/Subscribe Messaging Pattern]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-pub-sub-in-redis/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-pub-sub-in-redis/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T14:33:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working on an application that needs to be easily maintainable, scalable, and performant, the Publish/Subscribe messaging pattern is a good choice. The idea behind it is simple, but powerful. We have senders called publishers.  Their sole role is to send or publish messages. They don’t care about]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mihail Gaberov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Intruders – Top Ways Hackers Can Breach Your Smartphone’s Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-hackers-can-breach-your-smartphones-security/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-hackers-can-breach-your-smartphones-security/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T14:16:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smartphones are integral to our lives, making them prime targets for hackers. In this article, we will go through 7 ways hackers can gain access to your smartphone and how to protect against these attacks. Smartphones have become an essential part of our daily lives with instant access to information]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Punct in RegEx? How to Match All Punctuation Marks in Regular Expressions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-punct-in-regex-how-to-match-all-punctuation-marks-in-regular-expressions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-punct-in-regex-how-to-match-all-punctuation-marks-in-regular-expressions/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T11:28:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In regular expressions, "punct" means punctuation marks. It is all non-word and non-space characters. "Punct" is a predefined character class in regular expressions, and you can use it in any regex flavor that supports it. The Punct character class is denoted by \p{Punct} or simply \p{P}. It matches any punctuation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Write Better CSS By Borrowing Ideas From JavaScript Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/write-better-css-borrow-ideas-javascript-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/write-better-css-borrow-ideas-javascript-functions/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many problems with website layouts happen when we don’t write CSS with the same care we’d use when writing a JavaScript function. Let’s look at how we can borrow best practices and ideas from writing good JavaScript functions for writing CSS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yaphi Berhanu)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[strcmp in C – How to Compare Strings in C]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/strcmp-in-c-how-to-compare-strings-in-c/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/strcmp-in-c-how-to-compare-strings-in-c/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T20:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comparing strings is a common task in most programming languages. In C, you can use the strcmp function to handle string comparisons.  In this article, I will show you practical examples of the strcmp function, and offer insights into how it compares strings, what its return values mean, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Merge – The Definitive Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-definitive-guide-to-git-merge/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-definitive-guide-to-git-merge/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T17:07:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By reading this post, you are going to really understand git merge, one of the most common operations you'll perform in your Git repositories. Notes before we start  1. I also created two videos covering the contents of this post. If you wish to     watch]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Rosenbaum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Scrapy for Web Scraping in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-scrapy-for-web-scraping-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-scrapy-for-web-scraping-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T15:44:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you tired of manually collecting data from websites? Have you ever wished you could automate the process and gather massive amounts of data in a fraction of the time? We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to scrape websites with Python]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The REST API Handbook – How to Build, Test, Consume, and Document REST APIs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-consume-and-document-a-rest-api/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-consume-and-document-a-rest-api/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T13:55:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this tutorial we're going to take a deep dive into REST APIs. I recently wrote this article [/news/rest-vs-graphql-apis/] where I explained the main differences between common API types nowadays. And this tutorial aims to show you an example of how you can fully implement a REST API.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do I Enable Square Brackets in RegEx?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-do-i-enable-square-brackets-in-regex/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-do-i-enable-square-brackets-in-regex/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T12:31:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you’ll learn about what square brackets do in regular expressions, how to use them for specifying ranges, and how to match them as a character. What Does Square Bracket Do in RegEx? In regular expressions, square brackets ([ ]) are characters that have a special meaning of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible Target Sizes Cheatsheet]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/accessible-tap-target-sizes-rage-taps-clicks/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/accessible-tap-target-sizes-rage-taps-clicks/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Practical guidelines to prevent rage taps and rage clicks with accessible tap targets for icons, links and buttons — on desktop and on mobile. With useful techniques and guidelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Ternary Operator – Conditional Operators in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-tenary-operator/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-tenary-operator/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T15:29:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use conditional operators in Python to execute code based on a predefined condition(s).  In this article, you'll learn how to use the ternary operator in Python. You'll see its syntax along with some practical examples.  What Is the Ternary Operator Used for in Python? The ternary]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Potentially Dangerous Non-Accessibility Of Cookie Notices]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/potentially-dangerous-non-accessibility-cookie-notices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/potentially-dangerous-non-accessibility-cookie-notices/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this piece, a Web Content Accessibility Guidelines (WCAG) auditor shares some cookie banner error patterns that can massively hurt a page’s overall conformance. Let’s explore what to look out for with this omnipresent piece of the web interface.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Marcus Herrmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring The Potential Of Web Workers For Multithreading On The Web]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/potential-web-workers-multithreading-web/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/potential-web-workers-multithreading-web/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Sarah Oke Okolo explores the importance of Web Workers for multithreading on the web, including the limitations and considerations of using them and the strategies for mitigating potential issues associated with them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sarah Oke Okolo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building And Dockerizing A Node.js App With Stateless Architecture With Help From Kinsta]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/building-dockerizing-nodejs-app-stateless-architecture-kinsta/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/building-dockerizing-nodejs-app-stateless-architecture-kinsta/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dockerizing your Node.js apps can lead to smashing success—offering consistency, easy debugging, and hassle-free dependency management. When you host this container on Kinsta, you also benefit from high-speed performance, robust security, and top-notch scalability. By combining these two, you'll surely have a whale of a time as you sail smoothly through the development seas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tejas Kumar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Color Mechanics In UI Kits]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/color-mechanics-ui-kits/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/color-mechanics-ui-kits/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Adel Khamatov shares a model of color mechanics that he came up with during research on developing UI kits and illustrates an approach to solving related problems with best practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adel Khamatov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 59 With Chiara Aliotta: What Is Design Storytelling?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/smashing-podcast-episode-59/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/smashing-podcast-episode-59/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of The Smashing Podcast, we take a look at design storytelling. What is it, and how can it help us shape digital experiences? Vitaly talks to Chiara Aliotta to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Design Thinking?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/what-is-design-thinking/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/what-is-design-thinking/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered if things could have been done differently? But not sure how? Well, then, do not fall in love with the solution, but fall in love with the problem! Here’s an article to dive deep into how design thinking could do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Krithika Subramanian)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passkeys: What the Heck and Why?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377305</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/passkeys-what-the-heck-and-why/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T17:41:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These things called passkeys sure are making the rounds these days. They were a main attraction at W3C TPAC 2022, gained support in Safari 16, are finding their way into macOS and iOS, and are slated to …
Passkeys: What the Heck and Why? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Neal Fennimore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Design An Effective User Onboarding Flow]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/design-effective-user-onboarding-flow/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/design-effective-user-onboarding-flow/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to maximize conversions or collect necessary user information for other purposes, a user onboarding flow is necessary. In this article, you will learn how, with the help of Feathery, to design an effective user onboarding flow for your app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Suzanne Scacca)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Protect Your App With A Threat Model Based On JSONDiff]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/protect-app-threat-model-jsondiff/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/protect-app-threat-model-jsondiff/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a developer who wants to concentrate on delivering a killer application rather than worrying about countless security issues, threat model documents can help you do that. With small architectural changes, we can make these threats manageable and prevent them in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zack Grossbart &amp; Terry Yao)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Algorithms: Skills Of Designers That AI Can’t Replicate]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/skills-designers-ai-cant-replicate/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/skills-designers-ai-cant-replicate/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article highlights non-technical skills like curiosity, observation, empathy, advocacy, visual communication, and collaboration that designers routinely use in their process to make a difference through design. AI can be used to augment designers’ workflow instead of replacing people.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lyndon Cerejo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>